Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Yes! That is my ring! Please! It grants me Divine Intervention! Now I can escape! Give it to me NOW! I don't care about anything else...","Yes! That is my ring! Please! It grants me Divine Intervention! Now I can escape! Give it to me NOW! I don't care about anything else...","fbmwICOracleA_GREETING_0002a4ee_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"just let me out of here!","just let me out of here!","fbmwICOracleA_GREETING_0002a4ee_2"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Yes! That is my ring! Please! It grants me Divine Intervention! Now I can escape! Give it to me NOW! I don't care about anything else...","Yes! That is my ring! Please! It grants me Divine Intervention! Now I can escape! Give it to me NOW! I don't care about anything else...","fbmwICOracleA_GREETING_00f886a6_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"just let me out of here!","just let me out of here!","fbmwICOracleA_GREETING_00f886a6_2"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Yes! That is my ring! Please! It grants me Divine Intervention! Now I can escape! Give it to me NOW! I don't care about anything else...","Yes! That is my ring! Please! It grants me Divine Intervention! Now I can escape! Give it to me NOW! I don't care about anything else...","fbmwICOracleA_GREETING_00f886a5_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"just let me out of here!","just let me out of here!","fbmwICOracleA_GREETING_00f886a5_2"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Bring me my ring! BRING ME MY RING!","Bring me my ring! BRING ME MY RING!","fbmwICOracleA_GREETING_0002a4ef_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Please. Llaren Terano is a sorcerer and worshipper of Molag Bal. He is a terrible sorcerer, but he also carries a deadly sword.","Please. Llaren Terano is a sorcerer and worshipper of Molag Bal. He is a terrible sorcerer, but he also carries a deadly sword.","fbmwICOracleA_GREETING_0002a4f0_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"He stripped me and made me his prisoner. That's all I can remember. I can't recall how I got here, or why.","He stripped me and made me his prisoner. That's all I can remember. I can't recall how I got here, or why.","fbmwICOracleA_GREETING_0002a4f0_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I think he has poisoned my mind with spells. If you can recover my ring from Llaren Terano, I can use its enchantments to escape.","I think he has poisoned my mind with spells. If you can recover my ring from Llaren Terano, I can use its enchantments to escape.","fbmwICOracleA_GREETING_0002a4f0_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Please, rescue these slaves, too, if you can. Llaren Terano has their slave key. Bring me my ring. Please.","Please, rescue these slaves, too, if you can. Llaren Terano has their slave key. Bring me my ring. Please.","fbmwICOracleA_GREETING_0002a4f0_4"
"","","Healing Altar",Neutral,50,"You may pray at Imperial cult healing altars and receive blessings which cure common and blight diseases, cure poisons, and restore attributes.","You may pray at Imperial cult healing altars and receive blessings which cure common and blight diseases, cure poisons, and restore attributes.","MorroDefaultQuest_1healingSaltar_00321738_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Non-members pay 25 drakes. Newer members pay 10 drakes, while higher-ranking members receive blessings free.","Non-members pay 25 drakes. Newer members pay 10 drakes, while higher-ranking members receive blessings free.","MorroDefaultQuest_1healingSaltar_00321738_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Healing altars are found in: Vivec Foreign Quarter; Wolverine Hall in Sadrith Mora; Fort Buckmoth; Fort Moonmoth; Fort Pelagiad; Fort Darius;","Healing altars are found in: Vivec Foreign Quarter; Wolverine Hall in Sadrith Mora; Fort Buckmoth; Fort Moonmoth; Fort Pelagiad; Fort Darius;","MorroDefaultQuest_1healingSaltar_00321738_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Ald'ruhn Guild of Mages, and Imperial Chapels in Ebonheart.","Ald'ruhn Guild of Mages, and Imperial Chapels in Ebonheart.","MorroDefaultQuest_1healingSaltar_00321738_4"
"","","Services",Neutral,50,"You can find Imperial cult services in Fort Buckmoth, Fort Moonmoth, Fort Pelagiad, Fort Darius, Wolverine Hall in Sadrith Mora, Vivec Foreign Quarter, and Imperial chapels in Ebonheart.","You can find Imperial cult services in Fort Buckmoth, Fort Moonmoth, Fort Pelagiad, Fort Darius, Wolverine Hall in Sadrith Mora, Vivec Foreign Quarter, and Imperial chapels in Ebonheart.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Services_003228a7_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Seek training at Wolverine Hall, Fort Buckmoth, Fort Moonmoth, Ebonheart Imperial Chapels, Governor's Hall in Caldera, and Ald Velothi Outpost.","Seek training at Wolverine Hall, Fort Buckmoth, Fort Moonmoth, Ebonheart Imperial Chapels, Governor's Hall in Caldera, and Ald Velothi Outpost.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Services_003228a7_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Many Imperial cult locations have healing altars.","Many Imperial cult locations have healing altars.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Services_003228a7_3"
