Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"We still need four pieces of scrap metal to fix the centurions. Have you found some?","We still need four pieces of scrap metal to fix the centurions. Have you found some?","fbmwTGAldruhnDefenses_GREETING_0000ce4a_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Any luck getting hold of Boethiah's Pillow Book? I'm sure Gandosa has a copy.","Any luck getting hold of Boethiah's Pillow Book? I'm sure Gandosa has a copy.","fbmwTGBadGandosa_GREETING_0000ce4c_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Well,  have you been able to recover the Daggers of Judgement?","Well,  have you been able to recover the Daggers of Judgement?","fbmwTGDartsJudgement_GREETING_0000bfb7_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Do you have that Redoran Master Helm?","Do you have that Redoran Master Helm?","fbmwTGMasterHelm_GREETING_0000ce4d_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Have you returned with a copy of Withershins?","Have you returned with a copy of Withershins?","fbmwTGWithershins_GREETING_0000ce4b_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"You were sent to fetch Anareren's Devil Tanto from the Guild of Mages. What happened?","You were sent to fetch Anareren's Devil Tanto from the Guild of Mages. What happened?","fbmwTGLootAldruhnMG_GREETING_0000ce4e_1"
"","","Anareren's Devil Tanto",Neutral,50,"You've been kicked out of the Guild,&sUActnQuick1;. Better make amends, or no one's going to talk to you.","You've been kicked out of the Guild,&sUActnQuick1;. Better make amends, or no one's going to talk to you.","fbmwTGLootAldruhnMG_1AnarerenAsSDevilSTanto_00320547_1"
"","","Anareren's Devil Tanto",Neutral,50,"You already gave me the Devil Tanto.","You already gave me the Devil Tanto.","fbmwTGLootAldruhnMG_1AnarerenAsSDevilSTanto_0001c6ba_1"
"","","Anareren's Devil Tanto",Neutral,50,"Did you run into any trouble?","Did you run into any trouble?","fbmwTGLootAldruhnMG_1AnarerenAsSDevilSTanto_00320550_1"
"","","Anareren's Devil Tanto",Neutral,50,"Like I said, my source in the Mages Guild says they'll all be gone for a while.","Like I said, my source in the Mages Guild says they'll all be gone for a while.","fbmwTGLootAldruhnMG_1AnarerenAsSDevilSTanto_0001c6b8_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Go in there and take whatever you want, but be sure to bring me Anareren's Devil Tanto.","Go in there and take whatever you want, but be sure to bring me Anareren's Devil Tanto.","fbmwTGLootAldruhnMG_1AnarerenAsSDevilSTanto_0001c6b8_2"
"","","Anareren's Devil Tanto",Neutral,50,"Like I said, my source in the Mages Guild says they'll all be gone for a while.","Like I said, my source in the Mages Guild says they'll all be gone for a while.","fbmwTGLootAldruhnMG_1AnarerenAsSDevilSTanto_0001c6b9_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Go in there and take whatever you want, but be sure to bring me Anareren's Devil Tanto.","Go in there and take whatever you want, but be sure to bring me Anareren's Devil Tanto.","fbmwTGLootAldruhnMG_1AnarerenAsSDevilSTanto_0001c6b9_2"
"","","Boethiah's Pillow Book",Neutral,50,"You've been kicked out of the Guild, taffer. Better make amends, or no one's going to talk to you.","You've been kicked out of the Guild, taffer. Better make amends, or no one's going to talk to you.","fbmwTGBadGandosa_1BoethiahAsSPillowSBook_00320551_1"
"","","Boethiah's Pillow Book",Neutral,50,"You already gave me that book.","You already gave me that book.","fbmwTGBadGandosa_1BoethiahAsSPillowSBook_00034fe7_1"
"","","Boethiah's Pillow Book",Neutral,50,"Is that Boethiah's Pillow Book? You didn't happen to find that in Arobar Manor, did you?","Is that Boethiah's Pillow Book? You didn't happen to find that in Arobar Manor, did you?","fbmwTGBadGandosa_1BoethiahAsSPillowSBook_00034fe9_1"
"","","Boethiah's Pillow Book",Neutral,50,"Did you get the book?","Did you get the book?","fbmwTGBadGandosa_1BoethiahAsSPillowSBook_00034fe8_1"
"","","Boethiah's Pillow Book",Neutral,50,"A client of ours wants some dirt on the Arobar family. Apparently Gandosa Arobar has a copy of this book, which has been banned by the Temple.","A client of ours wants some dirt on the Arobar family. Apparently Gandosa Arobar has a copy of this book, which has been banned by the Temple.","fbmwTGBadGandosa_1BoethiahAsSPillowSBook_0032055b_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Fetch the book and return it to me. I have to admit I'm a bit curious myself.","Fetch the book and return it to me. I have to admit I'm a bit curious myself.","fbmwTGBadGandosa_1BoethiahAsSPillowSBook_0032055b_2"
"","","Gentleman Jim Stacey",Neutral,50,"Look for him in Vivec. You'll find him in the basement of Simine Fralinie's bookstore in the Foreign Quarter.","Look for him in Vivec. You'll find him in the basement of Simine Fralinie's bookstore in the Foreign Quarter.","MorroDefaultQuest_1GentlemanSJimSStacey_003207fa_1"
"","","Redoran Master Helm",Neutral,50,"You've been kicked out of the Guild, outlander. Better make amends, or no one's going to talk to you.","You've been kicked out of the Guild, outlander. Better make amends, or no one's going to talk to you.","fbmwTGMasterHelm_1RedoranSMasterSHelm_003208a4_1"
"","","Redoran Master Helm",Neutral,50,"You already brought me a Redoran Master Helm.","You already brought me a Redoran Master Helm.","fbmwTGMasterHelm_1RedoranSMasterSHelm_00034fe6_1"
"","","Redoran Master Helm",Neutral,50,"A client of ours wants a Redoran Master Helm, and I see you have one on you. Will you hand this over to the Guild, or get us another one?","A client of ours wants a Redoran Master Helm, and I see you have one on you. Will you hand this over to the Guild, or get us another one?","fbmwTGMasterHelm_1RedoranSMasterSHelm_00034fe5_1"
"","","Redoran Master Helm",Neutral,50,"Did you get a Redoran Master Helm?","Did you get a Redoran Master Helm?","fbmwTGMasterHelm_1RedoranSMasterSHelm_00034fe4_1"
"","","Redoran Master Helm",Neutral,50,"A client of ours wants a Redoran Master Helm. Most of the Councilors in House Redoran have one, but they can be hard to find.","A client of ours wants a Redoran Master Helm. Most of the Councilors in House Redoran have one, but they can be hard to find.","fbmwTGMasterHelm_1RedoranSMasterSHelm_003208a9_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I know Miner Arobar has one, probably in his bedroom. You'd have to check Arobar Manor here in Ald'ruhn, Under-Skar.","I know Miner Arobar has one, probably in his bedroom. You'd have to check Arobar Manor here in Ald'ruhn, Under-Skar.","fbmwTGMasterHelm_1RedoranSMasterSHelm_003208a9_2"
"","","Aengoth the Jeweler",Neutral,50,"Yes?","Yes?","MorroDefaultQuest_1AengothStheSJeweler_00320814_1"
"","","Daggers of Judgement",Neutral,50,"You've been kicked out of the Guild, taffer. Better make amends, or no one's going to talk to you.","You've been kicked out of the Guild, taffer. Better make amends, or no one's going to talk to you.","fbmwTGDartsJudgement_1DartsSofSJudgement_0032096b_1"
"","","Daggers of Judgement",Neutral,50,"You've already reported back to me about the Darts of Judgement.","You've already reported back to me about the Darts of Judgement.","fbmwTGDartsJudgement_1DartsSofSJudgement_00034fed_1"
"","","Daggers of Judgement",Neutral,50,"So you found the Darts of Judgement. Do you want to keep them or sell them to the Guild?","So you found the Darts of Judgement. Do you want to keep them or sell them to the Guild?","fbmwTGDartsJudgement_1DartsSofSJudgement_00320973_1"
"","","Daggers of Judgement",Neutral,50,"Eindel has four Darts of Judgement. They're very rare arrows made in my home province of Valenwood. Eindel is a guard at Llethri Manor in Ald'ruhn.","Eindel has four Darts of Judgement. They're very rare arrows made in my home province of Valenwood. Eindel is a guard at Llethri Manor in Ald'ruhn.","fbmwTGDartsJudgement_1DartsSofSJudgement_00320974_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If you find the Darts there, feel free to use them, but the Guild will pay good money if you don't want them.","If you find the Darts there, feel free to use them, but the Guild will pay good money if you don't want them.","fbmwTGDartsJudgement_1DartsSofSJudgement_00320974_2"
"","","Alms for the poor",Neutral,50,"You have my contribution.","You have my contribution.","fbmwICBuckmothAlms_1almsSforStheSpoor_00f8a34f_1"
"","","Alms for the poor",Neutral,50,"You're right. We all must do our part. Here. It's not much, but it's all I can spare.","You're right. We all must do our part. Here. It's not much, but it's all I can spare.","fbmwICBuckmothAlms_1almsSforStheSpoor_00f8a350_1"
"","","Alms for the poor",Neutral,50,"It's a worthy cause. Sorry, but this is all I can afford.","It's a worthy cause. Sorry, but this is all I can afford.","fbmwICBuckmothAlms_1almsSforStheSpoor_00f8a351_1"
"","","Sugar-Lips Habasi",Neutral,50,"You can find her in Balmora, at the South Wall Cornerclub.","You can find her in Balmora, at the South Wall Cornerclub.","MorroDefaultQuest_1SugarTLipsSHabasi_00320c64_1"
"","","Little Advice",Neutral,50,"You look like you're looking for something. It might be you'll find it at the Rat in the Pot. A fellow named Aengoth the Jeweler.","You look like you're looking for something. It might be you'll find it at the Rat in the Pot. A fellow named Aengoth the Jeweler.","MorroDefaultQuest_1littleSadvice_003218fa_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"He's good at looking for things. And finding them. And a warning. Stay clear of the Camonna Tong.","He's good at looking for things. And finding them. And a warning. Stay clear of the Camonna Tong.","MorroDefaultQuest_1littleSadvice_003218fa_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"They don't like outlanders, and what they don't like, they kill.","They don't like outlanders, and what they don't like, they kill.","MorroDefaultQuest_1littleSadvice_003218fa_3"
"","","Arobar Manor",Neutral,50,"It's here in Ald'ruhn, Under-Skar.","It's here in Ald'ruhn, Under-Skar.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ArobarSManor_00321ac7_1"
"","","Scrap Metal",Neutral,50,"You've been kicked out of the Guild, outlander. Better make amends, or no one's going to talk to you.","You've been kicked out of the Guild, outlander. Better make amends, or no one's going to talk to you.","fbmwTGAldruhnDefenses_1scrapSmetal_00321e71_1"
"","","Scrap Metal",Neutral,50,"You already brought me some scrap metal. Estoril can keep the Centurions working for a while.","You already brought me some scrap metal. Estoril can keep the Centurions working for a while.","fbmwTGAldruhnDefenses_1scrapSmetal_00034fec_1"
"","","Scrap Metal",Neutral,50,"Did you find some scrap metal?","Did you find some scrap metal?","fbmwTGAldruhnDefenses_1scrapSmetal_00034feb_1"
"","","Scrap Metal",Neutral,50,"You can find scrap metal in most Dwemer ruins. I wish I knew a better place to get some, but I don't.","You can find scrap metal in most Dwemer ruins. I wish I knew a better place to get some, but I don't.","fbmwTGAldruhnDefenses_1scrapSmetal_00321e76_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"We need four pieces of scrap metal to be on the safe side, but you don't need to try and clear out a Dwemer ruin, just run in, snatch some, and get out.","We need four pieces of scrap metal to be on the safe side, but you don't need to try and clear out a Dwemer ruin, just run in, snatch some, and get out.","fbmwTGAldruhnDefenses_1scrapSmetal_00321e76_2"
"","","Withershins",Neutral,50,"You've been kicked out of the Guild. Better make amends, or no one's going to talk to you.","You've been kicked out of the Guild. Better make amends, or no one's going to talk to you.","fbmwTGWithershins_1Withershins_00321ece_1"
"","","Withershins",Neutral,50,"You already brought me a copy of "Withershins."","You already brought me a copy of "Withershins."","fbmwTGWithershins_1Withershins_0002534f_1"
"","","Withershins",Neutral,50,"You've been kicked out of the Guild, taffer. Better make amends, or no one's going to talk to you.","You've been kicked out of the Guild, taffer. Better make amends, or no one's going to talk to you.","fbmwTGWithershins_1Withershins_00321edd_1"
"","","Withershins",Neutral,50,"Did you get a copy of "Withershins?"","Did you get a copy of "Withershins?"","fbmwTGWithershins_1Withershins_00321ee2_1"
"","","Withershins",Neutral,50,"Another client wants us to find a copy of this book for him. It's not for sale if you know what I mean.","Another client wants us to find a copy of this book for him. It's not for sale if you know what I mean.","fbmwTGWithershins_1Withershins_00321ed4_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I've heard that Miles Gloriosus over at the Andus Tradehouse in Maar Gan has a copy.","I've heard that Miles Gloriosus over at the Andus Tradehouse in Maar Gan has a copy.","fbmwTGWithershins_1Withershins_00321ed4_2"
"","","Withershins",Neutral,50,"Another client wants us to find a copy of this book for him. It's not for sale if you know what I mean.","Another client wants us to find a copy of this book for him. It's not for sale if you know what I mean.","fbmwTGWithershins_1Withershins_00321ee3_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I've heard that Miles Gloriosus over at the Andus Tradehouse in Maar Gan has a copy.","I've heard that Miles Gloriosus over at the Andus Tradehouse in Maar Gan has a copy.","fbmwTGWithershins_1Withershins_00321ee3_2"
"","","Big Helende",Neutral,50,"Go to Sadrith Mora. You'll find Big Helende at Dirty Muriel's Cornerclub. It's quite a place.","Go to Sadrith Mora. You'll find Big Helende at Dirty Muriel's Cornerclub. It's quite a place.","MorroDefaultQuest_1BigSHelende_00322024_1"
"","","Jobs",Neutral,50,"I got no jobs for you. Try Sugar-Lips Habasi in Balmora or Big Helende in Sadrith Mora. Or you could talk to the Master Thief himself, Gentleman Jim Stacey. He's in Vivec, but is very choosy about who he has work for him.","I got no jobs for you. Try Sugar-Lips Habasi in Balmora or Big Helende in Sadrith Mora. Or you could talk to the Master Thief himself, Gentleman Jim Stacey. He's in Vivec, but is very choosy about who he has work for him.","fbmwTGAdvancement_1jobs_0003414d_1"
"","","Jobs",Neutral,50,"Eindel, a Bosmer like me, has some fine arrows, the Darts of Judgement.","Eindel, a Bosmer like me, has some fine arrows, the Darts of Judgement.","fbmwTGAdvancement_1jobs_0003414c_1"
"","","Jobs",Neutral,50,"We got some Dwemer Spider Centurions from a friend, and we got Estoril who can fix them up, but we don't have any scrap metal.","We got some Dwemer Spider Centurions from a friend, and we got Estoril who can fix them up, but we don't have any scrap metal.","fbmwTGAdvancement_1jobs_0003414b_1"
"","","Jobs",Neutral,50,"There's another book I want you to fetch for me. It's called "Withershins."","There's another book I want you to fetch for me. It's called "Withershins."","fbmwTGAdvancement_1jobs_0003414a_1"
"","","Jobs",Neutral,50,"Gandosa Arobar is a Councilor's daughter if you know what I mean. I hear she's got a copy of Boethiah's Pillow Book.","Gandosa Arobar is a Councilor's daughter if you know what I mean. I hear she's got a copy of Boethiah's Pillow Book.","fbmwTGAdvancement_1jobs_00322e67_1"
"","","Jobs",Neutral,50,"There's a customer who wants a Redoran Master Helm.","There's a customer who wants a Redoran Master Helm.","fbmwTGAdvancement_1jobs_00034149_1"
"","","Jobs",Neutral,50,"I got a job for you. Something that might add some clink to your pockets. I've heard the Ald'ruhn Guild of Mages has been left unguarded.","I got a job for you. Something that might add some clink to your pockets. I've heard the Ald'ruhn Guild of Mages has been left unguarded.","fbmwTGAdvancement_1jobs_00034148_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I want you to get Anareren's Devil Tanto.","I want you to get Anareren's Devil Tanto.","fbmwTGAdvancement_1jobs_00034148_2"
"","","Yes.",Neutral,50,"Yes, this is just what I wanted. You can keep anything else you found.","Yes, this is just what I wanted. You can keep anything else you found.","fbmwTGLootAldruhnMG_1AnarerenAsSDevilSTanto1_00322f6c_1"
"","","No.",Neutral,50,"Well what's keeping you? You're not going to let some apprentice get in the way, are you?","Well what's keeping you? You're not going to let some apprentice get in the way, are you?","fbmwTGLootAldruhnMG_1AnarerenAsSDevilSTanto2_00322f6d_1"
"","","Yes, there was a guard",Neutral,50,"Damn. Seems like the Mages Guild always knows when we're planning something. Did you get the Devil Tanto?","Damn. Seems like the Mages Guild always knows when we're planning something. Did you get the Devil Tanto?","fbmwTGLootAldruhnMG_1AnarerenAsSDevilSTanto3_00322f6e_1"
"","","No",Neutral,50,"Good. I guess the Mages Guild didn't know about our plans this time. So did you get the Devil Tanto?","Good. I guess the Mages Guild didn't know about our plans this time. So did you get the Devil Tanto?","fbmwTGLootAldruhnMG_1AnarerenAsSDevilSTanto4_00322f6f_1"
"","","Give him the book.",Neutral,50,"Hm. Interesting books these Dunmer have. We're getting paid well for this job.","Hm. Interesting books these Dunmer have. We're getting paid well for this job.","fbmwTGBadGandosa_1BoethiahAsSPillowSBook1_00322f70_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I looked over the emergency supplies here and found a ring and amulet you might like. Just don't tell anyone I gave them to you, eh?","I looked over the emergency supplies here and found a ring and amulet you might like. Just don't tell anyone I gave them to you, eh?","fbmwTGBadGandosa_1BoethiahAsSPillowSBook1_00322f70_2"
"","","Keep the book.",Neutral,50,"I need that book. I can't keep my client waiting forever. I might have to hire someone else to get that book, if you know what I mean.","I need that book. I can't keep my client waiting forever. I might have to hire someone else to get that book, if you know what I mean.","fbmwTGBadGandosa_1BoethiahAsSPillowSBook2_00322f71_1"
"","","Keep the book.",Neutral,50,"I need that book. I can't keep my client waiting forever. I might have to hire someone else to get that book, if you know what I mean.","I need that book. I can't keep my client waiting forever. I might have to hire someone else to get that book, if you know what I mean.","fbmwTGBadGandosa_1BoethiahAsSPillowSBook2_00322f72_1"
"","","I found it in Arobar Manor",Neutral,50,"Well, I have a client that wanted some dirt on the Arobar family. Would you be willing to part with that book?","Well, I have a client that wanted some dirt on the Arobar family. Would you be willing to part with that book?","fbmwTGBadGandosa_1BoethiahAsSPillowSBook3_00322f73_1"
"","","I found it somewhere else",Neutral,50,"Oh. Well, a client of ours wants some dirt on Gandosa Arobar.","Oh. Well, a client of ours wants some dirt on Gandosa Arobar.","fbmwTGBadGandosa_1BoethiahAsSPillowSBook4_00322f74_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If you find her copy of Boethiah's Pillow Book, give it to me and I'll give you a little something for your trouble.","If you find her copy of Boethiah's Pillow Book, give it to me and I'll give you a little something for your trouble.","fbmwTGBadGandosa_1BoethiahAsSPillowSBook4_00322f74_2"
"","","Here, take the helm.",Neutral,50,"Good work. I hope our client appreciates this. Here. Take a little gold for your trouble.","Good work. I hope our client appreciates this. Here. Take a little gold for your trouble.","fbmwTGMasterHelm_1RedoranSMasterSHelm1_00323052_1"
"","","Not yet.",Neutral,50,"Well get us a Redoran Master Helm. I can't keep our clients waiting forever.","Well get us a Redoran Master Helm. I can't keep our clients waiting forever.","fbmwTGMasterHelm_1RedoranSMasterSHelm2_00323053_1"
"","","Give him the daggers",Neutral,50,"Here's 2000 septims for the Darts. You've done pretty good work for me. If you've got a price on your head, I'll see if I can't take care of it.","Here's 2000 septims for the Darts. You've done pretty good work for me. If you've got a price on your head, I'll see if I can't take care of it.","fbmwTGDartsJudgement_1DartsSofSJudgement1_00034fee_1"
"","","Give him the daggers",Neutral,50,"Here's 1500 septims for the Darts. You've done pretty good work for me, outlander.","Here's 1500 septims for the Darts. You've done pretty good work for me, outlander.","fbmwTGDartsJudgement_1DartsSofSJudgement1_00323088_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If you've got a price on your head, I'll see if I can't take care of it.","If you've got a price on your head, I'll see if I can't take care of it.","fbmwTGDartsJudgement_1DartsSofSJudgement1_00323088_2"
"","","Give him the daggers",Neutral,50,"Here's 1000 septims for the Darts. You've done pretty good work for me, outlander.","Here's 1000 septims for the Darts. You've done pretty good work for me, outlander.","fbmwTGDartsJudgement_1DartsSofSJudgement1_00323089_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If you've got a price on your head, I'll see if I can't take care of it.","If you've got a price on your head, I'll see if I can't take care of it.","fbmwTGDartsJudgement_1DartsSofSJudgement1_00323089_2"
"","","Give him the daggers",Neutral,50,"Here's 500 septims for the Dart. You've done pretty good work for me, outlander.","Here's 500 septims for the Dart. You've done pretty good work for me, outlander.","fbmwTGDartsJudgement_1DartsSofSJudgement1_0032308a_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If you've got a price on your head, I'll see if I can't take care of it.","If you've got a price on your head, I'll see if I can't take care of it.","fbmwTGDartsJudgement_1DartsSofSJudgement1_0032308a_2"
"","","Keep the daggers",Neutral,50,"You put them to good use, then. You've done pretty good work for me, outlander. If you've got a price on your head, I'll see if I can't take care of it.","You put them to good use, then. You've done pretty good work for me, outlander. If you've got a price on your head, I'll see if I can't take care of it.","fbmwTGDartsJudgement_1DartsSofSJudgement2_0032308b_1"
"","","Yes, here it is.",Neutral,50,"So you found some, eh? Well, I'll give you a fair price for it. How about 250 septims each? That should put some clink in your pockets.","So you found some, eh? Well, I'll give you a fair price for it. How about 250 septims each? That should put some clink in your pockets.","fbmwTGAldruhnDefenses_1scrapSmetal1_00323488_1"
"","","No, not yet.",Neutral,50,"Well, keep looking. We used to have some Spider Centurion guards, and I sure felt safer with them around.","Well, keep looking. We used to have some Spider Centurion guards, and I sure felt safer with them around.","fbmwTGAldruhnDefenses_1scrapSmetal2_0032348b_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"This is the right book. I'll give you a fair price for it. How does 1000 septims sound?","This is the right book. I'll give you a fair price for it. How does 1000 septims sound?","fbmwTGWithershins_1Withershins1_003234af_1"
"","","No, not yet",Neutral,50,"Well, keep looking. Like I said, I think Miles Gloriosus over in Maar Gan has a copy. I don't know where he keeps it, though.","Well, keep looking. Like I said, I think Miles Gloriosus over in Maar Gan has a copy. I don't know where he keeps it, though.","fbmwTGWithershins_1Withershins2_003234a0_1"
