Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Excuse me. Can you help me? I've been robbed by some notorious thieves!","Excuse me. Can you help me? I've been robbed by some notorious thieves!","fbmwMSGreetings_GREETING_00f8873c_1"
"","","Some notorious thieves",Neutral,50,"They've still got my jewels. Perhaps I'll get them back one day.","They've still got my jewels. Perhaps I'll get them back one day.","fbmwMVBanditVictim_1someSnotoriousSthieves_00f8aa2f_1"
"","","Some notorious thieves",Neutral,50,"Yes, just a few hours ago I was robbed. I'm certain it was the group led by the Khajiit, Dro'zhirr. They stole all of my jewelry, but most importantly, they got two family heirlooms of mine.","Yes, just a few hours ago I was robbed. I'm certain it was the group led by the Khajiit, Dro'zhirr. They stole all of my jewelry, but most importantly, they got two family heirlooms of mine.","fbmwMVBanditVictim_1someSnotoriousSthieves_00f8aa30_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"They've been in my family for years. If you can return them to me, I'd gladly pay your their weight in gold.","They've been in my family for years. If you can return them to me, I'd gladly pay your their weight in gold.","fbmwMVBanditVictim_1someSnotoriousSthieves_00f8aa30_2"
"","","Family Heirlooms",Neutral,50,"You've found them! I'm so relieved. Here, please take this gold as payment. I was able to keep it hidden when the outlaws robbed me, and I'd be glad for you to have it. Thank you again!","You've found them! I'm so relieved. Here, please take this gold as payment. I was able to keep it hidden when the outlaws robbed me, and I'd be glad for you to have it. Thank you again!","fbmwMVBanditVictim_1familySheirlooms_00f8aa8a_1"
"","","Family Heirlooms",Neutral,50,"You've found them! I'm so relieved. Here, please take this gold as payment. I was able to keep it hidden when the outlaws robbed me, and I'd be glad for you to have it. Thank you again!","You've found them! I'm so relieved. Here, please take this gold as payment. I was able to keep it hidden when the outlaws robbed me, and I'd be glad for you to have it. Thank you again!","fbmwMVBanditVictim_1familySheirlooms_00f8aa8b_1"
"","","Family Heirlooms",Neutral,50,"You've found them! I'm so relieved. Here, please take this gold as payment. I was able to keep it hidden when the outlaws robbed me, and I'd be glad for you to have it. Thank you again!","You've found them! I'm so relieved. Here, please take this gold as payment. I was able to keep it hidden when the outlaws robbed me, and I'd be glad for you to have it. Thank you again!","fbmwMVBanditVictim_1familySheirlooms_00f8aa8c_1"
"","","Family Heirlooms",Neutral,50,"If you can retrieve them for me, I'd be eternally grateful.","If you can retrieve them for me, I'd be eternally grateful.","fbmwMVBanditVictim_1familySheirlooms_00f8aa8d_1"
"","","Family Heirlooms",Neutral,50,"Yes, it was a ring and an amulet. They're both inscribed, so it shouldn't be tough to tell which ones are mine.","Yes, it was a ring and an amulet. They're both inscribed, so it shouldn't be tough to tell which ones are mine.","fbmwMVBanditVictim_1familySheirlooms_00f8aa8e_1"
"","","Family Heirlooms",Neutral,50,"It's good to have my jewelry back.","It's good to have my jewelry back.","fbmwMVBanditVictim_1familySheirlooms_00f8aa8f_1"
"","","Dro'Zhirr",Neutral,50,"Yes, that scoundrel. He's got my family heirlooms, and I want them back.","Yes, that scoundrel. He's got my family heirlooms, and I want them back.","fbmwMVBanditVictim_1DroAZhirr_00f8ab34_1"
"","","I'll get your jewels back.",Neutral,50,"You will? Excellent. I believe their hideout is somewhere east of Caldera, although none of the local authorities has been able to find them.","You will? Excellent. I believe their hideout is somewhere east of Caldera, although none of the local authorities has been able to find them.","fbmwMVBanditVictim_1someSnotoriousSthieves1_00322f6a_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"No great surprise there.","No great surprise there.","fbmwMVBanditVictim_1someSnotoriousSthieves1_00322f6a_2"
"","","I don't have the time.",Neutral,50,"Well! I'm sorry you're too busy to help out someone in need. Goodbye to you, then!","Well! I'm sorry you're too busy to help out someone in need. Goodbye to you, then!","fbmwMVBanditVictim_1someSnotoriousSthieves2_00322f6b_1"
