Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Heavy Armor Styles",Neutral,50,"In the West, cheap iron, steel, and silver heavy armor is made in quantity for the Legions, and many are trained in its use.","In the West, cheap iron, steel, and silver heavy armor is made in quantity for the Legions, and many are trained in its use.","MorroDefaultQuest_1heavySarmorSstyles_003209f3_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"In the East, the expense of the superb ebony and daedric heavy armors limits their use to aristocratic families.","In the East, the expense of the superb ebony and daedric heavy armors limits their use to aristocratic families.","MorroDefaultQuest_1heavySarmorSstyles_003209f3_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Suits of ebony and daedric armor are passed down from generation to generation, and represent a sizable portion of a Great House nobles' personal wealth.","Suits of ebony and daedric armor are passed down from generation to generation, and represent a sizable portion of a Great House nobles' personal wealth.","MorroDefaultQuest_1heavySarmorSstyles_003209f3_3"
"","","Little Advice",Neutral,50,"Albecius Colollius is a veteran battlemage. He hangs out at Arrille's Tradehouse in Seyda Neen.","Albecius Colollius is a veteran battlemage. He hangs out at Arrille's Tradehouse in Seyda Neen.","MorroDefaultQuest_1littleSadvice_00321939_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Talk to him if you want to know about battlemages and how they work here in Morrowind.","Talk to him if you want to know about battlemages and how they work here in Morrowind.","MorroDefaultQuest_1littleSadvice_00321939_2"
"","","Little Advice",Neutral,50,"Albecius Colollius is a veteran battlemage. He hangs out at Arrille's Tradehouse in Seyda Neen.","Albecius Colollius is a veteran battlemage. He hangs out at Arrille's Tradehouse in Seyda Neen.","MorroDefaultQuest_1littleSadvice_0032193a_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Talk to him if you want to know about battlemages and how they work here in Morrowind.","Talk to him if you want to know about battlemages and how they work here in Morrowind.","MorroDefaultQuest_1littleSadvice_0032193a_2"
"","","Latest Rumors",Neutral,50,"Did you hear that some fool lost Mentor's Ring. In a tomb along the Bitter Coast, or so they say.","Did you hear that some fool lost Mentor's Ring. In a tomb along the Bitter Coast, or so they say.","MorroDefaultQuest_1latestSrumors_0032162f_1"
"","","Armor Styles",Neutral,50,"The heavy armor styles, called 'Legion' or 'knight' style in the West and 'ebony' style in the East, require great strength and endurance.","The heavy armor styles, called 'Legion' or 'knight' style in the West and 'ebony' style in the East, require great strength and endurance.","MorroDefaultQuest_1armorSstyles_00321c18_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The light armor styles, called 'militia' in the West and 'Ashlander' in the East, favor speed and agility.","The light armor styles, called 'militia' in the West and 'Ashlander' in the East, favor speed and agility.","MorroDefaultQuest_1armorSstyles_00321c18_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The medium armor styles, called 'Imperial guard' in the West and 'Great House' in the East, are compromises between the heavy and light styles, balancing protection against mobility.","The medium armor styles, called 'Imperial guard' in the West and 'Great House' in the East, are compromises between the heavy and light styles, balancing protection against mobility.","MorroDefaultQuest_1armorSstyles_00321c18_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"A few less common exotic armor types are also found in Morrowind.","A few less common exotic armor types are also found in Morrowind.","MorroDefaultQuest_1armorSstyles_00321c18_4"
"","","Worn Weapons",Neutral,50,"Weapons become less effective with wear.","Weapons become less effective with wear.","MorroDefaultQuest_1wornSweapons_00321c33_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Eventually they break, and are useless until you repair them, but a worn weapon does only a fraction of the damage it should do.","Eventually they break, and are useless until you repair them, but a worn weapon does only a fraction of the damage it should do.","MorroDefaultQuest_1wornSweapons_00321c33_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You'll hack and stab and slash away, and suddenly realize you're doing almost nothing to your enemy.","You'll hack and stab and slash away, and suddenly realize you're doing almost nothing to your enemy.","MorroDefaultQuest_1wornSweapons_00321c33_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"So learn the basics of weapon repair, and touch up your weapons before every big fight, or pay a smith to keep your weapons in top shape.","So learn the basics of weapon repair, and touch up your weapons before every big fight, or pay a smith to keep your weapons in top shape.","MorroDefaultQuest_1wornSweapons_00321c33_4"
"","","Worn Armor",Neutral,50,"As it wears out, armor becomes less effective.","As it wears out, armor becomes less effective.","MorroDefaultQuest_1wornSarmor_003223cf_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Broken armor is completely useless until you repair it, but worn armor stops only a fraction of the damage that new or well-maintained armor does.","Broken armor is completely useless until you repair it, but worn armor stops only a fraction of the damage that new or well-maintained armor does.","MorroDefaultQuest_1wornSarmor_003223cf_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Learn the basics of armor repair, and go over your armor, piece by piece, before every big battle.","Learn the basics of armor repair, and go over your armor, piece by piece, before every big battle.","MorroDefaultQuest_1wornSarmor_003223cf_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Or visit a smith regularly to keep your armor in good shape.","Or visit a smith regularly to keep your armor in good shape.","MorroDefaultQuest_1wornSarmor_003223cf_4"
