Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"Almalexia","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"It is time for you to go, outlander. Sotha Sil must be stopped.","It is time for you to go, outlander. Sotha Sil must be stopped.","fbmwTRSothaSil_GREETING_0000b728_1"
"Almalexia","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Greetings, my dearest servant. You were to forge the blade of Nerevar once again.","Greetings, my dearest servant. You were to forge the blade of Nerevar once again.","fbmwTRBlade_GREETING_0000b727_1"
"Almalexia","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Welcome, outlander. It is time we talked of greater things. ","Welcome, outlander. It is time we talked of greater things.","fbmwTRMissingHand02_GREETING_00f8e593_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"I have watched you since your arrival in Vvardenfell, and you have been a strong and faithful servant to me.","I have watched you since your arrival in Vvardenfell, and you have been a strong and faithful servant to me.","fbmwTRMissingHand02_GREETING_00f8e593_2"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"None but the Nerevarine could have succeeded as you have. How long I have waited for this! My Nerevar, returned to me at last!","None but the Nerevarine could have succeeded as you have. How long I have waited for this! My Nerevar, returned to me at last!","fbmwTRMissingHand02_GREETING_00f8e593_3"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"I have watched from my Temple as others have made the claim, and I have seen them fall. I believe now that you are the one who was prophesied.","I have watched from my Temple as others have made the claim, and I have seen them fall. I believe now that you are the one who was prophesied.","fbmwTRMissingHand02_GREETING_00f8e593_4"
"Almalexia","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Have you eliminated the threat of my poor, mad Missing Hand, and brought peace to Mournhold?","Have you eliminated the threat of my poor, mad Missing Hand, and brought peace to Mournhold?","fbmwTRMissingHand02_GREETING_0000b726_1"
"Almalexia","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I sense that the danger in the Plaza has abated...for now. Go and speak with Fedris Hler. He will give you further instructions.","I sense that the danger in the Plaza has abated...for now. Go and speak with Fedris Hler. He will give you further instructions.","fbmwTRMHAttack_GREETING_00f8b912_1"
"Almalexia","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"There is a disturbance in the Plaza Brindisi Dorom. Investigate it, my good and faithful servant. I shall remain here.","There is a disturbance in the Plaza Brindisi Dorom. Investigate it, my good and faithful servant. I shall remain here.","fbmwTRMHAttack_GREETING_00f8b913_1"
"Almalexia","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I am well-pleased, good and faithful servant. My people look upon the elements, and see there written a divine testament to my lordship. Did ever any other god display such dominion over the earth and sky? But now...","I am well-pleased, good and faithful servant. My people look upon the elements, and see there written a divine testament to my lordship. Did ever any other god display such dominion over the earth and sky? But now...","fbmwTRShowPower_GREETING_00f8b9dd_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"With a heavy heart, I must lay a sad burden upon you. I bid you bring the peace of understanding to my Missing Hand.","With a heavy heart, I must lay a sad burden upon you. I bid you bring the peace of understanding to my Missing Hand.","fbmwTRShowPower_GREETING_00f8b9dd_2"
"Almalexia","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"In My wisdom I have sent you to activate the Karstangz-Bcharn. Tell me you have accomplished this task for your goddess.","In My wisdom I have sent you to activate the Karstangz-Bcharn. Tell me you have accomplished this task for your goddess.","fbmwTRShowPower_GREETING_00f8b9de_1"
"Almalexia","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"What have you learned about this End of Times cult and their beliefs? Have you served me well in gathering this information?","What have you learned about this End of Times cult and their beliefs? Have you served me well in gathering this information?","fbmwTRShowPower_GREETING_00f8b9df_1"
"Almalexia","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Greetings. It is good to see you again. Dear Fedris has told me more about your work so far here in Mournhold. He suggested I might find your services useful. After some consideration, I have decided that there may be a task for you to complete.","Greetings. It is good to see you again. Dear Fedris has told me more about your work so far here in Mournhold. He suggested I might find your services useful. After some consideration, I have decided that there may be a task for you to complete.","fbmwTRShowPower_GREETING_00f8b9e0_1"
"Almalexia","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"There is much work to be done. Leave me now, my loyal servant. We will speak again soon, I am sure.","There is much work to be done. Leave me now, my loyal servant. We will speak again soon, I am sure.","fbmwTRMazedBand_GREETING_00f8b922_1"
"Almalexia","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"So you are the person I have been hearing about. I welcome you to my chapel...or perhaps I should call you by another name? But, that is a discussion for a later time. ","So you are the person I have been hearing about. I welcome you to my chapel...or perhaps I should call you by another name? But, that is a discussion for a later time.","fbmwTRMazedBand_GREETING_00f8b923_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"I understand you have done well in my service, and, indeed, a service in my name is a service for all of Mournhold. Now, my faithful and obedient servant, let us discuss Barilzar's Mazed Band.","I understand you have done well in my service, and, indeed, a service in my name is a service for all of Mournhold. Now, my faithful and obedient servant, let us discuss Barilzar's Mazed Band.","fbmwTRMazedBand_GREETING_00f8b923_2"
"Almalexia","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I have not invited you. Please leave.","I have not invited you. Please leave.","fbmwMSGreetings_GREETING_00f8b9a5_1"
"Almalexia","","Warm, reflected glory, please!",Neutral,50,"I bless you with my gift, and mark you as my own. Be ever faithful in your service, and you may expect more generous rewards.","I bless you with my gift, and mark you as my own. Be ever faithful in your service, and you may expect more generous rewards.","fbmwTRMissingHand02_1MissingSHand2_0000e867_1"
"Almalexia","","Uh... nothing for me, right now...",Disgust,100,"[Almalexia regards you coolly.] Perhaps you think yourself too proud to accept the gifts of your Mistress? Very well. It is as you wish.","[Almalexia regards you coolly.] Perhaps you think yourself too proud to accept the gifts of your Mistress? Very well. It is as you wish.","fbmwTRMissingHand02_1MissingSHand1_0000e85c_1"
"Almalexia","","Protection against paralysis, please!",Neutral,50,"I bless you with my gift, and mark you as my own. Be ever faithful in your service, and you may expect more generous rewards.","I bless you with my gift, and mark you as my own. Be ever faithful in your service, and you may expect more generous rewards.","fbmwTRMissingHand02_1MissingSHand3_0000e868_1"
"Almalexia","","Skin like iron, please!",Neutral,50,"I bless you with my gift, and mark you as my own. Be ever faithful in your service, and you may expect more generous rewards.","I bless you with my gift, and mark you as my own. Be ever faithful in your service, and you may expect more generous rewards.","fbmwTRMissingHand02_1MissingSHand4_0000e869_1"
"Almalexia","","Tamed lightning, please!",Neutral,50,"I bless you with my gift, and mark you as my own. Be ever faithful in your service, and you may expect more generous rewards.","I bless you with my gift, and mark you as my own. Be ever faithful in your service, and you may expect more generous rewards.","fbmwTRMissingHand02_1MissingSHand5_0000e86a_1"
"Almalexia","","Continue",Neutral,50,"Salas Valor is already dead? The pain is almost more than I can bear... but somehow, you have anticipated my need and served me faithfully!","Salas Valor is already dead? The pain is almost more than I can bear... but somehow, you have anticipated my need and served me faithfully!","fbmwTRMissingHand02_1MissingSHand6_0000e862_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50," It is a sign! This miracle compels me to grant you a divine blessing. Would you like skin as tough as iron?","It is a sign! This miracle compels me to grant you a divine blessing. Would you like skin as tough as iron?","fbmwTRMissingHand02_1MissingSHand6_0000e862_2"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"Would you like the terrible force of lightning tamed as your protector? Or would you wish to always bask in warm comfort of my reflected glory?","Would you like the terrible force of lightning tamed as your protector? Or would you wish to always bask in warm comfort of my reflected glory?","fbmwTRMissingHand02_1MissingSHand6_0000e862_3"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"Quick, now! Choose! You must not keep your Deity waiting!","Quick, now! Choose! You must not keep your Deity waiting!","fbmwTRMissingHand02_1MissingSHand6_0000e862_4"
"Almalexia","","Continue",Neutral,50,"Now Salas Valor haunts the streets and sewers of Mournhold.","Now Salas Valor haunts the streets and sewers of Mournhold.","fbmwTRMissingHand02_1MissingSHand6_0000e863_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"His wild, distracted manner frightens the people, but even my Ordinators are afraid to confront so terrible a weaponmaster and war-wizard","His wild, distracted manner frightens the people, but even my Ordinators are afraid to confront so terrible a weaponmaster and war-wizard","fbmwTRMissingHand02_1MissingSHand6_0000e863_2"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"I beg you -- seek out Salas Valor. Relieve us of this threat to my beloved people, and bring peace to my sacred city of Mournhold.","I beg you -- seek out Salas Valor. Relieve us of this threat to my beloved people, and bring peace to my sacred city of Mournhold.","fbmwTRMissingHand02_1MissingSHand6_0000e863_3"
"Almalexia","","I need time to prepare.",Neutral,50,"There is not time to waste. Make your preparations quickly.","There is not time to waste. Make your preparations quickly.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1mustSbeSStopped2_00014c5e_1"
"Almalexia","","I am prepared to go.",Neutral,50,"Then I shall send you now. Do what you must, Nerevarine.","Then I shall send you now. Do what you must, Nerevarine.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1mustSbeSstopped1_00014c60_1"
"Almalexia","","fbmwAlmGreet",Neutral,50,"Many Blessings upon you, my loyal servant.","Many Blessings upon you, my loyal servant.","fbmwTRMazedBand_fbmwAlmGreet_0001fdf2_1"
"Almalexia","","fbmwAlmGreet",Neutral,50,"Come. Bathe in the light of My Mercy.","Come. Bathe in the light of My Mercy.","fbmwTRMazedBand_fbmwAlmGreet_0001fdf3_1"
"Almalexia","","fbmwAlmGreet",Neutral,50,"What may I do for you, my child?","What may I do for you, my child?","fbmwTRMazedBand_fbmwAlmGreet_0001fdf4_1"
"Almalexia","","Sotha Sil",Neutral,50,"I worry greatly about Sotha Sil. I fear he has gone mad.","I worry greatly about Sotha Sil. I fear he has gone mad.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1SothaSSil_00f8e597_1"
"Almalexia","","Ashstorms in Mournhold",Neutral,50,"Yes, the Karstangz-Bcharn is creating the weather just as I had hoped. And it will remain this way until I am satisfied these people have learned a lesson.","Yes, the Karstangz-Bcharn is creating the weather just as I had hoped. And it will remain this way until I am satisfied these people have learned a lesson.","fbmwTRShowPower_1AshstormsSinSMournhold_00f8ab4f_1"
"Almalexia","","Ashstorms in Mournhold",Neutral,50,"I see you have activated the Karstangz-Bcharn.","I see you have activated the Karstangz-Bcharn.","fbmwTRShowPower_1AshstormsSinSMournhold_00f8ba15_1"
"Almalexia","","Ashstorms in Mournhold",Neutral,50,"You have not yet created ashstorms, and my patience wears thin. This needs to be handled, and quickly.","You have not yet created ashstorms, and my patience wears thin. This needs to be handled, and quickly.","fbmwTRShowPower_1AshstormsSinSMournhold_00f8ba16_1"
"Almalexia","","Ashstorms in Mournhold",Neutral,50,"That's correct. While these storms may be common on the island of Vvardenfell, they do not occur here, so far removed from the Red Mountain. Now, though, they will, and these heretics will understand the power of the Tribunal. The power of Almalexia!","That's correct. While these storms may be common on the island of Vvardenfell, they do not occur here, so far removed from the Red Mountain. Now, though, they will, and these heretics will understand the power of the Tribunal. The power of Almalexia!","fbmwTRShowPower_1AshstormsSinSMournhold_00f8ba17_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"Take this, and use it to activate the machine. You will have to divine its workings on your own, but I believe you are up to the task.","Take this, and use it to activate the machine. You will have to divine its workings on your own, but I believe you are up to the task.","fbmwTRShowPower_1AshstormsSinSMournhold_00f8ba17_2"
"Almalexia","","Barilzar's Mazed Band",Neutral,50,"It is good and right that the Band be in my possession. Surely, it will be a boon to all of my people. Your efforts are appreciated.","It is good and right that the Band be in my possession. Surely, it will be a boon to all of my people. Your efforts are appreciated.","fbmwTRMazedBand_1BarilzarAsSMazedSBand_00f8ba23_1"
"Almalexia","","Barilzar's Mazed Band",Neutral,50,"An interesting item, is it not? It seems ordinary enough, but it is much more. The ring is cold now, but the embers of its power still burn hot within. I will use my magic to reawaken this power.","An interesting item, is it not? It seems ordinary enough, but it is much more. The ring is cold now, but the embers of its power still burn hot within. I will use my magic to reawaken this power.","fbmwTRMazedBand_1BarilzarAsSMazedSBand_00f8ba24_1"
"Almalexia","","Barilzar's Mazed Band",Neutral,50,"I was told you had the Mazed Band. Where is it? Retrieve it. Quickly.","I was told you had the Mazed Band. Where is it? Retrieve it. Quickly.","fbmwTRMazedBand_1BarilzarAsSMazedSBand_00f8ba25_1"
"Almalexia","","Reclaim Your Station",Neutral,50,"For years, the Chimer and the Dwemer had been at war.","For years, the Chimer and the Dwemer had been at war.","fbmwTRBlade_1reclaimSyourSstation_00001be8_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"The Dwemer spurned the Daedra that the Chimer worshipped, instead placing their faith in their metal creations.","The Dwemer spurned the Daedra that the Chimer worshipped, instead placing their faith in their metal creations.","fbmwTRBlade_1reclaimSyourSstation_00001be8_2"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"It was only when the Nords invaded Resdayn that the two nations were able to join as one under the leadership of our Nerevar and the Dwarf-King Dumac","It was only when the Nords invaded Resdayn that the two nations were able to join as one under the leadership of our Nerevar and the Dwarf-King Dumac","fbmwTRBlade_1reclaimSyourSstation_00001be8_3"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"In time, the two generals became blood friends, and on the day that Nerevar and I were wed, Dumac presented us with twin blades.","In time, the two generals became blood friends, and on the day that Nerevar and I were wed, Dumac presented us with twin blades.","fbmwTRBlade_1reclaimSyourSstation_00001be8_4"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"Hopesfire and Trueflame.","Hopesfire and Trueflame.","fbmwTRBlade_1reclaimSyourSstation_00001be8_5"
"Almalexia","","Pieces of the Blade",Neutral,50,"As I said, they are nearby. Look to those in the city that you know and trust for guidance. Find those who would have use for items such as this.","As I said, they are nearby. Look to those in the city that you know and trust for guidance. Find those who would have use for items such as this.","fbmwTRBlade_1piecesSofStheSblade_00011a64_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"Prove your mettle to me, Nerevarine, and soon we will stand together once again!","Prove your mettle to me, Nerevarine, and soon we will stand together once again!","fbmwTRBlade_1piecesSofStheSblade_00011a64_2"
"Almalexia","","Hands of Almalexia",Neutral,50,"The Hands of Almalexia are My personal guard, pledged to honor and protect and serve Me in all ways.","The Hands of Almalexia are My personal guard, pledged to honor and protect and serve Me in all ways.","MorroDefaultQuest_1HandsSofSAlmalexia_00011a5b_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"Their bodies and souls are buttressed by My Divine Favor. Their armor and weapons are imbued with glory by My Touch.","Their bodies and souls are buttressed by My Divine Favor. Their armor and weapons are imbued with glory by My Touch.","MorroDefaultQuest_1HandsSofSAlmalexia_00011a5b_2"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"On the face of Tamriel, there are no more terrible warriors than My Hands of Almalexia.","On the face of Tamriel, there are no more terrible warriors than My Hands of Almalexia.","MorroDefaultQuest_1HandsSofSAlmalexia_00011a5b_3"
"Almalexia","","Karstangz-Bcharn",Neutral,50,"It will remain active until I decide otherwise.","It will remain active until I decide otherwise.","fbmwTRShowPower_1KarstangzTBcharn_00001c47_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"The ashstorms will continue in Mournhold until I feel that these people have grown to appreciate all I do for them.","The ashstorms will continue in Mournhold until I feel that these people have grown to appreciate all I do for them.","fbmwTRShowPower_1KarstangzTBcharn_00001c47_2"
"Almalexia","","Karstangz-Bcharn",Neutral,50,"Well done, outlander. This is the effect I was looking for! Ashstorms in Mournhold!","Well done, outlander. This is the effect I was looking for! Ashstorms in Mournhold!","fbmwTRShowPower_1KarstangzTBcharn_00f8e59c_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"My magic will prevent anyone from further tampering with this machine. You will, of course, keep silent about this.","My magic will prevent anyone from further tampering with this machine. You will, of course, keep silent about this.","fbmwTRShowPower_1KarstangzTBcharn_00f8e59c_2"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"My powers are a bit drained, mortal...they are not gone. My ordinators will take care of the remains of this End of Times cult and their leader.","My powers are a bit drained, mortal...they are not gone. My ordinators will take care of the remains of this End of Times cult and their leader.","fbmwTRShowPower_1KarstangzTBcharn_00f8e59c_3"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"You have done well.","You have done well.","fbmwTRShowPower_1KarstangzTBcharn_00f8e59c_4"
"Almalexia","","Karstangz-Bcharn",Neutral,50,"I see you have restarted the machine, but this is not what I asked for! This weather is not uncommon in the city.","I see you have restarted the machine, but this is not what I asked for! This weather is not uncommon in the city.","fbmwTRShowPower_1KarstangzTBcharn_00f8e59d_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"Only an ashstorm will show these people my true power!","Only an ashstorm will show these people my true power!","fbmwTRShowPower_1KarstangzTBcharn_00f8e59d_2"
"Almalexia","","Karstangz-Bcharn",Neutral,50,"Go. Take the Dwemer Coherer and restart the machine. I will have ashstorms in Mournhold!","Go. Take the Dwemer Coherer and restart the machine. I will have ashstorms in Mournhold!","fbmwTRShowPower_1KarstangzTBcharn_00f8e59e_1"
"Almalexia","","Karstangz-Bcharn",Neutral,50,"Loosely translated: the Weather Witch. At its height, the Dwemer civilization was masterful in the use of machinery.","Loosely translated: the Weather Witch. At its height, the Dwemer civilization was masterful in the use of machinery.","fbmwTRShowPower_1KarstangzTBcharn_00f8e59f_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"In a time of drought, Dwemer scholars were commissioned to create a machine that would bring rain to their lands. They created the Karstangz-Bcharn.","In a time of drought, Dwemer scholars were commissioned to create a machine that would bring rain to their lands. They created the Karstangz-Bcharn.","fbmwTRShowPower_1KarstangzTBcharn_00f8e59f_2"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"Its existence was little more than a myth until recently, when the ruins opened beneath my city.","Its existence was little more than a myth until recently, when the ruins opened beneath my city.","fbmwTRShowPower_1KarstangzTBcharn_00f8e59f_3"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"I wish for you to activate the machine, make it to create ashstorms in Mournhold. Then, these heretics will know the power of Almalexia!","I wish for you to activate the machine, make it to create ashstorms in Mournhold. Then, these heretics will know the power of Almalexia!","fbmwTRShowPower_1KarstangzTBcharn_00f8e59f_4"
"Almalexia","","Lesson in Power",Neutral,50,"These fools must be reminded of the true power of a god. Since the attack on the city, much of my own power has been spent caring for my people.","These fools must be reminded of the true power of a god. Since the attack on the city, much of my own power has been spent caring for my people.","fbmwTRShowPower_1lessonSinSpower_00001c42_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"The number of wounded has been astronomical, and caring for them all has been taxing to even me.","The number of wounded has been astronomical, and caring for them all has been taxing to even me.","fbmwTRShowPower_1lessonSinSpower_00001c42_2"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"Still, I must demonstrate to these people what it is to mock the will of a god.","Still, I must demonstrate to these people what it is to mock the will of a god.","fbmwTRShowPower_1lessonSinSpower_00001c42_3"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"You will travel to the ruins of Bamz-Amschend and activate the Karstangz-Bcharn.","You will travel to the ruins of Bamz-Amschend and activate the Karstangz-Bcharn.","fbmwTRShowPower_1lessonSinSpower_00001c42_4"
"Almalexia","","You are the one",Neutral,50,"I believe you now to be the Nerevarine. Though I have watched others come and go, my belief is that you are the child of prophecy.","I believe you now to be the Nerevarine. Though I have watched others come and go, my belief is that you are the child of prophecy.","fbmwTRBlade_1youSareStheSone_00001b82_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"The time has come for you to reclaim your station. Together we can unite Morrowind once again, free from the Imperial yoke.","The time has come for you to reclaim your station. Together we can unite Morrowind once again, free from the Imperial yoke.","fbmwTRBlade_1youSareStheSone_00001b82_2"
"Almalexia","","Forge the Blade",Neutral,50,"The blade is reforged! Our time has almost arrived. There is but one obstacle that stands in our way, though it pains me to believe it is so.","The blade is reforged! Our time has almost arrived. There is but one obstacle that stands in our way, though it pains me to believe it is so.","fbmwTRBlade_1forgeStheSblade_00011a61_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"Sotha Sil. I cannot count the times I have fought by the Magician's side.","Sotha Sil. I cannot count the times I have fought by the Magician's side.","fbmwTRBlade_1forgeStheSblade_00011a61_2"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"It was he who stood with me the day I fought in Mournhold and banished Mehrunes Dagon to the depths of Oblivion.","It was he who stood with me the day I fought in Mournhold and banished Mehrunes Dagon to the depths of Oblivion.","fbmwTRBlade_1forgeStheSblade_00011a61_3"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"It was Sotha Sil who was able to delve the mysteries of Kagrenac's tools, and raise me to my rightful station.","It was Sotha Sil who was able to delve the mysteries of Kagrenac's tools, and raise me to my rightful station.","fbmwTRBlade_1forgeStheSblade_00011a61_4"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"Now, though, the Tinkerer has become unstable.","Now, though, the Tinkerer has become unstable.","fbmwTRBlade_1forgeStheSblade_00011a61_5"
"Almalexia","","Forge the Blade",Neutral,50,"The blade is whole, but the fire does not burn! Speak to the one who forged the blade, and find out why it does not burn!","The blade is whole, but the fire does not burn! Speak to the one who forged the blade, and find out why it does not burn!","fbmwTRBlade_1forgeStheSblade_00011a62_1"
"Almalexia","","Man he once was",Neutral,50,"He is completely mad. It was his creations, these Fabricants, that attacked my city.","He is completely mad. It was his creations, these Fabricants, that attacked my city.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1manSheSonceSwas_00001c37_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"This once great man is now a danger to Mournhold and to all of Morrowind. He must be stopped.","This once great man is now a danger to Mournhold and to all of Morrowind. He must be stopped.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1manSheSonceSwas_00001c37_2"
"Almalexia","","Must be stopped",Neutral,50,"Are you prepared now to stop Sotha Sil and take your place amongst the gods?","Are you prepared now to stop Sotha Sil and take your place amongst the gods?","fbmwTRSothaSil_1mustSbeSstopped_00001c20_1"
"Almalexia","","Must be stopped",Neutral,50,"I believe it is your calling to stop Sotha Sil's mad schemings. I do not know that he can be reasoned with, outlander, but it is possible.","I believe it is your calling to stop Sotha Sil's mad schemings. I do not know that he can be reasoned with, outlander, but it is possible.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1mustSbeSstopped_00014c59_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"If he cannot be, you must end his life. Though the idea saddens me, it is best for Morrowind...and it is best for him, as well.","If he cannot be, you must end his life. Though the idea saddens me, it is best for Morrowind...and it is best for him, as well.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1mustSbeSstopped_00014c59_2"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"You have the power to do this. The Trueflame can kill a god, if wielded by one of noble intent. Steel yourself, outlander, and do what must be done.","You have the power to do this. The Trueflame can kill a god, if wielded by one of noble intent. Steel yourself, outlander, and do what must be done.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1mustSbeSstopped_00014c59_3"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"I will send you to his Clockwork City now, if you are prepared. Good luck, Nerevarine.","I will send you to his Clockwork City now, if you are prepared. Good luck, Nerevarine.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1mustSbeSstopped_00014c59_4"
"Almalexia","","Clockwork City",Neutral,50,"His lair is as puzzling as the mind of the Sorcerer himself. Ever-moving, ever-changing, its levers and gears responding to its master's will alone.","His lair is as puzzling as the mind of the Sorcerer himself. Ever-moving, ever-changing, its levers and gears responding to its master's will alone.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1ClockworkSCity_00001ca1_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"It is here he performs his profane experiments, aided by his magic and tainted by his madness.","It is here he performs his profane experiments, aided by his magic and tainted by his madness.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1ClockworkSCity_00001ca1_2"
"Almalexia","","Missing Hand",Neutral,50,"You have done well in removing this threat to Our peace and security","You have done well in removing this threat to Our peace and security","fbmwTRMissingHand02_1missingSHand_00001c2b_1"
"Almalexia","","Missing Hand",Neutral,50,"Salas Valor is dead? The pain is almost more than I can bear...","Salas Valor is dead? The pain is almost more than I can bear...","fbmwTRMissingHand02_1missingSHand_0000e85d_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"But you have served me faithfully, and it is in my mind to grant you a divine blessing. Would you like skin as tough as iron?","But you have served me faithfully, and it is in my mind to grant you a divine blessing. Would you like skin as tough as iron?","fbmwTRMissingHand02_1missingSHand_0000e85d_2"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"Would you like my protection against paralyzing terror? Or would you wish to always bask in warm comfort of my reflected glory?","Would you like my protection against paralyzing terror? Or would you wish to always bask in warm comfort of my reflected glory?","fbmwTRMissingHand02_1missingSHand_0000e85d_3"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"Quick, now! Choose! You must not keep your Deity waiting!","Quick, now! Choose! You must not keep your Deity waiting!","fbmwTRMissingHand02_1missingSHand_0000e85d_4"
"Almalexia","","Missing Hand",Neutral,50,"When you have removed the threat Salas Valor represents to Our peace and security, report back to me.","When you have removed the threat Salas Valor represents to Our peace and security, report back to me.","fbmwTRMissingHand02_1missingSHand_0000e861_1"
"Almalexia","","Missing Hand",Neutral,50,"One of my most faithful guards, one of my very own Hands of Almalexia, pledged to honor and protect and serve me in all ways, has lost his mind.","One of my most faithful guards, one of my very own Hands of Almalexia, pledged to honor and protect and serve me in all ways, has lost his mind.","fbmwTRMissingHand02_1missingSHand_0000e864_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"Salas Valor has abandoned me, and now spews vile and slanderous untruths about me to any who would listen.","Salas Valor has abandoned me, and now spews vile and slanderous untruths about me to any who would listen.","fbmwTRMissingHand02_1missingSHand_0000e864_2"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"I pity him, and know he is not responsible for his actions. To view the splendor of a god may drive even the strongest mortal mad.","I pity him, and know he is not responsible for his actions. To view the splendor of a god may drive even the strongest mortal mad.","fbmwTRMissingHand02_1missingSHand_0000e864_3"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"But now he presents a threat to us, and he is very dangerous. I fear you may not be able to spare his life.","But now he presents a threat to us, and he is very dangerous. I fear you may not be able to spare his life.","fbmwTRMissingHand02_1missingSHand_0000e864_4"
"Almalexia","","End of Times",Neutral,50,"They will not continue to exist in my city.","They will not continue to exist in my city.","fbmwTRShowPower_1EndSofSTimes_00f8ba81_1"
"Almalexia","","End of Times",Neutral,50,"A suicide cult? In my city? What have you learned about their beliefs?","A suicide cult? In my city? What have you learned about their beliefs?","fbmwTRShowPower_1EndSofSTimes_00f8ba82_1"
"Almalexia","","End of Times",Neutral,50,"Have you found out more information yet?","Have you found out more information yet?","fbmwTRShowPower_1EndSofSTimes_00f8ba83_1"
"Almalexia","","End of Times",Neutral,50,"Very little is known about them yet, but there is one very disturbing fact we have learned: many of their members have been found dead.","Very little is known about them yet, but there is one very disturbing fact we have learned: many of their members have been found dead.","fbmwTRShowPower_1EndSofSTimes_00f8ba84_1"
"Almalexia","","Salas Valor",Neutral,50,"Salas Valor was once my most trusted Hand and faithful servant. But recently his behavior has been erratic.","Salas Valor was once my most trusted Hand and faithful servant. But recently his behavior has been erratic.","fbmwTRMissingHand02_1SalasSValor_00001bd4_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"He has been quiet and unresponsive. I am afraid... I may have allowed him to come too close.","He has been quiet and unresponsive. I am afraid... I may have allowed him to come too close.","fbmwTRMissingHand02_1SalasSValor_00001bd4_2"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"It is impossible that a mortal and a god might meet on equal ground, but... perhaps he had deluded himself.","It is impossible that a mortal and a god might meet on equal ground, but... perhaps he had deluded himself.","fbmwTRMissingHand02_1SalasSValor_00001bd4_3"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"I regret his lamentable state, and am sorry that I may have been partly responsible for his condition.","I regret his lamentable state, and am sorry that I may have been partly responsible for his condition.","fbmwTRMissingHand02_1SalasSValor_00001bd4_4"
"Almalexia","","Twin Blades",Neutral,50,"Yes. Hopesfire and Trueflame.","Yes. Hopesfire and Trueflame.","fbmwTRBlade_1twinSblades_00001b9b_1"
"Almalexia","","Twin Blades",Neutral,50,"Each was a magnificent blade, the pinnacle of Dwemer craftsmanship.","Each was a magnificent blade, the pinnacle of Dwemer craftsmanship.","fbmwTRBlade_1twinSblades_00014c5b_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"Their blades burned with an unearthly fire, and the sight of them struck fear into our enemies.","Their blades burned with an unearthly fire, and the sight of them struck fear into our enemies.","fbmwTRBlade_1twinSblades_00014c5b_2"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"My blade has been kept safe, but not so Trueflame, the Blade of Nerevar. It was lost at the battle of Red Mountain.","My blade has been kept safe, but not so Trueflame, the Blade of Nerevar. It was lost at the battle of Red Mountain.","fbmwTRBlade_1twinSblades_00014c5b_3"
"Almalexia","","His Madness",Neutral,50,"I have suspected for some time that the Lord Sotha Sil had entered Sheogorath's realm.","I have suspected for some time that the Lord Sotha Sil had entered Sheogorath's realm.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1hisSmadness_00001c55_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"His visits have been more and more infrequent, and punctuated by violent fits of anger.","His visits have been more and more infrequent, and punctuated by violent fits of anger.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1hisSmadness_00001c55_2"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"He began to speak of the fall of the Tribunal and the return of the Old Gods. But Sotha Sil is not a Seer; he is a Maker.","He began to speak of the fall of the Tribunal and the return of the Old Gods. But Sotha Sil is not a Seer; he is a Maker.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1hisSmadness_00001c55_3"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"He shapes the Here and the Now, while only I have been privy to what is to come. I know this...he is no longer the man he once was.","He shapes the Here and the Now, while only I have been privy to what is to come. I know this...he is no longer the man he once was.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1hisSmadness_00001c55_4"
"Almalexia","","Eno Romari",Neutral,50,"I did not want him killed! You displease me, mortal fool.","I did not want him killed! You displease me, mortal fool.","fbmwTRShowPower_1EnoSRomari_00f8e5a2_1"
"Almalexia","","Eno Romari",Neutral,50,"I will take care of him.","I will take care of him.","fbmwTRShowPower_1EnoSRomari_00f8e5a3_1"
"Almalexia","","Eno Romari",Neutral,50,"We know he is in the city, but little else about him.","We know he is in the city, but little else about him.","fbmwTRShowPower_1EnoSRomari_00f8e5a4_1"
"Almalexia","","Eno Romari",Neutral,50,"The leader of this little cult. He resides in Mournhold, though he is not known to have a permanent residence.","The leader of this little cult. He resides in Mournhold, though he is not known to have a permanent residence.","fbmwTRShowPower_1EnoSRomari_00f8e5a5_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"He is dangerous, as he spreads discontent among my people. He is not to be killed, though. I want no martyrs to this madman's cause.","He is dangerous, as he spreads discontent among my people. He is not to be killed, though. I want no martyrs to this madman's cause.","fbmwTRShowPower_1EnoSRomari_00f8e5a5_2"
"Almalexia","","Found dead",Neutral,50,"At least seven of them have been found so far. All dead, all in their homes.","At least seven of them have been found so far. All dead, all in their homes.","fbmwTRShowPower_1foundSdead_00f8e5a6_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"It appears they ingested a strong poison, and not even my magicks could revive those who were found.","It appears they ingested a strong poison, and not even my magicks could revive those who were found.","fbmwTRShowPower_1foundSdead_00f8e5a6_2"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"We must find out what drives this group, and rid my city of their presence. Speak with Meralyn Othan at the Great Bazaar.","We must find out what drives this group, and rid my city of their presence. Speak with Meralyn Othan at the Great Bazaar.","fbmwTRShowPower_1foundSdead_00f8e5a6_3"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"Her brother Sevil was one of those found. Learn what you can about them and of this Eno Romari.","Her brother Sevil was one of those found. Learn what you can about them and of this Eno Romari.","fbmwTRShowPower_1foundSdead_00f8e5a6_4"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"Take care with him, though. The words of a martyr cry louder than those of a zealot.","Take care with him, though. The words of a martyr cry louder than those of a zealot.","fbmwTRShowPower_1foundSdead_00f8e5a6_5"
"Almalexia","","Trueflame",Neutral,50,"The blade burns bright again!","The blade burns bright again!","fbmwTRBlade_1Trueflame_00001b9c_1"
"Almalexia","","Trueflame",Neutral,50,"Oh, how it burned with power! You must find the pieces and forge the blade once again.","Oh, how it burned with power! You must find the pieces and forge the blade once again.","fbmwTRBlade_1Trueflame_00014c5c_1"
"Almalexia","","Trueflame",Neutral,50,"The Blade of Nerevar. In the battle beneath Red Mountain, Trueflame was shattered, the flame extinguished, and in the confusion, the pieces lost.","The Blade of Nerevar. In the battle beneath Red Mountain, Trueflame was shattered, the flame extinguished, and in the confusion, the pieces lost.","fbmwTRBlade_1Trueflame_00014c5a_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"It is time for you, Nerevarine, to remake the blade and take your place by my side once again. I have only one, which I now give to you.","It is time for you, Nerevarine, to remake the blade and take your place by my side once again. I have only one, which I now give to you.","fbmwTRBlade_1Trueflame_00014c5a_2"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"Through my magic, I have been able to determine that the other pieces of the blade are nearby.","Through my magic, I have been able to determine that the other pieces of the blade are nearby.","fbmwTRBlade_1Trueflame_00014c5a_3"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"Find the other two pieces of the blade, and forge the blade anew. Only you may accomplish this, Nerevarine.","Find the other two pieces of the blade, and forge the blade anew. Only you may accomplish this, Nerevarine.","fbmwTRBlade_1Trueflame_00014c5a_4"
"Almalexia","","Craftsmen",Neutral,50,"You'll find a number of them in my fair city. It was these artisans who built this city from ruins under my guidance.","You'll find a number of them in my fair city. It was these artisans who built this city from ruins under my guidance.","fbmwTRBlade_1craftsmen_00014c48_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"This glorious temple was erected by men and mer of stout heart and strong faith.","This glorious temple was erected by men and mer of stout heart and strong faith.","fbmwTRBlade_1craftsmen_00014c48_2"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"If any in this land can forge that blade, they'll be found in my city.","If any in this land can forge that blade, they'll be found in my city.","fbmwTRBlade_1craftsmen_00014c48_3"
"Almalexia","","Unstable",Neutral,50,"Once, Sotha Sil was like we are, the Lord Vivec and I.","Once, Sotha Sil was like we are, the Lord Vivec and I.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1unstable_00001b92_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"He spent time among these mortals, instructing them, counseling them, protecting them from harm.","He spent time among these mortals, instructing them, counseling them, protecting them from harm.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1unstable_00001b92_2"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"He may have loved them more than any of us, though I know not why. It has been many years since any have seen the Sorcerer, though.","He may have loved them more than any of us, though I know not why. It has been many years since any have seen the Sorcerer, though.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1unstable_00001b92_3"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"Many more since he took initiates into his service.","Many more since he took initiates into his service.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1unstable_00001b92_4"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"I believe he grew weary of mortal imperfections, and retired to his Clockwork City, where he reshapes life,","I believe he grew weary of mortal imperfections, and retired to his Clockwork City, where he reshapes life,","fbmwTRSothaSil_1unstable_00001b92_5"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"And some say the very world, into an image he finds pleasing.","And some say the very world, into an image he finds pleasing.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1unstable_00001b92_6"
"Almalexia","","Beliefs",Neutral,50,"This cult will be gone from my city soon. I cannot allow such heresy to poison the minds of my people.","This cult will be gone from my city soon. I cannot allow such heresy to poison the minds of my people.","fbmwTRShowPower_1beliefs_00f8e5a8_1"
"Almalexia","","Beliefs",Neutral,50,"They would dare...? So, the Tribunal has lost its power, has it? These fools would dare question Almalexia's power, here in her city!","They would dare...? So, the Tribunal has lost its power, has it? These fools would dare question Almalexia's power, here in her city!","fbmwTRShowPower_1beliefs_00f8e5a9_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"I will give them a lesson in power,  and you will be my agent.","I will give them a lesson in power,  and you will be my agent.","fbmwTRShowPower_1beliefs_00f8e5a9_2"
"Almalexia","","Task",Neutral,50,"Since the horrendous attack on the city, there have been some alarming developments. One of the most troublesome has been a cult that has recently formed, led by a young Dunmer named Eno Romari.","Since the horrendous attack on the city, there have been some alarming developments. One of the most troublesome has been a cult that has recently formed, led by a young Dunmer named Eno Romari.","fbmwTRShowPower_1task_00f8ba87_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"They call themselves the End of Times. In these troubled times, I fear the cult is gaining in popularity.","They call themselves the End of Times. In these troubled times, I fear the cult is gaining in popularity.","fbmwTRShowPower_1task_00f8ba87_2"
"Almalexia","","Why did you want this ring?",Neutral,50,"Do not concern yourself too deeply in these matters, friend. I will use the ring as I do everything...to serve the Temple and all of Morrowind.","Do not concern yourself too deeply in these matters, friend. I will use the ring as I do everything...to serve the Temple and all of Morrowind.","fbmwTRMazedBand_fbmwTRBandQuestion_00f8bcbb_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"You have been a pleasant surprise to meet. I have seen something in you that I have not seen in a very long time. I bestow the blessing of My Light upon you.","You have been a pleasant surprise to meet. I have seen something in you that I have not seen in a very long time. I bestow the blessing of My Light upon you.","fbmwTRMazedBand_fbmwTRBandQuestion_00f8bcbb_2"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"May it serve you well. We will speak again soon.","May it serve you well. We will speak again soon.","fbmwTRMazedBand_fbmwTRBandQuestion_00f8bcbb_3"
"Almalexia","","It is my pleasure to serve you.",Neutral,50,"It is I who serve all of Morrowind. Your help has been appreciated. I have seen something in you that I have not seen in a very long time.","It is I who serve all of Morrowind. Your help has been appreciated. I have seen something in you that I have not seen in a very long time.","fbmwTRMazedBand_fbmwTRBandGive_00f8bcbd_1"
"Almalexia","","",Neutral,50,"I bestow the blessing of My Light upon you. We will speak again in the future.","I bestow the blessing of My Light upon you. We will speak again in the future.","fbmwTRMazedBand_fbmwTRBandGive_00f8bcbd_2"
