Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Commercial Potions",Neutral,50,"Commercial potions are guaranteed effective.","Commercial potions are guaranteed effective.","MorroDefaultQuest_1commercialSpotions_00320a14_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Most come in five commercial grades -- bargain, cheap, standard, quality, and exclusive -- increasing in effectiveness and duration according to quality and expense.","Most come in five commercial grades -- bargain, cheap, standard, quality, and exclusive -- increasing in effectiveness and duration according to quality and expense.","MorroDefaultQuest_1commercialSpotions_00320a14_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Some potions come in only one grade; they produce a single effect, and are guaranteed effective.","Some potions come in only one grade; they produce a single effect, and are guaranteed effective.","MorroDefaultQuest_1commercialSpotions_00320a14_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Adventurers lacking magic skills must rely on potions, scrolls, or enchantments when they require the benefits of magic effects.","Adventurers lacking magic skills must rely on potions, scrolls, or enchantments when they require the benefits of magic effects.","MorroDefaultQuest_1commercialSpotions_00320a14_4"
"","","Alteration Potions",Neutral,50,"Alteration potions provide beneficial magical effects from the domain of the Arcane College of Alteration.","Alteration potions provide beneficial magical effects from the domain of the Arcane College of Alteration.","MorroDefaultQuest_1alterationSpotions_00320a18_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Alteration potions include: burden, feather, and levitate.","Alteration potions include: burden, feather, and levitate.","MorroDefaultQuest_1alterationSpotions_00320a18_2"
"","","Vegetable Products",Neutral,50,"Vegetable products of commercial value on Vvardenfell include the following: ash yam, bittergreen petals, black anther, black lichen, bloat, chokeweed, comberry, corkbulb root, fire fern, gold kanet, green lichen, hackle-lo leaf, heather, kresh fiber, marshmerrow, moon sugar, muck, red lichen, resin, roobrush, saltrice, scathecraw, stoneflower petals, trama root, wickwheat, and willow anther.","Vegetable products of commercial value on Vvardenfell include the following: ash yam, bittergreen petals, black anther, black lichen, bloat, chokeweed, comberry, corkbulb root, fire fern, gold kanet, green lichen, hackle-lo leaf, heather, kresh fiber, marshmerrow, moon sugar, muck, red lichen, resin, roobrush, saltrice, scathecraw, stoneflower petals, trama root, wickwheat, and willow anther.","MorroDefaultQuest_1vegetableSproducts_00320a1a_1"
"","","Bittergreen Petals",Neutral,50,"Bittergreen is a red flowering plant with modest magical properties. It grows in the Red Mountain region.","Bittergreen is a red flowering plant with modest magical properties. It grows in the Red Mountain region.","MorroDefaultQuest_1bittergreenSpetals_00320a1c_1"
"","","Stoneflower Petals",Neutral,50,"Stoneflower petals are collected from a small common blue flower of the Ascadian Isles and Azura's Coast.","Stoneflower petals are collected from a small common blue flower of the Ascadian Isles and Azura's Coast.","MorroDefaultQuest_1stoneflowerSpetals_00320a1f_1"
"","","Mysticism Potions",Neutral,50,"Mysticism potions provide beneficial magical effects from the domain of the Arcane College of Mysticism.","Mysticism potions provide beneficial magical effects from the domain of the Arcane College of Mysticism.","MorroDefaultQuest_1mysticismSpotions_00320b6e_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Mysticism potions include: spell absorption, reflect, dispel, and telekinesis.","Mysticism potions include: spell absorption, reflect, dispel, and telekinesis.","MorroDefaultQuest_1mysticismSpotions_00320b6e_2"
"","","Mortar and Pestle",Neutral,50,"Mortar and Pestle is a bowl and grinding tool for mechanically reducing raw materials into the powders or pulps used in alchemical preparations.","Mortar and Pestle is a bowl and grinding tool for mechanically reducing raw materials into the powders or pulps used in alchemical preparations.","MorroDefaultQuest_1MortarSandSPestle_00320ba6_1"
"","","Alms for the poor",Neutral,50,"Sorry. I can't help you.","Sorry. I can't help you.","fbmwICBuckmothAlms_1almsSforStheSpoor_00f8a338_1"
"","","Homemade Potions",Neutral,50,"To make homemade potions, you need skill in alchemy, ingredients, and the necessary apparatus.","To make homemade potions, you need skill in alchemy, ingredients, and the necessary apparatus.","MorroDefaultQuest_1homemadeSpotions_00320cbd_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Ingredients can be collected from the animal bodies, plants, and the environment.","Ingredients can be collected from the animal bodies, plants, and the environment.","MorroDefaultQuest_1homemadeSpotions_00320cbd_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"There are four pieces of alchemist apparatus -- mortar and pestle, alembic, calcinator, and retort. Alchemical apparatus comes in grades of quality;","There are four pieces of alchemist apparatus -- mortar and pestle, alembic, calcinator, and retort. Alchemical apparatus comes in grades of quality;","MorroDefaultQuest_1homemadeSpotions_00320cbd_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"higher quality apparatus is more effective and reliable.","higher quality apparatus is more effective and reliable.","MorroDefaultQuest_1homemadeSpotions_00320cbd_4"
"","","Illusion Potions",Neutral,50,"Illusion potions provide beneficial magical effects from the domain of the Arcane College of Illusion.","Illusion potions provide beneficial magical effects from the domain of the Arcane College of Illusion.","MorroDefaultQuest_1illusionSpotions_00320cc1_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Illusion potions include: night-eye, invisibility, and light.","Illusion potions include: night-eye, invisibility, and light.","MorroDefaultQuest_1illusionSpotions_00320cc1_2"
"","","Mineral products",Neutral,50,"Mineral products of commercial value on Vvardenfell include the following: ash salts, diamond, emerald, ruby, and scrap metal.","Mineral products of commercial value on Vvardenfell include the following: ash salts, diamond, emerald, ruby, and scrap metal.","MorroDefaultQuest_1mineralSproducts_00320cc3_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Pearl is not a mineral product, but is traditionally included with gems because of its association with precious stones and their ornamental value.","Pearl is not a mineral product, but is traditionally included with gems because of its association with precious stones and their ornamental value.","MorroDefaultQuest_1mineralSproducts_00320cc3_2"
"","","Corprus Weepings",Neutral,50,"Corprus weepings are hardened secretions that fall from the fleshy sores of corprus victims.","Corprus weepings are hardened secretions that fall from the fleshy sores of corprus victims.","MorroDefaultQuest_1corprusSweepings_00320cc5_1"
"","","Luminous Russula",Neutral,50,"Luminous russula is a squat, mottled-brown-and-green toadstool mushroom of the Bitter Coast region with modest magical properties.","Luminous russula is a squat, mottled-brown-and-green toadstool mushroom of the Bitter Coast region with modest magical properties.","MorroDefaultQuest_1luminousSrussula_00320cc8_1"
"","","Restore Potions",Neutral,50,"Restore potions permanently restore attributes and abilities reduced by harmful spells or supernatural attacks.","Restore potions permanently restore attributes and abilities reduced by harmful spells or supernatural attacks.","MorroDefaultQuest_1restoreSpotions_00320f47_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Restore potions include: restore strength, restore intelligence, restore willpower, restore agility, restore speed, restore personality, restore luck, restore health, restore spell points, restore fatigue, and restore endurance.","Restore potions include: restore strength, restore intelligence, restore willpower, restore agility, restore speed, restore personality, restore luck, restore health, restore spell points, restore fatigue, and restore endurance.","MorroDefaultQuest_1restoreSpotions_00320f47_2"
"","","Fortify Potions",Neutral,50,"Fortify potions temporarily increase attributes and abilities.","Fortify potions temporarily increase attributes and abilities.","MorroDefaultQuest_1fortifySpotions_00320f4d_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Fortify potions include: fortify strength, fortify intelligence, fortify willpower, fortify agility, fortify speed, fortify personality, fortify luck, fortify health, fortify spell points, fortify fatigue, and fortify endurance.","Fortify potions include: fortify strength, fortify intelligence, fortify willpower, fortify agility, fortify speed, fortify personality, fortify luck, fortify health, fortify spell points, fortify fatigue, and fortify endurance.","MorroDefaultQuest_1fortifySpotions_00320f4d_2"
"","","Aquatic Potions",Neutral,50,"Aquatic potions aid the subject in movement and survival in an aquatic environment.","Aquatic potions aid the subject in movement and survival in an aquatic environment.","MorroDefaultQuest_1aquaticSpotions_00320f51_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Aquatic potions include: water breathing, swift swim, and water walking.","Aquatic potions include: water breathing, swift swim, and water walking.","MorroDefaultQuest_1aquaticSpotions_00320f51_2"
"","","Animal products",Neutral,50,"Animal products of commercial value on Vvardenfell include the following: alit hide, crab meat, dreugh wax, guar hide, hound meat, kagouti hide, kwama cuttle, kwama egg, netch leather, racer plumes, rat meat, scales, scrib jelly, scrib jerky, scuttle , shalk resin, and Sload soap.","Animal products of commercial value on Vvardenfell include the following: alit hide, crab meat, dreugh wax, guar hide, hound meat, kagouti hide, kwama cuttle, kwama egg, netch leather, racer plumes, rat meat, scales, scrib jelly, scrib jerky, scuttle , shalk resin, and Sload soap.","MorroDefaultQuest_1animalSproducts_00320f53_1"
"","","Exotic Products",Neutral,50,"Exotic products of commercial value on Vvardenfell include the following: bonemeal, corprus weepings, Daedra skin, Daedra's heart, ectoplasm, fire salts, frost salts, Ghoul heart, gravedust, raw ebony, raw glass, Scamp skin, Vampire dust, and void salts.","Exotic products of commercial value on Vvardenfell include the following: bonemeal, corprus weepings, Daedra skin, Daedra's heart, ectoplasm, fire salts, frost salts, Ghoul heart, gravedust, raw ebony, raw glass, Scamp skin, Vampire dust, and void salts.","MorroDefaultQuest_1exoticSproducts_00320f55_1"
"","","Violet Coprinus",Neutral,50,"Violet coprinus is a tall, slender-stemmed, light-green-capped mushroom of the Bitter Coast region with modest magical properties.","Violet coprinus is a tall, slender-stemmed, light-green-capped mushroom of the Bitter Coast region with modest magical properties.","MorroDefaultQuest_1violetScoprinus_0032104f_1"
"","","Resist Potions",Neutral,50,"Resist potions increase the subject's natural resistances to various harmful forces and conditions.","Resist potions increase the subject's natural resistances to various harmful forces and conditions.","MorroDefaultQuest_1resistSpotions_003212c0_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Resist potions include: resist fire, resist frost, resist shock, resist magicka, resist disease, and resist poison.","Resist potions include: resist fire, resist frost, resist shock, resist magicka, resist disease, and resist poison.","MorroDefaultQuest_1resistSpotions_003212c0_2"
"","","Detect Potions",Neutral,50,"Detect potions provide magical means of perceiving certain classes of things in space.","Detect potions provide magical means of perceiving certain classes of things in space.","MorroDefaultQuest_1detectSpotions_003212c4_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Detect potions include: detect key, detect creatures, and detect enchantment.","Detect potions include: detect key, detect creatures, and detect enchantment.","MorroDefaultQuest_1detectSpotions_003212c4_2"
"","","Shield Potions",Neutral,50,"Shield potions protect the subject from various forms of physical attack while injuring attackers in close proximity.","Shield potions protect the subject from various forms of physical attack while injuring attackers in close proximity.","MorroDefaultQuest_1shieldSpotions_003212c8_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Shield potions include: fire shield, lightning shield, and frost shield.","Shield potions include: fire shield, lightning shield, and frost shield.","MorroDefaultQuest_1shieldSpotions_003212c8_2"
"","","Daedra's Heart",Neutral,50,"A daedra's heart must be removed during the brief period of its appearance on the mortal plane.","A daedra's heart must be removed during the brief period of its appearance on the mortal plane.","MorroDefaultQuest_1DaedraAsSheart_003212ca_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The daedra's heart has modest magical properties, but, since removing the heart is generally fatal to the specimen, the substance is rare and expensive.","The daedra's heart has modest magical properties, but, since removing the heart is generally fatal to the specimen, the substance is rare and expensive.","MorroDefaultQuest_1DaedraAsSheart_003212ca_2"
"","","Hackle-Lo Leaf",Neutral,50,"Hackle-lo leaf is a tasty edible succulent leaf of the Grazelands, prized both for its taste and its roborative powers.","Hackle-lo leaf is a tasty edible succulent leaf of the Grazelands, prized both for its taste and its roborative powers.","MorroDefaultQuest_1hackleTloSleaf_003212cc_1"
"","","Bungler's Bane",Neutral,50,"Bungler's Bane is a mottled brown-and-orange shelf fungus collected from the trunks of trees in the Bitter Coast region.","Bungler's Bane is a mottled brown-and-orange shelf fungus collected from the trunks of trees in the Bitter Coast region.","MorroDefaultQuest_1bunglerAsSbane_0032144d_1"
"","","Little Advice",Neutral,50,"Anarenen at the Ald'ruhn Guild of Mages is happy to talk your ear off about alchemy.","Anarenen at the Ald'ruhn Guild of Mages is happy to talk your ear off about alchemy.","MorroDefaultQuest_1littleSadvice_0032194d_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"He's been on Vvardenfell a while, and knows everything there is to know about practicing the profession here.","He's been on Vvardenfell a while, and knows everything there is to know about practicing the profession here.","MorroDefaultQuest_1littleSadvice_0032194d_2"
"","","Little Advice",Neutral,50,"Anarenen at the Ald'ruhn Guild of Mages is happy to talk your ear off about alchemy.","Anarenen at the Ald'ruhn Guild of Mages is happy to talk your ear off about alchemy.","MorroDefaultQuest_1littleSadvice_0032194e_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"He's been on Vvardenfell a while, and knows everything there is to know about practicing the profession here.","He's been on Vvardenfell a while, and knows everything there is to know about practicing the profession here.","MorroDefaultQuest_1littleSadvice_0032194e_2"
"","","Toxic Potions",Neutral,50,"Toxic potions are potions with undesirable effects.","Toxic potions are potions with undesirable effects.","MorroDefaultQuest_1toxicSpotions_00321982_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"They are not available commercially, and when found, usually represent clumsy or ill-informed attempts to make useful potions by unskilled alchemists.","They are not available commercially, and when found, usually represent clumsy or ill-informed attempts to make useful potions by unskilled alchemists.","MorroDefaultQuest_1toxicSpotions_00321982_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Toxic potions include: drain strength, drain intelligence, drain willpower, drain agility, drain speed, drain personality, drain luck, drain health, drain spell points, drain fatigue, drain endurance, and paralyze.","Toxic potions include: drain strength, drain intelligence, drain willpower, drain agility, drain speed, drain personality, drain luck, drain health, drain spell points, drain fatigue, drain endurance, and paralyze.","MorroDefaultQuest_1toxicSpotions_00321982_3"
"","","Netch Leather",Neutral,50,"Cured netch skin, durable, flexible, and variously colored, is used throughout the Empire in garments, armor, weapons, household goods, and furnishings.","Cured netch skin, durable, flexible, and variously colored, is used throughout the Empire in garments, armor, weapons, household goods, and furnishings.","MorroDefaultQuest_1netchSleather_00321984_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Raw skins and prepared netch leather are important export products of Vvardenfell District.","Raw skins and prepared netch leather are important export products of Vvardenfell District.","MorroDefaultQuest_1netchSleather_00321984_2"
"","","Corkbulb Root",Neutral,50,"Corkbulb trees are grown for their tough, fibrous roots which have modest magical properties.","Corkbulb trees are grown for their tough, fibrous roots which have modest magical properties.","MorroDefaultQuest_1corkbulbSroot_00321985_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"On Vvardenfell corkbulb root is used in place of wood, since trees won't grow in this harsh environment. Corkbulb grows best in the Ascadian Isles.","On Vvardenfell corkbulb root is used in place of wood, since trees won't grow in this harsh environment. Corkbulb grows best in the Ascadian Isles.","MorroDefaultQuest_1corkbulbSroot_00321985_2"
"","","Willow Anther",Neutral,50,"Willow anther is the powdery residue from pollen-bearing parts of the willow flower that grows in the Ascadian Isles and on Azura's Coast.","Willow anther is the powdery residue from pollen-bearing parts of the willow flower that grows in the Ascadian Isles and on Azura's Coast.","MorroDefaultQuest_1willowSanther_00321989_1"
"","","Cure Potions",Neutral,50,"Cure potions remove diseases and harmful conditions.","Cure potions remove diseases and harmful conditions.","MorroDefaultQuest_1cureSpotions_00321c47_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Cure potions include: cure poison, cure common disease, cure paralyzation, and cure blight disease.","Cure potions include: cure poison, cure common disease, cure paralyzation, and cure blight disease.","MorroDefaultQuest_1cureSpotions_00321c47_2"
"","","Kagouti Hide",Neutral,50,"Kagouti hide is the skin of the wild kagouti. The hide is made into leather and used in clothing and household goods.","Kagouti hide is the skin of the wild kagouti. The hide is made into leather and used in clothing and household goods.","MorroDefaultQuest_1kagoutiShide_00321c49_1"
"","","Kwama Cuttle",Neutral,50,"Kwama cuttle is a tough, waxy substance that comes from the beak of kwama beasts. Kwama cuttle has modest magical properties.","Kwama cuttle is a tough, waxy substance that comes from the beak of kwama beasts. Kwama cuttle has modest magical properties.","MorroDefaultQuest_1kwamaScuttle_00321c4b_1"
"","","Racer Plumes",Neutral,50,"Racer plumes from the native bird-like cliff racer are used locally and throughout the Empire as decorations for garments and household goods.","Racer plumes from the native bird-like cliff racer are used locally and throughout the Empire as decorations for garments and household goods.","MorroDefaultQuest_1racerSplumes_00321c4d_1"
"","","Vampire Dust",Neutral,50,"Of interest only to necromancers and alchemists, vampire dust is collected solely from the withering corpses of slain vampires.","Of interest only to necromancers and alchemists, vampire dust is collected solely from the withering corpses of slain vampires.","MorroDefaultQuest_1VampireSdust_00321c4f_1"
"","","Black Anther",Neutral,50,"Black anther is a flowering plant that grows along Azura's Coast.","Black anther is a flowering plant that grows along Azura's Coast.","MorroDefaultQuest_1blackSanther_00321c51_1"
"","","Black Lichen",Neutral,50,"Black lichen is a hardy primitive plant that grows in the harsh conditions of the Ashlands, Red Mountain, Molag Amur, and Azura's Coast.","Black lichen is a hardy primitive plant that grows in the harsh conditions of the Ashlands, Red Mountain, Molag Amur, and Azura's Coast.","MorroDefaultQuest_1blackSlichen_00321c52_1"
"","","Green Lichen",Neutral,50,"Green lichen is a hardy primitive plant with modest magical properties that grows in the Ascadian Isles and Azura's Coast.","Green lichen is a hardy primitive plant with modest magical properties that grows in the Ascadian Isles and Azura's Coast.","MorroDefaultQuest_1greenSlichen_00321c55_1"
"","","Daedra Skin",Neutral,50,"Daedra skin must be removed from the specimen while it remains on the mortal plane.","Daedra skin must be removed from the specimen while it remains on the mortal plane.","fbmwHTDaedraSkin_1DaedraSSkin_00321e15_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Daedra skin has modest magical properties, but collecting it from the daedra is hard work and dangerous.","Daedra skin has modest magical properties, but collecting it from the daedra is hard work and dangerous.","fbmwHTDaedraSkin_1DaedraSSkin_00321e15_2"
"","","Ingredients",Neutral,50,"Ingredients sought by alchemists and apothecaries fall into four broad categories: animal, vegetable, and mineral products, and a fourth category loosely described as exotic.","Ingredients sought by alchemists and apothecaries fall into four broad categories: animal, vegetable, and mineral products, and a fourth category loosely described as exotic.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ingredients_00321e64_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Animal products come from mortal beasts. Vegetable products come from plants. Mineral products come from the earth.","Animal products come from mortal beasts. Vegetable products come from plants. Mineral products come from the earth.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ingredients_00321e64_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Exotic products come from many sources, but are generally of magical or otherworldly origin. When eaten, some ingredients have useful effects;","Exotic products come from many sources, but are generally of magical or otherworldly origin. When eaten, some ingredients have useful effects;","MorroDefaultQuest_1ingredients_00321e64_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"others have bad effects; the scale of effect depends on alchemy skill.","others have bad effects; the scale of effect depends on alchemy skill.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ingredients_00321e64_4"
"","","Scrib Jelly",Neutral,50,"Scribs are a larval form of the kwama.","Scribs are a larval form of the kwama.","MorroDefaultQuest_1scribSjelly_00321e68_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Crushed scribs produce a nutritious but sour-tasting gelatin with modest magical properties that the natives eat with gusto.","Crushed scribs produce a nutritious but sour-tasting gelatin with modest magical properties that the natives eat with gusto.","MorroDefaultQuest_1scribSjelly_00321e68_2"
"","","Scrib Jerky",Neutral,50,"Scribs cut into strips and dried in the sun are called scrib jerky.","Scribs cut into strips and dried in the sun are called scrib jerky.","MorroDefaultQuest_1scribSjerky_00321e6a_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Scrib jerky has modest magical properties, and tastes scarcely worse when spoiled than when fresh, and are a practical foodstuff for the hardy native traveler.","Scrib jerky has modest magical properties, and tastes scarcely worse when spoiled than when fresh, and are a practical foodstuff for the hardy native traveler.","MorroDefaultQuest_1scribSjerky_00321e6a_2"
"","","Shalk Resin",Neutral,50,"Shalk resins are the tough, soluble substances extracted from shalk hides.","Shalk resins are the tough, soluble substances extracted from shalk hides.","MorroDefaultQuest_1shalkSresin_00321e6c_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Shalk resins are used as glues and stiffeners in manufacturing bonemold and chitin armors.","Shalk resins are used as glues and stiffeners in manufacturing bonemold and chitin armors.","MorroDefaultQuest_1shalkSresin_00321e6c_2"
"","","Frost Salts",Neutral,50,"Frost salts are the crystalline compound that precipitates from elemental frost in solution.","Frost salts are the crystalline compound that precipitates from elemental frost in solution.","MorroDefaultQuest_1frostSsalts_00321e6e_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Such residues may be collected from the remains of frost atronachs that have been banished from the mortal plane.","Such residues may be collected from the remains of frost atronachs that have been banished from the mortal plane.","MorroDefaultQuest_1frostSsalts_00321e6e_2"
"","","Ghoul Heart",Neutral,50,"The substance called ghoul heart is heart tissue collected from the remains of an ash ghoul.","The substance called ghoul heart is heart tissue collected from the remains of an ash ghoul.","MorroDefaultQuest_1GhoulSheart_00321e70_1"
"","","Scrap Metal",Neutral,50,"Scrap metal refers not to common scraps of iron and steel, but to bits of exotic metals recovered from animated Dwemer artifacts like the centurion.","Scrap metal refers not to common scraps of iron and steel, but to bits of exotic metals recovered from animated Dwemer artifacts like the centurion.","MorroDefaultQuest_1scrapSmetal_00321e7d_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Such metal is rare and precious, and prized both by collectors of antiquities and students of metals and enchantments.","Such metal is rare and precious, and prized both by collectors of antiquities and students of metals and enchantments.","MorroDefaultQuest_1scrapSmetal_00321e7d_2"
"","","Fire Petals",Neutral,50,"Fire petals have modest magical properties, and are collected from the fire fern plant that grows on Red Mountain, in Molag Mar, and on Azura's Coast.","Fire petals have modest magical properties, and are collected from the fire fern plant that grows on Red Mountain, in Molag Mar, and on Azura's Coast.","MorroDefaultQuest_1fireSpetals_00321e7f_1"
"","","Kresh Fiber",Neutral,50,"Kreshweed fiber is a resinous fiber with modest magical properties that comes from the coarse grass of the Grazelands and Azura's Coast called kreshweed.","Kreshweed fiber is a resinous fiber with modest magical properties that comes from the coarse grass of the Grazelands and Azura's Coast called kreshweed.","MorroDefaultQuest_1kreshSfiber_00321e81_1"
"","","Marshmerrow",Neutral,50,"The sweet pulp of marshmerrow reeds is a delectable foodstuff, and when eaten fresh or prepared, it has modest healing properties.","The sweet pulp of marshmerrow reeds is a delectable foodstuff, and when eaten fresh or prepared, it has modest healing properties.","MorroDefaultQuest_1marshmerrow_00321e83_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Marshmerrow is an important cash crop of the farms and plantations of the Ascadian Isles, but it also grows wild in the Grazelands and on Azura's Coast.","Marshmerrow is an important cash crop of the farms and plantations of the Ascadian Isles, but it also grows wild in the Grazelands and on Azura's Coast.","MorroDefaultQuest_1marshmerrow_00321e83_2"
"","","Coda Flower",Neutral,50,"The coda flower is the fruiting body collected from the primitive draggle-tail plant of the Bitter Coast.","The coda flower is the fruiting body collected from the primitive draggle-tail plant of the Bitter Coast.","MorroDefaultQuest_1codaSflower_00321e85_1"
"","","Ampoule Pod",Neutral,50,"The immature state of the fruiting body of the primitive draggle-tail plant of the Bitter Coast is called the ampoule pod.","The immature state of the fruiting body of the primitive draggle-tail plant of the Bitter Coast is called the ampoule pod.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ampouleSpod_00321e87_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"This pod has modest magical properties prized by alchemists.","This pod has modest magical properties prized by alchemists.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ampouleSpod_00321e87_2"
"","","Hypha Facia",Neutral,50,"Hypha facia is a light brown shelf fungus collected from the trunks of trees in the Bitter Coast Region.","Hypha facia is a light brown shelf fungus collected from the trunks of trees in the Bitter Coast Region.","MorroDefaultQuest_1hyphaSfacia_00321e8a_1"
"","","Sload Soap",Neutral,50,"Sload soap is a waxy substance made from the immature non-sentient forms of the sload.","Sload soap is a waxy substance made from the immature non-sentient forms of the sload.","MorroDefaultQuest_1SloadSSoap_00322381_1"
"","","Dreugh Wax",Neutral,50,"Dreugh wax is a tough, waxy substance with modest magical properties, scraped from dreugh shells.","Dreugh wax is a tough, waxy substance with modest magical properties, scraped from dreugh shells.","MorroDefaultQuest_1dreughSwax_003223e7_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Dreugh are powerful aquatic creatures, and hunting them for their hides and wax is a dangerous occupation.","Dreugh are powerful aquatic creatures, and hunting them for their hides and wax is a dangerous occupation.","MorroDefaultQuest_1dreughSwax_003223e7_2"
"","","Hound Meat",Neutral,50,"Hound meat is the flesh of the nix-hound. The meat is sweet and tender, and has modest magical properties.","Hound meat is the flesh of the nix-hound. The meat is sweet and tender, and has modest magical properties.","MorroDefaultQuest_1houndSmeat_003223e9_1"
"","","Fire Salts",Neutral,50,"Fire salts are the crystalline compound that precipitates from elemental fire in solution.","Fire salts are the crystalline compound that precipitates from elemental fire in solution.","MorroDefaultQuest_1fireSsalts_003223eb_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Such residues may be collected from the remains of fire atronachs that have been banished from the mortal plane.","Such residues may be collected from the remains of fire atronachs that have been banished from the mortal plane.","MorroDefaultQuest_1fireSsalts_003223eb_2"
"","","Scamp Skin",Neutral,50,"Scamp skin must be removed from the specimen while it is still bound on the mortal plane.","Scamp skin must be removed from the specimen while it is still bound on the mortal plane.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ScampSskin_00322119_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"It is an unpleasant business for both the scamp and skin-farmer, and alchemists have trouble keeping the substance in stock.","It is an unpleasant business for both the scamp and skin-farmer, and alchemists have trouble keeping the substance in stock.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ScampSskin_00322119_2"
"","","Void Salts",Neutral,50,"Void salts are rare crystalline precipitates with modest magical properties collected from the evanescent remains of a slain storm atronach.","Void salts are rare crystalline precipitates with modest magical properties collected from the evanescent remains of a slain storm atronach.","MorroDefaultQuest_1voidSsalts_0032211b_1"
"","","Gold Kanet",Neutral,50,"Gold kanet is a flowering plant commonly found in the Ascadian Isles and on Azura's Coast.","Gold kanet is a flowering plant commonly found in the Ascadian Isles and on Azura's Coast.","MorroDefaultQuest_1goldSkanet_0032211e_1"
"","","Moon Sugar",Neutral,50,"Moon sugar is a grainy powder of small white crystals refined from cane grasses of Elseweyr's coasts and estuaries.","Moon sugar is a grainy powder of small white crystals refined from cane grasses of Elseweyr's coasts and estuaries.","MorroDefaultQuest_1moonSsugar_00322120_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Used as a spice in Elsweyr, it has modest magical properties, and is also a potent narcotic, and illegal in Morrowind and the rest of the Empire.","Used as a spice in Elsweyr, it has modest magical properties, and is also a potent narcotic, and illegal in Morrowind and the rest of the Empire.","MorroDefaultQuest_1moonSsugar_00322120_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Criminals have attempted to grow moon sugar grasses in Vvardenfell, without success.","Criminals have attempted to grow moon sugar grasses in Vvardenfell, without success.","MorroDefaultQuest_1moonSsugar_00322120_3"
"","","Red Lichen",Neutral,50,"Red lichen is a hardy primitive plant that grows in the harsh conditions of Red Mountain, Molag Amur, and the Ashlands.","Red lichen is a hardy primitive plant that grows in the harsh conditions of Red Mountain, Molag Amur, and the Ashlands.","MorroDefaultQuest_1redSlichen_00322122_1"
"","","Scathecraw",Neutral,50,"Scathecraw is the soft inner flesh of long, tough reddish grasses growing in the thermal ash regions of the Ashlands, Molag Amur, and Red Mountain.","Scathecraw is the soft inner flesh of long, tough reddish grasses growing in the thermal ash regions of the Ashlands, Molag Amur, and Red Mountain.","MorroDefaultQuest_1scathecraw_00322124_1"
"","","Trama Root",Neutral,50,"A calming tea with modest magical properties is brewed from the thick, bitter-tasting root of the trama shrub.","A calming tea with modest magical properties is brewed from the thick, bitter-tasting root of the trama shrub.","MorroDefaultQuest_1tramaSroot_00322126_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The Trama shrub grows in the bitter, ashy soils of the Ashlands, Molag Amur, and Red Mountain.","The Trama shrub grows in the bitter, ashy soils of the Ashlands, Molag Amur, and Red Mountain.","MorroDefaultQuest_1tramaSroot_00322126_2"
"","","Calcinator",Neutral,50,"A calcinator is a stove or crucible which reduces metals and substances to ash so their arcane properties can be separated from the dross.","A calcinator is a stove or crucible which reduces metals and substances to ash so their arcane properties can be separated from the dross.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Calcinator_003221d6_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"They must be made of porcelain or iron device to withstand the high temperatures necessary to reduce certain substances to ash.","They must be made of porcelain or iron device to withstand the high temperatures necessary to reduce certain substances to ash.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Calcinator_003221d6_2"
"","","Alit Hide",Neutral,50,"The tough hide of the wild alit makes a serviceable multi-purpose leather. Ashlanders hunt the alit and use their tanned hides as trade goods.","The tough hide of the wild alit makes a serviceable multi-purpose leather. Ashlanders hunt the alit and use their tanned hides as trade goods.","MorroDefaultQuest_1alitShide_0032251f_1"
"","","Crab meat",Neutral,50,"The mudcrab native to Vvardenfell is prized for its sweet crab meat.","The mudcrab native to Vvardenfell is prized for its sweet crab meat.","MorroDefaultQuest_1crabSmeat_00322521_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The flesh of the mudcrab is both tasty and possessed of modest magical properties.","The flesh of the mudcrab is both tasty and possessed of modest magical properties.","MorroDefaultQuest_1crabSmeat_00322521_2"
"","","Guar Hide",Neutral,50,"Guar hide is cured to make guar leather, used in native clothing, armors, and household goods.","Guar hide is cured to make guar leather, used in native clothing, armors, and household goods.","MorroDefaultQuest_1guarShide_00322523_1"
"","","Kwama Egg",Neutral,50,"Kwama eggs are a rich, nutritious foodstuff with modest magical properties.","Kwama eggs are a rich, nutritious foodstuff with modest magical properties.","MorroDefaultQuest_1kwamaSegg_00322525_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Popular throughout the Empire, kwama eggs stay fresh for a long time, and kwama mining is a profitable industry on Vvardenfell.","Popular throughout the Empire, kwama eggs stay fresh for a long time, and kwama mining is a profitable industry on Vvardenfell.","MorroDefaultQuest_1kwamaSegg_00322525_2"
"","","Ectoplasm",Neutral,50,"Ectoplasm is a filmy residue with modest magical properties that remains after a revenant spirit has been banished from the mortal plane.","Ectoplasm is a filmy residue with modest magical properties that remains after a revenant spirit has been banished from the mortal plane.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ectoplasm_00322527_1"
"","","Gravedust",Neutral,50,"Gravedust is spirit-affinitive dust taken from remains buried in consecrated ground.","Gravedust is spirit-affinitive dust taken from remains buried in consecrated ground.","MorroDefaultQuest_1gravedust_00322529_1"
"","","Raw Ebony",Neutral,50,"Raw ebony is one of the most precious substances in the Empire, and most of the continent's deposits are here on Vvardenfell.","Raw ebony is one of the most precious substances in the Empire, and most of the continent's deposits are here on Vvardenfell.","MorroDefaultQuest_1rawSebony_0032252b_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Raw ebony itself is an extremely hard, durable, black glass-like substance, said to be the crystalized blood of the gods.","Raw ebony itself is an extremely hard, durable, black glass-like substance, said to be the crystalized blood of the gods.","MorroDefaultQuest_1rawSebony_0032252b_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Raw ebony is protected by Imperial law, and may not be mined or exported without an Imperial charter.","Raw ebony is protected by Imperial law, and may not be mined or exported without an Imperial charter.","MorroDefaultQuest_1rawSebony_0032252b_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Ebony smuggling is a profitable but dangerous source of illegal wealth on Vvardenfell.","Ebony smuggling is a profitable but dangerous source of illegal wealth on Vvardenfell.","MorroDefaultQuest_1rawSebony_0032252b_4"
"","","Raw Glass",Neutral,50,"Raw glass is similar to raw ebony, but less well-known. Ebony is jet black, while glass is a milky translucent green.","Raw glass is similar to raw ebony, but less well-known. Ebony is jet black, while glass is a milky translucent green.","MorroDefaultQuest_1rawSglass_0032252d_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Less durable, but much lighter and more flexible than ebony, glass is used primarily to make the distinctive, elegant glass armors and weapons of High Elven design.","Less durable, but much lighter and more flexible than ebony, glass is used primarily to make the distinctive, elegant glass armors and weapons of High Elven design.","MorroDefaultQuest_1rawSglass_0032252d_2"
"","","Ash Salts",Neutral,50,"Ash salts are hard grey crystals formed from the ash deposited by ash storms in the ash wastes and lava fields.","Ash salts are hard grey crystals formed from the ash deposited by ash storms in the ash wastes and lava fields.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ashSsalts_0032252f_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Ash salts are most often collected from the remains of creatures like the ash slave, the ash ghoul, and ash zombie.","Ash salts are most often collected from the remains of creatures like the ash slave, the ash ghoul, and ash zombie.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ashSsalts_0032252f_2"
"","","Chokeweed",Neutral,50,"Chokeweed is a tough shrub growing in the rocky highlands of the West Gash.","Chokeweed is a tough shrub growing in the rocky highlands of the West Gash.","MorroDefaultQuest_1chokeweed_00322531_1"
"","","Wickwheat",Neutral,50,"Wickwheat is a wild Ashland grain with modest magical properties that grows in the Grazelands.","Wickwheat is a wild Ashland grain with modest magical properties that grows in the Grazelands.","MorroDefaultQuest_1wickwheat_00322533_1"
"","","Spore Pod",Neutral,50,"Spore pods are collected from the slough fern of the Bitter Coast.","Spore pods are collected from the slough fern of the Bitter Coast.","MorroDefaultQuest_1sporeSpod_00322535_1"
"","","Apparatus",Neutral,50,"Making potions requires pieces of specialized alchemical equipment called 'apparatus.' Better quality apparatus are more reliable in their results, and produce a finer product.","Making potions requires pieces of specialized alchemical equipment called 'apparatus.' Better quality apparatus are more reliable in their results, and produce a finer product.","MorroDefaultQuest_1apparatus_003225ca_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The four types of apparatus are: mortar and pestle, retort, alembic, and calcinator. Apparatus can be purchased from alchemists.","The four types of apparatus are: mortar and pestle, retort, alembic, and calcinator. Apparatus can be purchased from alchemists.","MorroDefaultQuest_1apparatus_003225ca_2"
"","","Bonemeal",Neutral,50,"Bonemeal is a finely ground powder with modest magical properties made from the bones of the bonewalker, an undead creature often found guarding ancestral tombs.","Bonemeal is a finely ground powder with modest magical properties made from the bones of the bonewalker, an undead creature often found guarding ancestral tombs.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Bonemeal_00322709_1"
"","","Rat Meat",Neutral,50,"Rat meat is tough and greasy, with an unpleasant odor and taste.","Rat meat is tough and greasy, with an unpleasant odor and taste.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ratSmeat_003227f8_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Nonetheless, it is cheap, abundant, and nutritious, and palatable when cooked in a stew and masked by strong strong spices.","Nonetheless, it is cheap, abundant, and nutritious, and palatable when cooked in a stew and masked by strong strong spices.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ratSmeat_003227f8_2"
"","","Comberry",Neutral,50,"The comberry is a bush that produces a bitter berry, best known as the basis of the native comberry brandy, a rough but potent alcoholic beverage of Morrowind.","The comberry is a bush that produces a bitter berry, best known as the basis of the native comberry brandy, a rough but potent alcoholic beverage of Morrowind.","MorroDefaultQuest_1comberry_003227fa_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Comberry is grown in the Ascadian Isles.","Comberry is grown in the Ascadian Isles.","MorroDefaultQuest_1comberry_003227fa_2"
"","","Roobrush",Neutral,50,"Roobrush is a tough, low, wiry shrub growing in arid, poor, ashy soils of the West Gash.","Roobrush is a tough, low, wiry shrub growing in arid, poor, ashy soils of the West Gash.","MorroDefaultQuest_1roobrush_003227fc_1"
"","","Saltrice",Neutral,50,"Saltrice is another of the tasty and nutritious foodstuffs with modest magical properties raised as export crops by Morrowind's farmers and plantation owners.","Saltrice is another of the tasty and nutritious foodstuffs with modest magical properties raised as export crops by Morrowind's farmers and plantation owners.","MorroDefaultQuest_1saltrice_003227fe_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Most saltrice seen in the Empire comes from southeastern Morrowind, but there are also some new and prospering farms and plantations in the Ascadian Isles.","Most saltrice seen in the Empire comes from southeastern Morrowind, but there are also some new and prospering farms and plantations in the Ascadian Isles.","MorroDefaultQuest_1saltrice_003227fe_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Saltrice also grows wild  in the Grazelands and on Azura's Coast.","Saltrice also grows wild  in the Grazelands and on Azura's Coast.","MorroDefaultQuest_1saltrice_003227fe_3"
"","","Potions",Neutral,50,"Alchemists, apothecaries, and healers, as well as general merchants, sell commercial potions. These potions are easy and reliable, but costly.","Alchemists, apothecaries, and healers, as well as general merchants, sell commercial potions. These potions are easy and reliable, but costly.","MorroDefaultQuest_1potions_00322921_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If you have training and skill in alchemy, and the necessary apparatus and ingredients, you can make your own homemade potions in the field.","If you have training and skill in alchemy, and the necessary apparatus and ingredients, you can make your own homemade potions in the field.","MorroDefaultQuest_1potions_00322921_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The eleven kinds of potions are: cure potions, restore potions, fortify potions, resist potions, aquatic potions, mysticism potions, alteration potions, illusion potions, detect potions, shield potions, and toxic potions.","The eleven kinds of potions are: cure potions, restore potions, fortify potions, resist potions, aquatic potions, mysticism potions, alteration potions, illusion potions, detect potions, shield potions, and toxic potions.","MorroDefaultQuest_1potions_00322921_3"
"","","Scuttle",Neutral,50,"Scuttle is Vvardenfell's favorite local dish.","Scuttle is Vvardenfell's favorite local dish.","MorroDefaultQuest_1scuttle_00322923_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"This cheese-like, greasy substance made from the flesh of local beetles is remarkably tasty, and has modest magical properties.","This cheese-like, greasy substance made from the flesh of local beetles is remarkably tasty, and has modest magical properties.","MorroDefaultQuest_1scuttle_00322923_2"
"","","Diamond",Neutral,50,"The diamond is a rare, transparent, extremely hard gemstone of great value.","The diamond is a rare, transparent, extremely hard gemstone of great value.","MorroDefaultQuest_1diamond_0032292b_1"
"","","Emerald",Neutral,50,"The emerald is a transparent green gem with modest magical properties.","The emerald is a transparent green gem with modest magical properties.","MorroDefaultQuest_1emerald_0032292d_1"
"","","Ash Yam",Neutral,50,"Ash yam is a tough tuberous root vegetable with modest magical properties. It grows commonly in the Ascadians Isles region.","Ash yam is a tough tuberous root vegetable with modest magical properties. It grows commonly in the Ascadians Isles region.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ashSyam_0032292f_1"
"","","Heather",Neutral,50,"Heather is a low evergreen shrub of the Ascadian Isles, known for its small, pinkish-purple flowers with modest magical properties.","Heather is a low evergreen shrub of the Ascadian Isles, known for its small, pinkish-purple flowers with modest magical properties.","MorroDefaultQuest_1heather_00322932_1"
"","","Alembic",Neutral,50,"An alembic is glass container in which the arcane properties of natural and supernatural substances are distilled from their raw ingredients.","An alembic is glass container in which the arcane properties of natural and supernatural substances are distilled from their raw ingredients.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Alembic_003229af_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The substances are infused, then heated until vapor is produced.","The substances are infused, then heated until vapor is produced.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Alembic_003229af_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The vapor then condenses in a separate container, precipitating the distilled elements with the desired magical properties.","The vapor then condenses in a separate container, precipitating the distilled elements with the desired magical properties.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Alembic_003229af_3"
"","","Scales",Neutral,50,"The meat of the slaughterfish is meally and noisome, but dried slaughterfish scales are said by locals to be 'a crunchy treat' when prepared in the native manner.","The meat of the slaughterfish is meally and noisome, but dried slaughterfish scales are said by locals to be 'a crunchy treat' when prepared in the native manner.","MorroDefaultQuest_1scales_00322c44_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Foreigners are advised to beware of slaughterfish scales.","Foreigners are advised to beware of slaughterfish scales.","MorroDefaultQuest_1scales_00322c44_2"
"","","Retort",Neutral,50,"An retort is a vessel with a beaked cap or head used in alchemical processes to transform, purify, or refine raw materials into the sublime substances used in alchemical preparations.","An retort is a vessel with a beaked cap or head used in alchemical processes to transform, purify, or refine raw materials into the sublime substances used in alchemical preparations.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Retort_00322c7c_1"
"","","Bloat",Neutral,50,"Bloat is the thick, pulpy-white tuber of the bloatspore plant. It grows in dark, damp locations.","Bloat is the thick, pulpy-white tuber of the bloatspore plant. It grows in dark, damp locations.","MorroDefaultQuest_1bloat_00322e12_1"
"","","Resin",Neutral,50,"Resins are the tough, soluble substances of vegetable origin used by the Dunmer as glues and stiffeners in the manufacture of their unique chitin and bonemold armors and weapons.","Resins are the tough, soluble substances of vegetable origin used by the Dunmer as glues and stiffeners in the manufacture of their unique chitin and bonemold armors and weapons.","MorroDefaultQuest_1resin_00322d10_1"
"","","Pearl",Neutral,50,"These smooth, round, lustrous beads are prized for ornamental purposes.","These smooth, round, lustrous beads are prized for ornamental purposes.","MorroDefaultQuest_1pearl_00322d12_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The cave collop and other native Morrowind mollusks only occasionally produce pearls; their scarcity increases their market value.","The cave collop and other native Morrowind mollusks only occasionally produce pearls; their scarcity increases their market value.","MorroDefaultQuest_1pearl_00322d12_2"
"","","Muck",Neutral,50,"Muck is the damp, fibrous slime from crushed muckspunge plants that grow in the West Gash and on Azura's Coast.","Muck is the damp, fibrous slime from crushed muckspunge plants that grow in the West Gash and on Azura's Coast.","MorroDefaultQuest_1muck_00322edc_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Unless properly prepared in the native manner, it is mildly toxic.","Unless properly prepared in the native manner, it is mildly toxic.","MorroDefaultQuest_1muck_00322edc_2"
"","","Ruby",Neutral,50,"Rubies are transparent red gems that appear occasionally on the surface and more often in subterranean deposits on Vvardenfell.","Rubies are transparent red gems that appear occasionally on the surface and more often in subterranean deposits on Vvardenfell.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ruby_00322e60_1"
