Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Have you found the Staff of the Silver Dawn?","Have you found the Staff of the Silver Dawn?","fbmwHTAdvancement_GREETING_0000126d_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Do you have the Sload Soap?","Do you have the Sload Soap?","fbmwHTAdvancement_GREETING_0000126e_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I am Arara Uvulas, the Mouth of Master Neloth.","I am Arara Uvulas, the Mouth of Master Neloth.","fbmwHTAdvancement_GREETING_0000126f_1"
"","","Staff of the Silver Dawn",Neutral,50,"You already gave me the Staff of the Silver Dawn.","You already gave me the Staff of the Silver Dawn.","fbmwHTSilverDawn_1StaffSofStheSSilverSDawn_0000127a_1"
"","","Staff of the Silver Dawn",Neutral,50,"Is that the Staff of the Silver Dawn?","Is that the Staff of the Silver Dawn?","fbmwHTSilverDawn_1StaffSofStheSSilverSDawn_00320496_1"
"","","Staff of the Silver Dawn",Neutral,50,"I believe someone in the Mages Guild here is Sadrith Mora has this staff.","I believe someone in the Mages Guild here is Sadrith Mora has this staff.","fbmwHTSilverDawn_1StaffSofStheSSilverSDawn_00001279_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Master Neloth wants the staff, and I cannot leave my duties here long enough to fetch it for him.","Master Neloth wants the staff, and I cannot leave my duties here long enough to fetch it for him.","fbmwHTSilverDawn_1StaffSofStheSSilverSDawn_00001279_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Go to Wolverine Hall, get the staff, and bring it back to me.","Go to Wolverine Hall, get the staff, and bring it back to me.","fbmwHTSilverDawn_1StaffSofStheSSilverSDawn_00001279_3"
"","","Conjuration Expert",Neutral,50,"A mage skilled at Conjuration is adept at summoning otherworldly creatures, including ghosts.","A mage skilled at Conjuration is adept at summoning otherworldly creatures, including ghosts.","fbmwTownSadrith_1ConjurationSexpert_00f8aa63_1"
"","","Telvanni Hortator",Neutral,50,"That's a title given to a special champion and war leader among the Great Houses. Why?","That's a title given to a special champion and war leader among the Great Houses. Why?","fbmwMQ10_1TelvanniSHortator_00025aea_1"
"","","Gateway Haunting",Neutral,50,"I inspected the manifestations in the South Turret bed chamber of the Gateway Inn. I examined the site thoroughly, but I found no evidence of a restless spirit or ancestral influences.","I inspected the manifestations in the South Turret bed chamber of the Gateway Inn. I examined the site thoroughly, but I found no evidence of a restless spirit or ancestral influences.","fbmwTownSadrith_1GatewayShaunting_00f8af39_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The ghost itself is trivial, and easily banished, but I don't know why it reappears, or how to stop the reappearances. I can't be sure, but my experience and intution tells me that a Conjuration expert is involved.","The ghost itself is trivial, and easily banished, but I don't know why it reappears, or how to stop the reappearances. I can't be sure, but my experience and intution tells me that a Conjuration expert is involved.","fbmwTownSadrith_1GatewayShaunting_00f8af39_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"By that, I mean a mage skilled at summoning ghosts. That's all I can tell you.","By that, I mean a mage skilled at summoning ghosts. That's all I can tell you.","fbmwTownSadrith_1GatewayShaunting_00f8af39_3"
"","","Latest Rumors",Neutral,50,"Skink-in-Tree's-Shade seems like a decent sort... for an Argonian. But he has an unhealthy interest in vampires.","Skink-in-Tree's-Shade seems like a decent sort... for an Argonian. But he has an unhealthy interest in vampires.","MorroDefaultQuest_1latestSrumors_00321633_1"
"","","Master Neloth",Neutral,50,"Yes, he is my patron and I represent him on the Telvanni Council. Master Neloth lives in the tower of Tel Naga, here in Sadrith Mora.","Yes, he is my patron and I represent him on the Telvanni Council. Master Neloth lives in the tower of Tel Naga, here in Sadrith Mora.","MorroDefaultQuest_1MasterSNeloth_003217ba_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"What do you want?","What do you want?","MorroDefaultQuest_1MasterSNeloth_003217ba_2"
"","","Sload Soap",Neutral,50,"I have all the sload soap I need right now.","I have all the sload soap I need right now.","fbmwHTSloadSoap_1SloadSSoap_00001278_1"
"","","Sload Soap",Neutral,50,"Do you have the five portions of sload soap?","Do you have the five portions of sload soap?","fbmwHTSloadSoap_1SloadSSoap_00001277_1"
"","","Sload Soap",Neutral,50,"Yes, Master Neloth needs five portions of sload soap to help with his research. Here are 500 drakes.","Yes, Master Neloth needs five portions of sload soap to help with his research. Here are 500 drakes.","fbmwHTSloadSoap_1SloadSSoap_0032237f_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You can keep what is left after you purchase the sload soap.","You can keep what is left after you purchase the sload soap.","fbmwHTSloadSoap_1SloadSSoap_0032237f_2"
"","","Chores",Neutral,50,"I do not have any chores for you. Check with my patron, Master Neloth, or with the other Mouths.","I do not have any chores for you. Check with my patron, Master Neloth, or with the other Mouths.","fbmwHTAdvancement_1chores_00001272_1"
"","","Chores",Neutral,50,"Master Neloth asked me to acquire a Staff of the Silver Dawn and deliver it to him.","Master Neloth asked me to acquire a Staff of the Silver Dawn and deliver it to him.","fbmwHTAdvancement_1chores_00001271_1"
"","","Chores",Neutral,50,"Master Neloth needs five portions of Sload Soap.","Master Neloth needs five portions of Sload Soap.","fbmwHTAdvancement_1chores_00322c01_1"
"","","Patron",Neutral,50,"Master Neloth is not taking on any proteges.","Master Neloth is not taking on any proteges.","fbmwHTAdvancement_1patron_00322b70_1"
"","","Patron",Neutral,50,"I do not think Dratha would agree to be your patron.","I do not think Dratha would agree to be your patron.","fbmwHTAdvancement_1patron_00322b71_1"
"","","Yes, here it is.",Neutral,50,"Good. I hope Master Neloth will be pleased with it. I have this old dagger I no longer use.","Good. I hope Master Neloth will be pleased with it. I have this old dagger I no longer use.","fbmwHTSilverDawn_1StaffSofStheSSilverSDawn1_00322f2e_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And I can teach you to blind your enemies as the staff does.","And I can teach you to blind your enemies as the staff does.","fbmwHTSilverDawn_1StaffSofStheSSilverSDawn1_00322f2e_2"
"","","No.",Neutral,50,"Master Neloth will want the Staff of the Silver Dawn soon, outlander. You should give it to me before Master Neloth becomes less cooperative.","Master Neloth will want the Staff of the Silver Dawn soon, outlander. You should give it to me before Master Neloth becomes less cooperative.","fbmwHTSilverDawn_1StaffSofStheSSilverSDawn2_00322f30_1"
"","","Teach me to blind my enemies.",Neutral,50,"Yes, of course. [Arara teaches you to blind your enemies.] Now, if you'll excuse me...","Yes, of course. [Arara teaches you to blind your enemies.] Now, if you'll excuse me...","fbmwHTSilverDawn_1StaffSofStheSSilverSDawn3_00322f31_1"
"","","No, thank you.",Neutral,50,"Very well. If you want more chores, speak with the other Mouths.","Very well. If you want more chores, speak with the other Mouths.","fbmwHTSilverDawn_1StaffSofStheSSilverSDawn4_00322f32_1"
"","","How is a Hortator chosen?",Neutral,50,"All the Telvanni councilors must vote to choose a Hortator, and the vote must be unanimous. It's an old tradition, rarely used -- never in my lifetime.","All the Telvanni councilors must vote to choose a Hortator, and the vote must be unanimous. It's an old tradition, rarely used -- never in my lifetime.","fbmwMQ10_1TelvanniSHortator1_003230dd_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"A Hortator's duty is to lead a Great House in war, and we haven't had a war in a very long time.","A Hortator's duty is to lead a Great House in war, and we haven't had a war in a very long time.","fbmwMQ10_1TelvanniSHortator1_003230dd_2"
"","","Tell your story and ask to be confirmed as Hortator.",Neutral,50,"I see. Well. It sounds important. You'll have to speak directly to Master Neloth about this.","I see. Well. It sounds important. You'll have to speak directly to Master Neloth about this.","fbmwMQTelvanniNeloth_1TelvanniSHortator2_003230fc_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Tel Naga, Master Neloth's tower, is right in the center of Sadrith Mora.","Tel Naga, Master Neloth's tower, is right in the center of Sadrith Mora.","fbmwMQTelvanniNeloth_1TelvanniSHortator2_003230fc_2"
"","","Yes, here they are.",Neutral,50,"Perhaps these will put Master Neloth in a better mood. He is old, you see, and has trouble moving about.","Perhaps these will put Master Neloth in a better mood. He is old, you see, and has trouble moving about.","fbmwHTSloadSoap_1SloadSSoap1_00323550_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I use the soap along with some roobrush and bonemeal to make an ointment for his joints.","I use the soap along with some roobrush and bonemeal to make an ointment for his joints.","fbmwHTSloadSoap_1SloadSSoap1_00323550_2"
"","","Yes, here they are.",Neutral,50,"I do not appreciate tricks, outlander. Either bring me the sload soap, or...","I do not appreciate tricks, outlander. Either bring me the sload soap, or...","fbmwHTSloadSoap_1SloadSSoap1_00323551_1"
"","","No, not yet.",Neutral,50,"Master Neloth is venerable and patient, but he will not wait forever.","Master Neloth is venerable and patient, but he will not wait forever.","fbmwHTSloadSoap_1SloadSSoap2_00323552_1"
