Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Happy,50,"Well hello there.  You don't look like one of the natives, and I don't recall seeing you on the last ship from Vvardenfell.","Well hello there.  You don't look like one of the natives, and I don't recall seeing you on the last ship from Vvardenfell.","fbmwBMFalmer_GREETING_00f8ac72_1"
"","","",Happy,70,"Perhaps you're a mercenary?  I'm here to do some research, myself.  Please, join me for a drink.","Perhaps you're a mercenary?  I'm here to do some research, myself.  Please, join me for a drink.","fbmwBMFalmer_GREETING_00f8ac72_2"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Hello again.  I'm still looking to hire an explorer, if you're interested.","Hello again.  I'm still looking to hire an explorer, if you're interested.","fbmwBMFalmer_GREETING_00f8ac73_1"
"","","GREETING",Surprise,50,"You've returned.  Have you found any evidence of the Falmer here on Solstheim?","You've returned.  Have you found any evidence of the Falmer here on Solstheim?","fbmwBMFalmer_GREETING_00f8ac74_1"
"","","",Surprise,80,"Hmmm.... Let me see....  No...no...wait...yes!  Oh...hmmm....no....","Hmmm.... Let me see....  No...no...wait...yes!  Oh...hmmm....no....","fbmwBMFalmer_GREETING_00f8ac74_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I'm afraid this isn't what I'm looking for. Please continue your explorations, and do be more certain next time.","I'm afraid this isn't what I'm looking for. Please continue your explorations, and do be more certain next time.","fbmwBMFalmer_GREETING_00f8ac74_3"
"","","GREETING",Surprise,50,"You've returned.  Have you found any evidence of the Falmer here on Solstheim?","You've returned.  Have you found any evidence of the Falmer here on Solstheim?","fbmwBMFalmer_GREETING_00f8ac75_1"
"","","",Surprise,100,"What's this? "Fall of the Snow Prince," you say?  Fascinating.  Let me see it.","What's this? "Fall of the Snow Prince," you say?  Fascinating.  Let me see it.","fbmwBMFalmer_GREETING_00f8ac75_2"
"","","",Happy,100,"Hmmm...yes...yes...amazing!  By my Falmer ancestors, you've done it, friend!","Hmmm...yes...yes...amazing!  By my Falmer ancestors, you've done it, friend!","fbmwBMFalmer_GREETING_00f8ac75_3"
"","","",Happy,100,"The account in this tome is remarkable!  Rieklings indeed!  I don't see how this Snow Prince could have been anything BUT a Falmer, do you?","The account in this tome is remarkable!  Rieklings indeed!  I don't see how this Snow Prince could have been anything BUT a Falmer, do you?","fbmwBMFalmer_GREETING_00f8ac75_4"
"","","",Happy,50,"You're a credit to explorers everywhere, friend.  Here's the gold, as promised, and thank you!","You're a credit to explorers everywhere, friend.  Here's the gold, as promised, and thank you!","fbmwBMFalmer_GREETING_00f8ac75_5"
"","","Hire an Explorer",Happy,60,"Listen, friend...  You seem an able sort. And you did listen politely to my ramblings!  Would you be interested in helping me with my research?","Listen, friend...  You seem an able sort. And you did listen politely to my ramblings!  Would you be interested in helping me with my research?","fbmwBMFalmer_1hireSanSexplorer_00f8ac86_1"
"","","",Happy,50,"I need someone to do a bit of exploring and investigating. I'll pay you, of course, with some gold up front. Are you interested?","I need someone to do a bit of exploring and investigating. I'll pay you, of course, with some gold up front. Are you interested?","fbmwBMFalmer_1hireSanSexplorer_00f8ac86_2"
"","","Hire an Explorer",Neutral,50,"I've already hired an explorer -- you.  Now please get going.  I'm anxious to know what evidence you might find.","I've already hired an explorer -- you.  Now please get going.  I'm anxious to know what evidence you might find.","fbmwBMFalmer_1hireSanSexplorer_00f8ac87_1"
"","","Elven Ancestry",Happy,100,"I have long believed that I, Athellor, have the blood of the Falmer flowing through my veins!  I'm on a journey of self-discovery.","I have long believed that I, Athellor, have the blood of the Falmer flowing through my veins!  I'm on a journey of self-discovery.","fbmwBMFalmer_1ElvenSancestry_00f8ac8c_1"
"","","",Happy,50,"I wish to know who I am, and where I came from.","I wish to know who I am, and where I came from.","fbmwBMFalmer_1ElvenSancestry_00f8ac8c_2"
"","","",Happy,50,"I'm hoping that if I find some evidence of the Falmer's existence, I will better understand myself, and my past.","I'm hoping that if I find some evidence of the Falmer's existence, I will better understand myself, and my past.","fbmwBMFalmer_1ElvenSancestry_00f8ac8c_3"
"","","",Sad,50,"But alas, I'm a noble, not an adventurer.  That's why I've come to this establishment.","But alas, I'm a noble, not an adventurer.  That's why I've come to this establishment.","fbmwBMFalmer_1ElvenSancestry_00f8ac8c_4"
"","","",Happy,50,"I'm hoping to hire an explorer to do some of the more... physical work. Another drink?","I'm hoping to hire an explorer to do some of the more... physical work. Another drink?","fbmwBMFalmer_1ElvenSancestry_00f8ac8c_5"
"","","Elven Ancestry",Happy,50,"I KNOW I have Falmer ancestors.  I can feel the chill Falmer blood coursing through my veins.","I KNOW I have Falmer ancestors.  I can feel the chill Falmer blood coursing through my veins.","fbmwBMFalmer_1ElvenSancestry_00f8ac8d_1"
"","","",Happy,50,"That's why I'm in this bar.  I need to hire an explorer to seek out the evidence I need.","That's why I'm in this bar.  I need to hire an explorer to seek out the evidence I need.","fbmwBMFalmer_1ElvenSancestry_00f8ac8d_2"
"","","Some Research",Happy,50,"Yes, research on the Falmer.  Some call them Snow Elves, though I find that designation a gross oversimplification.","Yes, research on the Falmer.  Some call them Snow Elves, though I find that designation a gross oversimplification.","fbmwBMFalmer_1someSresearch_00f8ac92_1"
"","","",Happy,30,"You see, according to Nord legend, the Falmer are an elusive race of Elves who dwell in cold, remote regions.","You see, according to Nord legend, the Falmer are an elusive race of Elves who dwell in cold, remote regions.","fbmwBMFalmer_1someSresearch_00f8ac92_2"
"","","",Disgust,50,"They're usually blamed for any number of disasters -- blizzards, missing children, you name it.","They're usually blamed for any number of disasters -- blizzards, missing children, you name it.","fbmwBMFalmer_1someSresearch_00f8ac92_3"
"","","",Disgust,80,"The locals think those vile Riekling ice creatures are the Falmer of legend, an insulting and absurd notion if ever there was one.","The locals think those vile Riekling ice creatures are the Falmer of legend, an insulting and absurd notion if ever there was one.","fbmwBMFalmer_1someSresearch_00f8ac92_4"
"","","",Happy,100,"Here, please, have another drink...","Here, please, have another drink...","fbmwBMFalmer_1someSresearch_00f8ac92_5"
"","","Some Research",Happy,50,"Yes, I'm here on Solstheim doing some research on the Falmer.","Yes, I'm here on Solstheim doing some research on the Falmer.","fbmwBMFalmer_1someSresearch_00f8ac93_1"
"","","",Disgust,50,"The locals think the legendary Falmer are actually the Rieklings, those hideous little ice creatures that inhabit the island. What an absurd notion.","The locals think the legendary Falmer are actually the Rieklings, those hideous little ice creatures that inhabit the island. What an absurd notion.","fbmwBMFalmer_1someSresearch_00f8ac93_2"
"","","Absurd Notion",Neutral,50,"The Rieklings?  The Snow Elves of legend?  Preposterous.  You see, I believe the Falmer REALLY existed, centuries ago.","The Rieklings?  The Snow Elves of legend?  Preposterous.  You see, I believe the Falmer REALLY existed, centuries ago.","fbmwBMFalmer_1absurdSnotion_00aabec5_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"They were Elves, just like the Altmer, Dunmer or Bosmer. Then...they just faded away.","They were Elves, just like the Altmer, Dunmer or Bosmer. Then...they just faded away.","fbmwBMFalmer_1absurdSnotion_00aabec5_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"They bred with the other Elven races, and ceased to exist as an identifiable culture.","They bred with the other Elven races, and ceased to exist as an identifiable culture.","fbmwBMFalmer_1absurdSnotion_00aabec5_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"It's very likely that the Falmer are an important part of Elven ancestry.  My friend, your glass is almost emptttyyyyy....","It's very likely that the Falmer are an important part of Elven ancestry.  My friend, your glass is almost emptttyyyyy....","fbmwBMFalmer_1absurdSnotion_00aabec5_4"
"","","Absurd Notion",Neutral,50,"The mere suggestion that the Falmer are no more than the Rieklings is ridiculous.","The mere suggestion that the Falmer are no more than the Rieklings is ridiculous.","fbmwBMFalmer_1absurdSnotion_00aabec4_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The Falmer WERE a real race, until they intermingled with the other Elven races.","The Falmer WERE a real race, until they intermingled with the other Elven races.","fbmwBMFalmer_1absurdSnotion_00aabec4_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"It's quite clear to me that the Falmer are an important piece in the puzzle that is Elven Ancestry.","It's quite clear to me that the Falmer are an important piece in the puzzle that is Elven Ancestry.","fbmwBMFalmer_1absurdSnotion_00aabec4_3"
