Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Ah, my friend. How may I be of service to you?","Ah, my friend. How may I be of service to you?","fbmwFGCorprusStalker_GREETING_00f886d4_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Are you here to get rid of the Corprus Stalker?","Are you here to get rid of the Corprus Stalker?","fbmwMSGreetings_GREETING_00f8d276_1"
"","","ServiceRefusal",Neutral,50,"I can't buy or sell anything with a Corprus Stalker on the loose!","I can't buy or sell anything with a Corprus Stalker on the loose!","MorroDefaultQuest_ServiceRefusal_00f8d07f_1"
"","","Girith's Guar Hides",Neutral,50,"Thank you again for helping us out with that Ashlander business.","Thank you again for helping us out with that Ashlander business.","fbmwMVOutcastAshlanders_1GirithAsSguarShides_00f8a2ad_1"
"","","Girith's Guar Hides",Neutral,50,"Ahhh...my old friend Girith! I heard you helped him out of some serious trouble not long ago. Some business with a couple of no-good Ashlanders, right?","Ahhh...my old friend Girith! I heard you helped him out of some serious trouble not long ago. Some business with a couple of no-good Ashlanders, right?","fbmwMVOutcastAshlanders_1GirithAsSguarShides_00f8a2ae_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"They'll never learn. Anyway, you have my thanks; I had quite an investment in those guar hides. Would have taken quite a beating had Girith not been had not been able to sell them.","They'll never learn. Anyway, you have my thanks; I had quite an investment in those guar hides. Would have taken quite a beating had Girith not been had not been able to sell them.","fbmwMVOutcastAshlanders_1GirithAsSguarShides_00f8a2ae_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Here, take these as a token of our appreciation.","Here, take these as a token of our appreciation.","fbmwMVOutcastAshlanders_1GirithAsSguarShides_00f8a2ae_3"
"","","Corprus Stalker",Neutral,50,"Aren't you finished yet? Didn't you say you'd kill it for me?","Aren't you finished yet? Didn't you say you'd kill it for me?","fbmwFGCorprusStalker_1CorprusSStalker_00f8a430_1"
"","","Corprus Stalker",Neutral,50,"Thanks for dispatching that Corprus Stalker. You obviously have great skill.","Thanks for dispatching that Corprus Stalker. You obviously have great skill.","fbmwFGCorprusStalker_1CorprusSStalker_00f8a431_1"
"","","Corprus Stalker",Neutral,50,"Thanks for dispatching that Corprus Stalker. You obviously have great skill.","Thanks for dispatching that Corprus Stalker. You obviously have great skill.","fbmwFGCorprusStalker_1CorprusSStalker_00f8a432_1"
"","","Corprus Stalker",Neutral,50,"We were able to trap it upstairs, but no one wants to risk disease by getting close to it. Normally Master Aryon would take care of it, but he's been so busy recently.","We were able to trap it upstairs, but no one wants to risk disease by getting close to it. Normally Master Aryon would take care of it, but he's been so busy recently.","fbmwFGCorprusStalker_1CorprusSStalker_00f8a433_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Please hurry. It's wrecking my shop!","Please hurry. It's wrecking my shop!","fbmwFGCorprusStalker_1CorprusSStalker_00f8a433_2"
"","","Corprus Stalker",Neutral,50,"We were able to trap it upstairs, but no one wants to risk disease by getting close to it. Normally Master Aryon would take care of it, but he's been so busy recently.","We were able to trap it upstairs, but no one wants to risk disease by getting close to it. Normally Master Aryon would take care of it, but he's been so busy recently.","fbmwFGCorprusStalker_1CorprusSStalker_00f8a434_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Are you saying that you're up to the challenge?","Are you saying that you're up to the challenge?","fbmwFGCorprusStalker_1CorprusSStalker_00f8a434_2"
"","","Yes, I am.",Neutral,50,"Excellent! Have at it! But be careful!","Excellent! Have at it! But be careful!","fbmwFGCorprusStalker_fbmwfgberwenyes_00f8a97c_1"
"","","No, sorry.",Neutral,50,"Then leave now. It's not safe here with that thing on the loose!","Then leave now. It's not safe here with that thing on the loose!","fbmwFGCorprusStalker_fbmwfgberwenno_00f8a97e_1"
