Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Bivale Teneran",Neutral,50,"I am Bivale Teneran. How may I help you?","I am Bivale Teneran. How may I help you?","fbmwHHIndEsp3_1BivaleSTeneran_00321535_1"
"","","Rasha's Shirts",Neutral,50,"Thank you again. Rasha does do good work, does he not?","Thank you again. Rasha does do good work, does he not?","fbmwVTraderLate_1RashaAsSshirts_003212fd_1"
"","","Rasha's Shirts",Neutral,50,"Ah...you've brought the shirts from Rasha. Wonderful! He does such fine work, and he sells them to me for very reasonable prices.","Ah...you've brought the shirts from Rasha. Wonderful! He does such fine work, and he sells them to me for very reasonable prices.","fbmwVTraderLate_1RashaAsSshirts_00f8af3f_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"He's a careful sort, but that's just smart business if you ask me. Thank you for your help, and here's your payment.","He's a careful sort, but that's just smart business if you ask me. Thank you for your help, and here's your payment.","fbmwVTraderLate_1RashaAsSshirts_00f8af3f_2"
"","","Rasha's Shirts",Neutral,50,"Do you not have the shirts, friend? I can see you are oath-bound to Zenithar to deliver them. You had better recover them and deliver them to me.","Do you not have the shirts, friend? I can see you are oath-bound to Zenithar to deliver them. You had better recover them and deliver them to me.","fbmwVTraderLate_1RashaAsSshirts_00f8af40_1"
"","","Ienas Sarandas",Neutral,50,"The young fellow's family has lived in Ald'ruhn a long time. His parents died recently and left him their house and estate.","The young fellow's family has lived in Ald'ruhn a long time. His parents died recently and left him their house and estate.","MorroDefaultQuest_1IenasSSarandas_00321369_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But Ienas has fallen in with a fast crowd. I believe he's taken to drinking expensive liquor and has incurred some gambling debts.","But Ienas has fallen in with a fast crowd. I believe he's taken to drinking expensive liquor and has incurred some gambling debts.","MorroDefaultQuest_1IenasSSarandas_00321369_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"He's a charming lad, everyone likes him, but he's not very sensible, and suddenly becoming rich seems to have made him an irresponsible fool.","He's a charming lad, everyone likes him, but he's not very sensible, and suddenly becoming rich seems to have made him an irresponsible fool.","MorroDefaultQuest_1IenasSSarandas_00321369_3"
"","","My Trade",Neutral,50,"I am a clothier. I make clothes and sell them. Of course. I make clothes with style and distinction.","I am a clothier. I make clothes and sell them. Of course. I make clothes with style and distinction.","MorroDefaultQuest_1myStrade_00322789_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"My clients are either discerning nobles or merchants or commoners with exceptional taste... and financial resources.","My clients are either discerning nobles or merchants or commoners with exceptional taste... and financial resources.","MorroDefaultQuest_1myStrade_00322789_2"
"","","Scroll",Neutral,50,"You gave me the scroll already, outlander.","You gave me the scroll already, outlander.","fbmwHHIndEsp3_1scroll_00005455_1"
"","","Scroll",Neutral,50,"Well, are you going to give me the scroll or not?","Well, are you going to give me the scroll or not?","fbmwHHIndEsp3_1scroll_00005456_1"
"","","Work",Neutral,50,"You've been paid.","You've been paid.","fbmwTownAldBivale_1work_00f0a389_1"
"","","Work",Anger,50,"I see you have the brocade shirt and silk pants from Ienas Sarandas. And I hear Ienas Sarandas was found dead in his home.","I see you have the brocade shirt and silk pants from Ienas Sarandas. And I hear Ienas Sarandas was found dead in his home.","fbmwTownAldBivale_1work_00f0a38a_1"
"","","",Anger,40,"I don't suppose YOU had anything to do with that? Here's the 50 drakes I promised you. And I'll take the goods. ","I don't suppose YOU had anything to do with that? Here's the 50 drakes I promised you. And I'll take the goods.","fbmwTownAldBivale_1work_00f0a38a_2"
"","","",Anger,50,"But don't expect me to thank you for them. No debt is worth a man's life. Of course, there were no witnesses.","But don't expect me to thank you for them. No debt is worth a man's life. Of course, there were no witnesses.","fbmwTownAldBivale_1work_00f0a38a_3"
"","","",Anger,70,"But everyone knows you killed that poor fool. Don't think anyone here will forgive you for that.","But everyone knows you killed that poor fool. Don't think anyone here will forgive you for that.","fbmwTownAldBivale_1work_00f0a38a_4"
"","","Work",Happy,50,"Thank you again. You handled the affair very well.","Thank you again. You handled the affair very well.","fbmwTownAldBivale_1work_00f0a38b_1"
"","","Work",Happy,50,"I see you have the brocade shirt and silk pants from Ienas Sarandas. Here are the 50 drakes for your services. ","I see you have the brocade shirt and silk pants from Ienas Sarandas. Here are the 50 drakes for your services.","fbmwTownAldBivale_1work_00f0a38c_1"
"","","",Happy,40,"And thank you very much for handling this situation so well. I really appreciate it.","And thank you very much for handling this situation so well. I really appreciate it.","fbmwTownAldBivale_1work_00f0a38c_2"
"","","Work",Neutral,50,"Thank you again.","Thank you again.","fbmwTownAldBivale_1work_00f0a38d_1"
"","","Work",Happy,50,"I see you have the brocade shirt and silk pants from Ienas Sarandas. Here are the 50 drakes for your services. Thank you very much.","I see you have the brocade shirt and silk pants from Ienas Sarandas. Here are the 50 drakes for your services. Thank you very much.","fbmwTownAldBivale_1work_00f0a38e_1"
"","","Work",Neutral,50,"I made a brocade shirt and silk pants for Ienas Sarandas.","I made a brocade shirt and silk pants for Ienas Sarandas.","fbmwTownAldBivale_1work_00322ea0_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"He gave me half-payment on account, and said he'd pay me the rest later, but it's been weeks, and I have my own bills to pay.","He gave me half-payment on account, and said he'd pay me the rest later, but it's been weeks, and I have my own bills to pay.","fbmwTownAldBivale_1work_00322ea0_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Find Ienas Sarandas, get the overdue payment of 360 drakes he owes me, or get the shirt and pants and bring them back to me, and I'll give you 50 drakes for your services.","Find Ienas Sarandas, get the overdue payment of 360 drakes he owes me, or get the shirt and pants and bring them back to me, and I'll give you 50 drakes for your services.","fbmwTownAldBivale_1work_00322ea0_3"
"","","Give her the scroll.",Neutral,50,"Yes, as I expected. Tell Nileno Dorvayn that I received the scroll and understood the message.","Yes, as I expected. Tell Nileno Dorvayn that I received the scroll and understood the message.","fbmwHHIndEsp3_1scroll1_00323625_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Why not take this outfit? A present for my efficient courier.","Why not take this outfit? A present for my efficient courier.","fbmwHHIndEsp3_1scroll1_00323625_2"
"","","Give her the scroll.",Neutral,50,"Yes, as I expected. Tell Nileno Dorvayn that I received the scroll and understood the message.","Yes, as I expected. Tell Nileno Dorvayn that I received the scroll and understood the message.","fbmwHHIndEsp3_1scroll1_00006071_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Why not take this outfit? A present for my efficient courier.","Why not take this outfit? A present for my efficient courier.","fbmwHHIndEsp3_1scroll1_00006071_2"
"","","Keep the scroll.",Neutral,50,"I'm sorry. I must have mistaken you for someone else. What are you hear for? A new shirt? How about this one?","I'm sorry. I must have mistaken you for someone else. What are you hear for? A new shirt? How about this one?","fbmwHHIndEsp3_1scroll2_00323626_1"
