Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I will wait here and guard the gate. Good luck, my friend.","I will wait here and guard the gate. Good luck, my friend.","fbmwBMWildHunt_GREETING_00f8b8d3_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Wait, my friend. I can go not further. This contest can have only one victor, and you will have to be the one. Perhaps if you are able to escape, I will find my way out in time. ","Wait, my friend. I can go not further. This contest can have only one victor, and you will have to be the one. Perhaps if you are able to escape, I will find my way out in time.","fbmwBMWildHunt_GREETING_00f8b8d4_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"For now, I will guard this gate and make sure none of the beasts follow you through. Take care if you encounter the others. Karstaag is a wild creature, and will certainly try to kill you.","For now, I will guard this gate and make sure none of the beasts follow you through. Take care if you encounter the others. Karstaag is a wild creature, and will certainly try to kill you.","fbmwBMWildHunt_GREETING_00f8b8d4_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Heart-Fang worries me...there is something wild in his eyes that I do not trust. Good luck.","Heart-Fang worries me...there is something wild in his eyes that I do not trust. Good luck.","fbmwBMWildHunt_GREETING_00f8b8d4_3"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Let us continue through this maze.","Let us continue through this maze.","fbmwBMWildHunt_GREETING_00f8b8d5_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"You! Do not think that I cannot see through the form you now wear. I am sorry it must come to this. I had thought better of you. It is clear, though, that you have joined with these dark forces. Killing you will be an act of mercy.","You! Do not think that I cannot see through the form you now wear. I am sorry it must come to this. I had thought better of you. It is clear, though, that you have joined with these dark forces. Killing you will be an act of mercy.","fbmwBMWildHunt_GREETING_00f8b8d6_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"It is you! I am sorry you, too, have been brought to play in this nefarious game. Since the werewolves captured me at the fort, I have been held here by this demon Hircine. Soon, others joined me:","It is you! I am sorry you, too, have been brought to play in this nefarious game. Since the werewolves captured me at the fort, I have been held here by this demon Hircine. Soon, others joined me:","fbmwBMWildHunt_GREETING_00f8b8d7_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"one of the Nords, named Heart-Fang, along with a beast named Karstaag. I believe the only hope for escape is to find our way through this maze.","one of the Nords, named Heart-Fang, along with a beast named Karstaag. I believe the only hope for escape is to find our way through this maze.","fbmwBMWildHunt_GREETING_00f8b8d7_2"
"","","Captain Carius",Neutral,50,"I am Captain Falx Carius, commander of Fort Frostmoth.","I am Captain Falx Carius, commander of Fort Frostmoth.","MorroDefaultQuest_1CaptainSCarius_00321570_1"
"","","Find our way",Neutral,50,"I believe we can find our way out of this demon realm.","I believe we can find our way out of this demon realm.","fbmwBMWildHunt_1findSourSway_00f8bb19_1"
"","","Find our way",Neutral,50,"That is what the demon told me. We are to fight our way through this maze, which is hunted by the werewolves the demon calls his Hounds. I am weak, my friend, and have been here for too long. Perhaps together, we can find our way to safety.","That is what the demon told me. We are to fight our way through this maze, which is hunted by the werewolves the demon calls his Hounds. I am weak, my friend, and have been here for too long. Perhaps together, we can find our way to safety.","fbmwBMWildHunt_1findSourSway_00f8bb1a_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"We must find the key to allow us through the gate in the center of this maze.","We must find the key to allow us through the gate in the center of this maze.","fbmwBMWildHunt_1findSourSway_00f8bb1a_2"
"","","Let us go together.",Neutral,50,"I am glad for your companionship. Together we will fight our way through these demon hordes and escape this evil prison. There is a door in the center of this maze, but we will need a key to enter.","I am glad for your companionship. Together we will fight our way through these demon hordes and escape this evil prison. There is a door in the center of this maze, but we will need a key to enter.","fbmwBMWildHunt_fbmwbmWildHuntCapnGood_00f8bc70_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Let us go find this key and leave this place.","Let us go find this key and leave this place.","fbmwBMWildHunt_fbmwbmWildHuntCapnGood_00f8bc70_2"
"","","Only one can survive. It'll be me.",Neutral,50,"I cannot believe this! Your mind has been clouded by these demons! I am sorry to have to fight you, for I thought you a friend. If this is how it must be, I wish you an honorable death.","I cannot believe this! Your mind has been clouded by these demons! I am sorry to have to fight you, for I thought you a friend. If this is how it must be, I wish you an honorable death.","fbmwBMWildHunt_fbmwbmWildHuntCapnEvil_00f8bc72_1"
