Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Latest Rumors",Neutral,50,"Mistress Dratha has been looking for something called a "Flesh Amulet." I heard Master Neloth is keeping it from her, to try and get some concession on the Council.","Mistress Dratha has been looking for something called a "Flesh Amulet." I heard Master Neloth is keeping it from her, to try and get some concession on the Council.","MorroDefaultQuest_1latestSrumors_0032163c_1"
