Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"You! Defend yourself!","You! Defend yourself!","fbmwICRich_GREETING_0002a4de_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"We have nothing to discuss. Excuse me.","We have nothing to discuss. Excuse me.","fbmwICRich_GREETING_0002a4dd_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I said I was busy. Perhaps you are hard of hearing?","I said I was busy. Perhaps you are hard of hearing?","fbmwICRich_GREETING_0002a4dc_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I am Cunius Pelelius, a principal and charter-holder of the Caldera Mining Company.","I am Cunius Pelelius, a principal and charter-holder of the Caldera Mining Company.","fbmwICRich_GREETING_000100f0_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I cannot imagine why someone like you should think you have business with me, but I will listen, if you can be brief and polite.","I cannot imagine why someone like you should think you have business with me, but I will listen, if you can be brief and polite.","fbmwICRich_GREETING_000100f0_2"
"","","Evidence of Corruption",Neutral,50,"I gave you the key. I'm risking my job here, if not my life. What more do you want?","I gave you the key. I'm risking my job here, if not my life. What more do you want?","fbmwHRCalderaCorrupt_1evidenceSofScorruption_003205e0_1"
"","","Evidence of Corruption",Neutral,50,"All right, all right. I'll tell you this because I trust you. Take this key. There's a record book in Odral's Helvi chest on the second floor.","All right, all right. I'll tell you this because I trust you. Take this key. There's a record book in Odral's Helvi chest on the second floor.","fbmwHRCalderaCorrupt_1evidenceSofScorruption_003205e1_1"
"","","",Fear,50,"Stendarr have mercy on me if anyone finds out about this.","Stendarr have mercy on me if anyone finds out about this.","fbmwHRCalderaCorrupt_1evidenceSofScorruption_003205e1_2"
"","","Evidence of Corruption",Neutral,50,"What are you suggesting?","What are you suggesting?","fbmwHRCalderaCorrupt_1evidenceSofScorruption_003205e2_1"
"","","Donate 500 Drakes",Neutral,50,"I don't know what you're talking about. I have reliable information indicating that you are no longer involved in this matter in any official capacity.","I don't know what you're talking about. I have reliable information indicating that you are no longer involved in this matter in any official capacity.","fbmwICRich_1donateS500Sdrakes_00f8a395_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Leave me immediately. Or I shall be forced to conclude that your intentions are criminal.","Leave me immediately. Or I shall be forced to conclude that your intentions are criminal.","fbmwICRich_1donateS500Sdrakes_00f8a395_2"
"","","Donate 500 Drakes",Neutral,50,"Our business is concluded. You will leave me in peace.","Our business is concluded. You will leave me in peace.","fbmwICRich_1donateS500Sdrakes_00f8a396_1"
"","","Donate 500 Drakes",Neutral,50,"I am busy. Excuse me.","I am busy. Excuse me.","fbmwICRich_1donateS500Sdrakes_00f8a397_1"
"","","Donate 500 Drakes",Neutral,50,"Yes. I recall speaking with someone about a donation to the Widows and Orphans Fund. I am very busy at the moment, but I would be happy to discuss this matter at a later date. Now, if you'll excuse me?","Yes. I recall speaking with someone about a donation to the Widows and Orphans Fund. I am very busy at the moment, but I would be happy to discuss this matter at a later date. Now, if you'll excuse me?","fbmwICRich_1donateS500Sdrakes_00f8a398_1"
"","","Cunius Pelelius",Neutral,50,"Yes. I am Cunius Pelelius.","Yes. I am Cunius Pelelius.","fbmwICRich_1CuniusSPelelius_00321071_1"
"","","Demand the money he promised.",Neutral,50,"You impertinent hound! Do you doubt my honor? Defend yourself, knave!","You impertinent hound! Do you doubt my honor? Defend yourself, knave!","fbmwICRich_fbmwicrichdemand_00f8a9ec_1"
"","","Press him for a commitment.",Neutral,50,"Your views are unwelcome, ser. I have said I will be happy to discuss this matter at a later date. We will not discuss this further.","Your views are unwelcome, ser. I have said I will be happy to discuss this matter at a later date. We will not discuss this further.","fbmwICRich_fbmwicrichpress_00f8a9ee_1"
"","","Thank him for his attention.",Neutral,50,"Thank me? What for? Are you still here?","Thank me? What for? Are you still here?","fbmwICRich_fbmwicrichthank_00f8a9f0_1"
"","","Threaten to reveal his smuggling.",Neutral,50,"You are a fool to listen to idle rumor, and a greater fool to confront me with it. Leave me, ser.","You are a fool to listen to idle rumor, and a greater fool to confront me with it. Leave me, ser.","fbmwICRich_fbmwicrichebony_00f8a9f2_1"
"","","Show him the Secret Caldera Ledger.",Neutral,50,"This is most awkward. Since you confront me with this, I presume you intend blackmail? If you hope for cash, I must disappoint you -- I have no ready cash at present.","This is most awkward. Since you confront me with this, I presume you intend blackmail? If you hope for cash, I must disappoint you -- I have no ready cash at present.","fbmwICRich_fbmwicledger_00f8a9f4_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You must content yourself with these pieces of raw ebony. I'm sure you can get your 500 drakes for them... and more. Now, leave me.","You must content yourself with these pieces of raw ebony. I'm sure you can get your 500 drakes for them... and more. Now, leave me.","fbmwICRich_fbmwicledger_00f8a9f4_2"
"","","Threaten with a slave's testimony.",Neutral,50,"This is most awkward. Since you confront me with this, I presume you intend blackmail? If you hope for cash, I must disappoint you -- I have no ready cash at present.","This is most awkward. Since you confront me with this, I presume you intend blackmail? If you hope for cash, I must disappoint you -- I have no ready cash at present.","fbmwICRich_fbmwicrichslave_00f8a9f6_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You must content yourself with these pieces of raw ebony. I'm sure you can get your 500 drakes for them... and more. Now, leave me.","You must content yourself with these pieces of raw ebony. I'm sure you can get your 500 drakes for them... and more. Now, leave me.","fbmwICRich_fbmwicrichslave_00f8a9f6_2"
