Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"Ash Ghoul","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"The Sixth House greets you, Lord Nerevar. I am known as Dagoth Gares, priest of Ilunibi Shrine, and minister to Sixth House servants.","The Sixth House greets you, Lord Nerevar. I am known as Dagoth Gares, priest of Ilunibi Shrine, and minister to Sixth House servants.","fbmwMQ07_GREETING_0001fa98_1"
"Ash Ghoul","","",Neutral,50,"My Lord, Dagoth Ur, has informed me of your coming. I wish that this time you had come to honor your Lord's friendship, not to betray it.","My Lord, Dagoth Ur, has informed me of your coming. I wish that this time you had come to honor your Lord's friendship, not to betray it.","fbmwMQ07_GREETING_0001fa98_2"
"Ash Ghoul","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Yes, Lord Nerevar? What would you ask of me? Would you hear of my Lord, Dagoth Ur? Or of the Sixth House, or of Sixth House servants?","Yes, Lord Nerevar? What would you ask of me? Would you hear of my Lord, Dagoth Ur? Or of the Sixth House, or of Sixth House servants?","fbmwMQ07_GREETING_0001fa99_1"
"Ash Ghoul","","Sixth House Servants",Neutral,50,"Forgive the rude welcome, but until you have declared for us, we must treat you as our enemy.","Forgive the rude welcome, but until you have declared for us, we must treat you as our enemy.","fbmwMQ07_1SixthSHouseSservants_00aafa97_1"
"Ash Ghoul","","",Neutral,50,"The Sleepers and Dreamers are newly come to Lord Dagoth, and not yet blessed with his power.","The Sleepers and Dreamers are newly come to Lord Dagoth, and not yet blessed with his power.","fbmwMQ07_1SixthSHouseSservants_00aafa97_2"
"Ash Ghoul","","",Neutral,50,"But the Children of His Flesh, they are deep in the heart of his mysteries.","But the Children of His Flesh, they are deep in the heart of his mysteries.","fbmwMQ07_1SixthSHouseSservants_00aafa97_3"
"Ash Ghoul","","",Neutral,50,"Their bodies swell to contain his glory, and to yield the rich sacraments of our Lord's feasts.","Their bodies swell to contain his glory, and to yield the rich sacraments of our Lord's feasts.","fbmwMQ07_1SixthSHouseSservants_00aafa97_4"
"Ash Ghoul","","",Neutral,50,"And we are the least of his servants, for Ash Poets, Ascended Sleepers, and Ash Vampires stand high above us in the Lord's bountiful grace.","And we are the least of his servants, for Ash Poets, Ascended Sleepers, and Ash Vampires stand high above us in the Lord's bountiful grace.","fbmwMQ07_1SixthSHouseSservants_00aafa97_5"
"Ash Ghoul","","Lord's Friendship",Neutral,50,"Lord Dagoth gives me these words to say to you, so you may give them thought. 'Once we were friends and brothers, Lord Nerevar, in peace and in war.'","Lord Dagoth gives me these words to say to you, so you may give them thought. 'Once we were friends and brothers, Lord Nerevar, in peace and in war.'","fbmwMQ07_1LordAsSfriendship_00aafa94_1"
"Ash Ghoul","","",Neutral,50,"'Yet beneath Red Mountain, you struck me down as I guarded the treasure you bound me by oath to defend.'","'Yet beneath Red Mountain, you struck me down as I guarded the treasure you bound me by oath to defend.'","fbmwMQ07_1LordAsSfriendship_00aafa94_2"
"Ash Ghoul","","",Neutral,50,"'But, remembering our old friendship, I would forgive you, and raise you high in my service.'","'But, remembering our old friendship, I would forgive you, and raise you high in my service.'","fbmwMQ07_1LordAsSfriendship_00aafa94_3"
"Ash Ghoul","","",Neutral,50,"My Lord Dagoth bids you come to Red Mountain.","My Lord Dagoth bids you come to Red Mountain.","fbmwMQ07_1LordAsSfriendship_00aafa94_4"
"Ash Ghoul","","",Neutral,50,"For the friendship and honor that once you shared, he would grant you counsel and power, if only you would pledge that friendship anew.","For the friendship and honor that once you shared, he would grant you counsel and power, if only you would pledge that friendship anew.","fbmwMQ07_1LordAsSfriendship_00aafa94_5"
"Ash Ghoul","","",Neutral,50,"I am not your Lord Dagoth, yet I, too, would say to you... Do you come with weapons to strike me down?","I am not your Lord Dagoth, yet I, too, would say to you... Do you come with weapons to strike me down?","fbmwMQ07_1LordAsSfriendship_00aafa94_6"
"Ash Ghoul","","",Neutral,50,"Or would you put away your weapon, and join me in friendship?","Or would you put away your weapon, and join me in friendship?","fbmwMQ07_1LordAsSfriendship_00aafa94_7"
"Ash Ghoul","","Ilunibi Shrine",Neutral,50,"Ilunibi shrine is just a small, quiet retreat for Sixth House servants, a place to contemplate and grow strong and wise in Lord Dagoth's ways.","Ilunibi shrine is just a small, quiet retreat for Sixth House servants, a place to contemplate and grow strong and wise in Lord Dagoth's ways.","fbmwMQ07_1IlunibiSshrine_00aafa93_1"
"Ash Ghoul","","",Neutral,50,"Here we share the sacraments of flesh and blood, and dream the dreams of our Lord.","Here we share the sacraments of flesh and blood, and dream the dreams of our Lord.","fbmwMQ07_1IlunibiSshrine_00aafa93_2"
"Ash Ghoul","","",Neutral,50,"This and other lesser shrines are hidden from prying eyes throughout the land.","This and other lesser shrines are hidden from prying eyes throughout the land.","fbmwMQ07_1IlunibiSshrine_00aafa93_3"
"Ash Ghoul","","",Neutral,50,"But the greatest shrines of Sixth House servants lie beneath Red Mountain, in the citadels of our Lord and his close kin.","But the greatest shrines of Sixth House servants lie beneath Red Mountain, in the citadels of our Lord and his close kin.","fbmwMQ07_1IlunibiSshrine_00aafa93_4"
"Ash Ghoul","","Sixth House",Neutral,50,"The Sixth House was not dead, but only sleeping.","The Sixth House was not dead, but only sleeping.","fbmwMQ07_1SixthSHouse_0001fa96_1"
"Ash Ghoul","","",Neutral,50,"Now it wakes from its long dream, and with its Lord, Dagoth Ur, it comes forth to free Morrowind of foreign rulers and divine pretenders.","Now it wakes from its long dream, and with its Lord, Dagoth Ur, it comes forth to free Morrowind of foreign rulers and divine pretenders.","fbmwMQ07_1SixthSHouse_0001fa96_2"
"Ash Ghoul","","",Neutral,50,"When the land is swept clean of false friends and greedy thieves, the children of Veloth will build anew a garden of plenty in this blighted wasteland.","When the land is swept clean of false friends and greedy thieves, the children of Veloth will build anew a garden of plenty in this blighted wasteland.","fbmwMQ07_1SixthSHouse_0001fa96_3"
"Ash Ghoul","","Dagoth Ur",Neutral,50,"Dagoth Ur is the Awakened Lord of the Sixth House, come to cast down false gods, drive foreigners from the land, and restore the ancient glory of Morrowind.","Dagoth Ur is the Awakened Lord of the Sixth House, come to cast down false gods, drive foreigners from the land, and restore the ancient glory of Morrowind.","fbmwMQ07_1DagothSUr_0001fa92_1"
"Ash Ghoul","","",Neutral,50,"He bids you come to Red Mountain.","He bids you come to Red Mountain.","fbmwMQ07_1DagothSUr_0001fa92_2"
"Ash Ghoul","","",Neutral,50,"For the friendship and honor that once you shared, he would grant you counsel and power, if only you would pledge that friendship anew.","For the friendship and honor that once you shared, he would grant you counsel and power, if only you would pledge that friendship anew.","fbmwMQ07_1DagothSUr_0001fa92_3"
"Ash Ghoul","","",Neutral,50,"The path to Red Mountain is long, and filled with danger, but if you are worthy, you will find there wisdom, a firm friend, and all the power you need to set the world aright.","The path to Red Mountain is long, and filled with danger, but if you are worthy, you will find there wisdom, a firm friend, and all the power you need to set the world aright.","fbmwMQ07_1DagothSUr_0001fa92_4"
"Ash Ghoul","","Our Enemy",Neutral,50,"Lord Dagoth would far rather have you as a friend than as an enemy.","Lord Dagoth would far rather have you as a friend than as an enemy.","fbmwMQ07_1ourSenemy_00aafa95_1"
"Ash Ghoul","","",Neutral,50,"But until you submit to him, Sixth House servants will treat you as an enemy, and try to destroy you.","But until you submit to him, Sixth House servants will treat you as an enemy, and try to destroy you.","fbmwMQ07_1ourSenemy_00aafa95_2"
"Ash Ghoul","","",Neutral,50,"If you wish to be our friend, first you must go to Lord Dagoth in his citadel on Red Mountain, and make your submission.","If you wish to be our friend, first you must go to Lord Dagoth in his citadel on Red Mountain, and make your submission.","fbmwMQ07_1ourSenemy_00aafa95_3"
