Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Do you plan to serve me again, Darkling?","Do you plan to serve me again, Darkling?","MorroDefaultQuest_GREETING_0000a256_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"You try my patience, accident.","You try my patience, accident.","MorroDefaultQuest_GREETING_0000a98a_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"What is it, little monster? How does an abomination such as you plan to serve me?","What is it, little monster? How does an abomination such as you plan to serve me?","MorroDefaultQuest_GREETING_0000a98b_1"
"","","Plan to serve me",Neutral,50,"You? An unfortunate accident perpetrated by one of my kind? Hmmm...you are expendable enough, so may be of use.","You? An unfortunate accident perpetrated by one of my kind? Hmmm...you are expendable enough, so may be of use.","fbmwVAVampChild_1planStoSserveSme_00f8ad55_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I have some questions about my past I need answered, and you might be fit to get this information. Answers about my family.","I have some questions about my past I need answered, and you might be fit to get this information. Answers about my family.","fbmwVAVampChild_1planStoSserveSme_00f8ad55_2"
"","","Plan to serve me",Neutral,50,"You try my patience, but I suppose I can make further use of you. You are expendable after all.","You try my patience, but I suppose I can make further use of you. You are expendable after all.","fbmwVAVampChild_1planStoSserveSme_00f8ad56_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I wish for you to take care of a bothersome vampire hunter.","I wish for you to take care of a bothersome vampire hunter.","fbmwVAVampChild_1planStoSserveSme_00f8ad56_2"
"","","About my family",Neutral,50,"A vampire hunter? And not a very good one, apparently. Interesting. I had thought I would be more interested by this, but it's not the case.","A vampire hunter? And not a very good one, apparently. Interesting. I had thought I would be more interested by this, but it's not the case.","fbmwVAVampChild_1aboutSmySfamily_00aa8be4_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Family is an odd thing, is it not? Defined by blood, separated by blood, joined by blood. In the end, it is all just blood.","Family is an odd thing, is it not? Defined by blood, separated by blood, joined by blood. In the end, it is all just blood.","fbmwVAVampChild_1aboutSmySfamily_00aa8be4_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Well, as Kjeld is already dead, there is nothing further to be done regarding this matter. You have access to the clan services, new blood.","Well, as Kjeld is already dead, there is nothing further to be done regarding this matter. You have access to the clan services, new blood.","fbmwVAVampChild_1aboutSmySfamily_00aa8be4_3"
"","","About my family",Neutral,50,"There is no more you need know about this right now.","There is no more you need know about this right now.","fbmwVAVampChild_1aboutSmySfamily_00aa8be3_1"
"","","About my family",Neutral,50,"Yes, Fresh Blood, I once had a family. We were high born, even among the Altmer, and I lived with my husband and young son until my Rebirth.","Yes, Fresh Blood, I once had a family. We were high born, even among the Altmer, and I lived with my husband and young son until my Rebirth.","fbmwVAVampChild_1aboutSmySfamily_00aa8be2_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"My sire killed my former husband, but my son Vilandon was allowed to live.","My sire killed my former husband, but my son Vilandon was allowed to live.","fbmwVAVampChild_1aboutSmySfamily_00aa8be2_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I am curious what became of the boy, although he has likely gone the way of all mortals now. Still, it would be amusing to know his fate.","I am curious what became of the boy, although he has likely gone the way of all mortals now. Still, it would be amusing to know his fate.","fbmwVAVampChild_1aboutSmySfamily_00aa8be2_3"
"","","About my family",Neutral,50,"There is no more to say about this matter.","There is no more to say about this matter.","fbmwVAVampChild_1aboutSmySfamily_00aa8be6_1"
"","","About my family",Neutral,50,"A vampire hunter? And not a very good one, apparently. Interesting. Family is an odd thing, is it not?","A vampire hunter? And not a very good one, apparently. Interesting. Family is an odd thing, is it not?","fbmwVAVampChild_1aboutSmySfamily_00aa8be5_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Defined by blood, separated by blood, joined by blood. In the end, it is all just blood. Now, let us put this matter to rest. Find this Kjeld.","Defined by blood, separated by blood, joined by blood. In the end, it is all just blood. Now, let us put this matter to rest. Find this Kjeld.","fbmwVAVampChild_1aboutSmySfamily_00aa8be5_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Kill him.","Kill him.","fbmwVAVampChild_1aboutSmySfamily_00aa8be5_3"
"","","Vampire Hunter",Neutral,50,"You've killed him, but not as you were ordered! Leave my presence, fool.","You've killed him, but not as you were ordered! Leave my presence, fool.","MorroDefaultQuest_1vampireShunter_00f8a4fe_1"
"","","Vampire Hunter",Anger,50,"Yes, he came nosing about our lair some weeks ago. Some of my spies have tracked him to the city of Ald'ruhn.","Yes, he came nosing about our lair some weeks ago. Some of my spies have tracked him to the city of Ald'ruhn.","MorroDefaultQuest_1vampireShunter_00f8ad59_1"
"","","",Anger,80,"It is not enough for you to kill him, though. I want him killed in broad daylight, with plenty of folk there to see his death.","It is not enough for you to kill him, though. I want him killed in broad daylight, with plenty of folk there to see his death.","MorroDefaultQuest_1vampireShunter_00f8ad59_2"
"","","",Anger,75,"Let it serve as an example for all who would dare intrude in Ashmelech.","Let it serve as an example for all who would dare intrude in Ashmelech.","MorroDefaultQuest_1vampireShunter_00f8ad59_3"
"","","Vampire Hunter",Neutral,50,"I have no more to say on this topic, new blood. Begone.","I have no more to say on this topic, new blood. Begone.","MorroDefaultQuest_1vampireShunter_00f8ad5a_1"
"","","Vampire Hunter",Neutral,50,"You've killed him, but not as you were ordered! Leave my presence, fool.","You've killed him, but not as you were ordered! Leave my presence, fool.","MorroDefaultQuest_1vampireShunter_00f8ad5b_1"
"","","Vampire Hunter",Surprise,100,"You've gotten rid of him, and in full view of the local populace? Well done, little abomination!","You've gotten rid of him, and in full view of the local populace? Well done, little abomination!","MorroDefaultQuest_1vampireShunter_00f8ad5c_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"For your efforts, take this. It is an amulet that will allow you to return to Ashmelech when in need.","For your efforts, take this. It is an amulet that will allow you to return to Ashmelech when in need.","MorroDefaultQuest_1vampireShunter_00f8ad5c_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"It is possible I will have future rewards for you, should you be able to rid this world of a large number of the Berne and Quarra clan.","It is possible I will have future rewards for you, should you be able to rid this world of a large number of the Berne and Quarra clan.","MorroDefaultQuest_1vampireShunter_00f8ad5c_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Now leave me.","Now leave me.","MorroDefaultQuest_1vampireShunter_00f8ad5c_4"
"","","Vampire Hunter",Neutral,50,"You've gotten rid of him, and in full view of the local populace? Well done, little abomination! For your efforts, take this. It is an amulet that will allow you to return to Ashmelech when in need.","You've gotten rid of him, and in full view of the local populace? Well done, little abomination! For your efforts, take this. It is an amulet that will allow you to return to Ashmelech when in need.","MorroDefaultQuest_1vampireShunter_00f8a4ff_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"It is possible I will have future rewards for you, should you be able to rid this world of a large number of the Berne and Quarra clan. Now leave me.","It is possible I will have future rewards for you, should you be able to rid this world of a large number of the Berne and Quarra clan. Now leave me.","MorroDefaultQuest_1vampireShunter_00f8a4ff_2"
"","","Vampire Hunter",Neutral,50,"I have no more to say on this topic, new blood. Begone.","I have no more to say on this topic, new blood. Begone.","MorroDefaultQuest_1vampireShunter_00f8a500_1"
"","","Vampire Hunter",Neutral,50,"Yes, he came nosing about our lair some weeks ago. Some of my spies have tracked him to the city of Ald'ruhn. It is not enough for you to kill him, though.","Yes, he came nosing about our lair some weeks ago. Some of my spies have tracked him to the city of Ald'ruhn. It is not enough for you to kill him, though.","MorroDefaultQuest_1vampireShunter_00f8a501_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I want him killed in broad daylight, with plenty of folk there to see his death. Let it serve as an example for all who would dare intrude in Ashmelech.","I want him killed in broad daylight, with plenty of folk there to see his death. Let it serve as an example for all who would dare intrude in Ashmelech.","MorroDefaultQuest_1vampireShunter_00f8a501_2"
"","","Future Rewards",Neutral,50,"There is nothing further you may do for me.","There is nothing further you may do for me.","MorroDefaultQuest_1futureSrewards_00f8ad62_1"
"","","Future Rewards",Neutral,50,"I have no rewards for you yet, yearling.","I have no rewards for you yet, yearling.","MorroDefaultQuest_1futureSrewards_00f8ad63_1"
"","","Future Rewards",Neutral,50,"You have done well in ridding the world of many of our opposing clans.","You have done well in ridding the world of many of our opposing clans.","MorroDefaultQuest_1futureSrewards_00f8ad64_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"As a final gift to you, I will allow you the use of the cattle here in Ashmelech to feed.","As a final gift to you, I will allow you the use of the cattle here in Ashmelech to feed.","MorroDefaultQuest_1futureSrewards_00f8ad64_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Feed, but do not kill them. This would displease me greatly.","Feed, but do not kill them. This would displease me greatly.","MorroDefaultQuest_1futureSrewards_00f8ad64_3"
"","","Family Crest",Neutral,50,"Any Altmer who has met one of my kin should recognize the seal on that ring.","Any Altmer who has met one of my kin should recognize the seal on that ring.","fbmwVAVampChild_1familyScrest_00f8ad78_1"
"","","Family Crest",Neutral,50,"Any Altmer who has met one of my kin should recognize the seal on that ring.","Any Altmer who has met one of my kin should recognize the seal on that ring.","fbmwVAVampChild_1familyScrest_00f8a60c_1"
"","","Vilandon",Neutral,50,"He was my son. What has become of him, I do not know.","He was my son. What has become of him, I do not know.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Vilandon_00f8ab3c_1"
"","","Vilandon",Neutral,50,"He was my son. What has become of him, I do not know.","He was my son. What has become of him, I do not know.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Vilandon_00f8ad88_1"
"","","Kjeld",Neutral,50,"Well done, new meat. You have some potential, perhaps. This matter is now settled. You have access to the clan services.","Well done, new meat. You have some potential, perhaps. This matter is now settled. You have access to the clan services.","fbmwVAVampChild_1Kjeld_00f8ad8b_1"
"","","Kjeld",Neutral,50,"He is of the Quarra Clan, and resides in Druscashti. He is powerful, and will be well guarded, but such is your lot. Go.","He is of the Quarra Clan, and resides in Druscashti. He is powerful, and will be well guarded, but such is your lot. Go.","fbmwVAVampChild_1Kjeld_00f8ad8c_1"
"","","Kjeld",Neutral,50,"Well done, new meat. You have some potential, perhaps. This matter is now settled. You have access to the clan services.","Well done, new meat. You have some potential, perhaps. This matter is now settled. You have access to the clan services.","fbmwVAVampChild_1Kjeld_00f8ab49_1"
"","","Kjeld",Neutral,50,"He is of the Quarra Clan, and resides in Druscashti. He is powerful, and will be well guarded, but such is your lot. Go.","He is of the Quarra Clan, and resides in Druscashti. He is powerful, and will be well guarded, but such is your lot. Go.","fbmwVAVampChild_1Kjeld_00f8ab4a_1"
"","","I cannot help you.",Neutral,50,"You are as useless as you are pathetic. Leave my sight.","You are as useless as you are pathetic. Leave my sight.","fbmwVAVampChild_1aboutSmySfamily2_00323250_1"
"","","I will find out about your child.",Neutral,50,"Good. If you bring me back useful information, I will allow you use of the clan services here at Ashmelech...if it suits me to.","Good. If you bring me back useful information, I will allow you use of the clan services here at Ashmelech...if it suits me to.","fbmwVAVampChild_1aboutSmySfamily1_00323251_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The last I heard of any of my former family, they occupied the region that is now Sadrith Mora. You may wish to start there. Take this ring;","The last I heard of any of my former family, they occupied the region that is now Sadrith Mora. You may wish to start there. Take this ring;","fbmwVAVampChild_1aboutSmySfamily1_00323251_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"it bears my family crest. Any high elf in the region should recognize it, and may be able to give you information valuable to me. Go.","it bears my family crest. Any high elf in the region should recognize it, and may be able to give you information valuable to me. Go.","fbmwVAVampChild_1aboutSmySfamily1_00323251_3"
"","","I will kill this vampire hunter.",Neutral,50,"You show some degree of bravery, but you are young. And stupid. No matter. Find this one who kills our kind. Bring him to justice in the light of day, and let all who see know that they can suffer the same fate.","You show some degree of bravery, but you are young. And stupid. No matter. Find this one who kills our kind. Bring him to justice in the light of day, and let all who see know that they can suffer the same fate.","fbmwVAVampHunter_fbmwvavamphunteryes_00f8a995_1"
"","","I will not do this for you.",Neutral,50,"Hmph. I should have expected as much. You are cowardly even for your ilk. Begone, then. I have nothing further to say to you.","Hmph. I should have expected as much. You are cowardly even for your ilk. Begone, then. I have nothing further to say to you.","fbmwVAVampHunter_fbmwvavamphunterno_00f8a997_1"
"","","I will kill him for all to see.",Surprise,80,"You show some degree of bravery, but you are young.","You show some degree of bravery, but you are young.","MorroDefaultQuest_1VampireShunter1_00f8ad9e_1"
"","","",Disgust,90,"And stupid.","And stupid.","MorroDefaultQuest_1VampireShunter1_00f8ad9e_2"
"","","",Anger,50,"No matter. Find this one who kills our kind.","No matter. Find this one who kills our kind.","MorroDefaultQuest_1VampireShunter1_00f8ad9e_3"
"","","",Anger,50,"Bring him to justice in the light of day, and let all who see know that they can suffer the same fate.","Bring him to justice in the light of day, and let all who see know that they can suffer the same fate.","MorroDefaultQuest_1VampireShunter1_00f8ad9e_4"
"","","I will not do this for you.",Anger,80,"Hmph. I should have expected as much. You are cowardly even for your ilk.","Hmph. I should have expected as much. You are cowardly even for your ilk.","MorroDefaultQuest_1vampireshunter2_00f8ada0_1"
"","","",Anger,50,"Begone, then. I have nothing further to say to you.","Begone, then. I have nothing further to say to you.","MorroDefaultQuest_1vampireshunter2_00f8ada0_2"
