Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"CRIME GREETINGS","CRIME GREETINGS","MorroDefaultQuest_GREETING_0002a4b5_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Greetings 2 (VAMPIRE/NUDITY)","Greetings 2 (VAMPIRE/NUDITY)","MorroDefaultQuest_GREETING_0002a494_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Greeting 1","Greeting 1","MorroDefaultQuest_GREETING_0002a489_1"
"","","Smuggling Raw Ebony",Neutral,50,"Thank you, friend. Because of you, This one has freedom, so you must have truth. The boss man, Cunius Pelelius? He comes at night. He thinks he sneaks, thinks no one sees him.","Thank you, friend. Because of you, This one has freedom, so you must have truth. The boss man, Cunius Pelelius? He comes at night. He thinks he sneaks, thinks no one sees him.","fbmwICRich_1smugglingSrawSebony_00f8a2b6_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But everyone sees. He takes ebony and puts it in a bag. Then he sneaks out again.","But everyone sees. He takes ebony and puts it in a bag. Then he sneaks out again.","fbmwICRich_1smugglingSrawSebony_00f8a2b6_2"
"","","Smuggling Raw Ebony",Neutral,50,"Thank you, friend. I have my freedom, so you will have the truth. The boss man, Cunius Pelelius? He comes at night. He thinks he sneaks, thinks no one sees him. But everyone sees. He takes ebony and puts it in a bag. Then he sneaks out again.","Thank you, friend. I have my freedom, so you will have the truth. The boss man, Cunius Pelelius? He comes at night. He thinks he sneaks, thinks no one sees him. But everyone sees. He takes ebony and puts it in a bag. Then he sneaks out again.","fbmwICRich_1smugglingSrawSebony_00f8a2b7_1"
"","","Echo of Souls",Neutral,50,"Thou wilt come to me there, my love, our senses tingling, through the inky ocean delight, our voices mingling.","Thou wilt come to me there, my love, our senses tingling, through the inky ocean delight, our voices mingling.","MorroDefaultQuest_1echoSofSsouls_00321869_1"
"","","Lover feels",Neutral,50,"You stand upon my native shore. I'm pledged to guard Lord Dagoth's door.","You stand upon my native shore. I'm pledged to guard Lord Dagoth's door.","MorroDefaultQuest_1loverSfeels_00321e3f_1"
"","","Debt Money",Neutral,50,"Elethus Tobor owed money to the Camonna Tong for gambling debts. He's very poor and probably can't pay the money.","Elethus Tobor owed money to the Camonna Tong for gambling debts. He's very poor and probably can't pay the money.","MorroDefaultQuest_1debtSmoney_00322317_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If you want to complete this contract, you'll have to either kill him or pay the debt yourself.","If you want to complete this contract, you'll have to either kill him or pay the debt yourself.","MorroDefaultQuest_1debtSmoney_00322317_2"
"","","We see you",Neutral,50,"We see with one eye, we speak with one voice, we dream with one soul. We are all one in the Master, Lord Dagoth be praised.","We see with one eye, we speak with one voice, we dream with one soul. We are all one in the Master, Lord Dagoth be praised.","MorroDefaultQuest_1WeSseeSyou_003223bb_1"
