Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Join the Royal Guards",Neutral,50,"I've had worse jobs. Tienius Delitian knows what he's doing. He offered me a position, and I took it. Delitian is a hard-ass, but he's fair. I got no complaints.","I've had worse jobs. Tienius Delitian knows what he's doing. He offered me a position, and I took it. Delitian is a hard-ass, but he's fair. I got no complaints.","fbmwTR07Guard_1joinStheSRoyalSGuards_00f8ba1d_1"
"","","Mention your Hlaalu connections.",Neutral,50,"I don't think it's important. But you should mention it to Tienius Delitian, if you haven't already. He doesn't like surprises.","I don't think it's important. But you should mention it to Tienius Delitian, if you haven't already. He doesn't like surprises.","fbmwTR07Guard_fbmwtr07hlaalu_00f8bc93_1"
"","","Ask about King Helseth.",Neutral,50,"King Llethan was a joke king. King Helseth is a real king. I like to be on the winning side, and King Helseth looks like winning to me.","King Llethan was a joke king. King Helseth is a real king. I like to be on the winning side, and King Helseth looks like winning to me.","fbmwTR07Guard_fbmwtr07helseth_00f8bc9c_1"
"","","Ask about King Llethan.",Neutral,50,"He's dead. He doesn't matter.","He's dead. He doesn't matter.","fbmwTR07Guard_fbmwtr07llethan_00f8bca5_1"
