Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Do you want to discuss your stronghold?","Do you want to discuss your stronghold?","fbmwHHStronghold_GREETING_000079e8_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Are you looking for me? Do you want to build a stronghold?","Are you looking for me? Do you want to build a stronghold?","fbmwHHStronghold_GREETING_000079e9_1"
"","","Construction Contract",Neutral,50,"Only the Duke can issue construction contracts.","Only the Duke can issue construction contracts.","fbmwHHStronghold_1constructionScontract_0032071d_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"All three Great Houses have been ignoring this rule recently, but I have been ordered to insist that all new stronghold have the proper papers.","All three Great Houses have been ignoring this rule recently, but I have been ordered to insist that all new stronghold have the proper papers.","fbmwHHStronghold_1constructionScontract_0032071d_2"
"","","Guard against bandits",Neutral,50,"There are no more bandits near your stronghold to guard against.","There are no more bandits near your stronghold to guard against.","fbmwHHStronghold_1guardSagainstSbandits_0000680b_1"
"","","Guard against bandits",Neutral,50,"The bandit leader is dead? Good.","The bandit leader is dead? Good.","fbmwHHStronghold_1guardSagainstSbandits_0000680c_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I will give the orders to put the finishing touches on your stronghold.","I will give the orders to put the finishing touches on your stronghold.","fbmwHHStronghold_1guardSagainstSbandits_0000680c_2"
"","","Guard against bandits",Neutral,50,"I see that you hired a guard from the Fighters Guild. Now you must find the bandits nearby and kill their leader.","I see that you hired a guard from the Fighters Guild. Now you must find the bandits nearby and kill their leader.","fbmwHHStronghold_1guardSagainstSbandits_0000680d_1"
"","","Guard against bandits",Neutral,50,"Yes, go to the Fighters Guild or the Imperial Legion here in Balmora.","Yes, go to the Fighters Guild or the Imperial Legion here in Balmora.","fbmwHHStronghold_1guardSagainstSbandits_0000680e_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"See if they will let you hire someone to garrison your stronghold.","See if they will let you hire someone to garrison your stronghold.","fbmwHHStronghold_1guardSagainstSbandits_0000680e_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Perhaps with their aid you can track down the bandits near your stronghold.","Perhaps with their aid you can track down the bandits near your stronghold.","fbmwHHStronghold_1guardSagainstSbandits_0000680e_3"
"","","Recruit some miners",Neutral,50,"You've recruited some miners and the Shurdan-Raplay Egg Mine should give you some steady income.","You've recruited some miners and the Shurdan-Raplay Egg Mine should give you some steady income.","fbmwHHStronghold_1recruitSsomeSminers_00006809_1"
"","","Recruit some miners",Neutral,50,"In House Hlaalu, we always have a shortage of egg miners.","In House Hlaalu, we always have a shortage of egg miners.","fbmwHHStronghold_1recruitSsomeSminers_0000680a_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But this gives us the opportunity to recruit miners from the other Houses.","But this gives us the opportunity to recruit miners from the other Houses.","fbmwHHStronghold_1recruitSsomeSminers_0000680a_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"There are usually some unemployed miners in Gnisis and Tel Aruhn.","There are usually some unemployed miners in Gnisis and Tel Aruhn.","fbmwHHStronghold_1recruitSsomeSminers_0000680a_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Go to either of these cities and ask around.","Go to either of these cities and ask around.","fbmwHHStronghold_1recruitSsomeSminers_0000680a_4"
"","","Shurdan-Raplay",Neutral,50,"The Shurdan-Raplay Egg Mine is back in business.","The Shurdan-Raplay Egg Mine is back in business.","fbmwHHStronghold_1ShurdanTRaplay_000067fd_1"
"","","Shurdan-Raplay",Neutral,50,"The queen there is no longer blighted. Now you can recruit some miners.","The queen there is no longer blighted. Now you can recruit some miners.","fbmwHHStronghold_1ShurdanTRaplay_000067fe_1"
"","","Shurdan-Raplay",Neutral,50,"It's just across he River Odai from your stronghold. The queen there is blighted.","It's just across he River Odai from your stronghold. The queen there is blighted.","fbmwHHStronghold_1ShurdanTRaplay_000067ff_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If you need scrolls of cure blight, try speaking with Hetman Abelmawia in Gnisis or Pierlette Rostorard in Sadrith Mora.","If you need scrolls of cure blight, try speaking with Hetman Abelmawia in Gnisis or Pierlette Rostorard in Sadrith Mora.","fbmwHHStronghold_1ShurdanTRaplay_000067ff_2"
"","","Stronghold",Neutral,50,"You've been expelled. If you want to improve your stronghold, you'll need to make amends.","You've been expelled. If you want to improve your stronghold, you'll need to make amends.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_00322340_1"
"","","Stronghold",Neutral,50,"Your stronghold is complete, outlander. It rivals that of the greatest Hlaalu councilors.","Your stronghold is complete, outlander. It rivals that of the greatest Hlaalu councilors.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_000067ef_1"
"","","Stronghold",Neutral,50,"I have given the orders to begin the final stages of your stronghold, outlander.","I have given the orders to begin the final stages of your stronghold, outlander.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_000067f0_1"
"","","Stronghold",Neutral,50,"You have earned a high rank in House Hlaalu, and I am prepared to give you the stronghold you deserve, outlander.","You have earned a high rank in House Hlaalu, and I am prepared to give you the stronghold you deserve, outlander.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_000067f1_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Alas, before anyone would be willing to move to your stronghold, you must find a way to guard against bandits that prey on your trade.","Alas, before anyone would be willing to move to your stronghold, you must find a way to guard against bandits that prey on your trade.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_000067f1_2"
"","","Stronghold",Neutral,50,"The improvements to your stronghold are complete. Speak with me again when you need a stronghold fit for a Councilor of House Hlaalu.","The improvements to your stronghold are complete. Speak with me again when you need a stronghold fit for a Councilor of House Hlaalu.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_000067f2_1"
"","","Stronghold",Neutral,50,"I have given the orders to being the next phase of construction. Give it some time, outlander.","I have given the orders to being the next phase of construction. Give it some time, outlander.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_000067f3_1"
"","","Stronghold",Neutral,50,"Ilasour Tansumiran and Llaals Ores seem to be the only unemployed miners who could have helped you.","Ilasour Tansumiran and Llaals Ores seem to be the only unemployed miners who could have helped you.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_000067f4_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And now, If Ilasour Tansumiran and Llaals Ores are dead, that is the end of your ambitions.","And now, If Ilasour Tansumiran and Llaals Ores are dead, that is the end of your ambitions.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_000067f4_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"A stronghold that cannot support itself -- and its House -- is no stronghold at all.","A stronghold that cannot support itself -- and its House -- is no stronghold at all.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_000067f4_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"So there will be no stronghold for you, and no more advancement.","So there will be no stronghold for you, and no more advancement.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_000067f4_4"
"","","Stronghold",Neutral,50,"If the kwama queen at Shurdan-Raplay is dead, that is the end of your ambitions.","If the kwama queen at Shurdan-Raplay is dead, that is the end of your ambitions.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_000067f5_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"A stronghold that cannot support itself -- and its House -- is no stronghold at all.","A stronghold that cannot support itself -- and its House -- is no stronghold at all.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_000067f5_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"So there will be no stronghold for you, and no more advancement.","So there will be no stronghold for you, and no more advancement.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_000067f5_3"
"","","Stronghold",Neutral,50,"Your stronghold is now helping House Hlaalu with business and trade.","Your stronghold is now helping House Hlaalu with business and trade.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_000067f6_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I will give the orders to begin the next phase of construction.","I will give the orders to begin the next phase of construction.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_000067f6_2"
"","","Stronghold",Neutral,50,"When you are ready to improve your stronghold, you will need to find some business to engage in, such as farming or egg mining.","When you are ready to improve your stronghold, you will need to find some business to engage in, such as farming or egg mining.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_000067f7_1"
"","","Stronghold",Neutral,50,"So what did Durbul gro-Rush say? Ah, that is good news.","So what did Durbul gro-Rush say? Ah, that is good news.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_000067f8_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Your stronghold should be ready soon, then. Thank you for keeping me up to date.","Your stronghold should be ready soon, then. Thank you for keeping me up to date.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_000067f8_2"
"","","Stronghold",Neutral,50,"Just go talk to Durbul gro-Rush at the site of your new stronghold.","Just go talk to Durbul gro-Rush at the site of your new stronghold.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_000067f9_1"
"","","Stronghold",Neutral,50,"I want you to go check on your stronghold and talk to the foreman, Durbul gro-Rush, to make sure everything is going as planned.","I want you to go check on your stronghold and talk to the foreman, Durbul gro-Rush, to make sure everything is going as planned.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_000067fa_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Rethan Manor is being built on the Odai Plateau.","Rethan Manor is being built on the Odai Plateau.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_000067fa_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If you follow the Odai River south of Balmora, you should see construction to the southwest after the wood bridge.","If you follow the Odai River south of Balmora, you should see construction to the southwest after the wood bridge.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_000067fa_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I will mark it on your map.","I will mark it on your map.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_000067fa_4"
"","","Stronghold",Neutral,50,"The construction should begin any day now.","The construction should begin any day now.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_000067fb_1"
"","","Stronghold",Neutral,50,"Do you have the proper papers?","Do you have the proper papers?","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_000067fc_1"
"","","Stronghold",Neutral,50,"If you want to build a stronghold, I must have a construction contract and a land deed.","If you want to build a stronghold, I must have a construction contract and a land deed.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_00322344_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Baren Alen at the Hlaalu Vaults in Vivec can provide you with the land deed, but you must speak with Duke Vedam Dren to get the construction contract.","Baren Alen at the Hlaalu Vaults in Vivec can provide you with the land deed, but you must speak with Duke Vedam Dren to get the construction contract.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_00322344_2"
"","","Stronghold",Neutral,50,"I cannot accept contracts for strongholds from anyone under the rank of Kinsman.","I cannot accept contracts for strongholds from anyone under the rank of Kinsman.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold_00322345_1"
"","","Egg Mining",Neutral,50,"Egg mining may not be glamorous, but it's a good, steady business. You may come to appreciate it in time.","Egg mining may not be glamorous, but it's a good, steady business. You may come to appreciate it in time.","fbmwHHStronghold_1eggSmining_000067ea_1"
"","","Egg Mining",Neutral,50,"If the kwama queen at Shurdan-Raplay is dead, that is the end of your ambitions.","If the kwama queen at Shurdan-Raplay is dead, that is the end of your ambitions.","fbmwHHStronghold_1eggSmining_000067eb_1"
"","","",Neutral,50," A stronghold that cannot support itself -- and its House -- is no stronghold at all.","A stronghold that cannot support itself -- and its House -- is no stronghold at all.","fbmwHHStronghold_1eggSmining_000067eb_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"So there will be no stronghold for you, and no more advancement.","So there will be no stronghold for you, and no more advancement.","fbmwHHStronghold_1eggSmining_000067eb_3"
"","","Egg Mining",Neutral,50,"Ilasour Tansumiran and Llaals Ores seem to be the only unemployed miners who could have helped you.","Ilasour Tansumiran and Llaals Ores seem to be the only unemployed miners who could have helped you.","fbmwHHStronghold_1eggSmining_000067ec_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And now, If Ilasour Tansumiran and Llaals Ores are dead, that is the end of your ambitions.","And now, If Ilasour Tansumiran and Llaals Ores are dead, that is the end of your ambitions.","fbmwHHStronghold_1eggSmining_000067ec_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"A stronghold that cannot support itself -- and its House -- is no stronghold at all.","A stronghold that cannot support itself -- and its House -- is no stronghold at all.","fbmwHHStronghold_1eggSmining_000067ec_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"So there will be no stronghold for you, and no more advancement.","So there will be no stronghold for you, and no more advancement.","fbmwHHStronghold_1eggSmining_000067ec_4"
"","","Egg Mining",Neutral,50,"I believe there are several egg mines near your stronghold, outlander.","I believe there are several egg mines near your stronghold, outlander.","fbmwHHStronghold_1eggSmining_000067ed_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Unfortunately, the only one that is on the land you purchased is the Shurdan-Raplay Egg Mine, which is blighted.","Unfortunately, the only one that is on the land you purchased is the Shurdan-Raplay Egg Mine, which is blighted.","fbmwHHStronghold_1eggSmining_000067ed_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If you cure the kwama queen in the Shurdan-Raplay mine and recruit some miners, you will have a profitable business for your stronghold.","If you cure the kwama queen in the Shurdan-Raplay mine and recruit some miners, you will have a profitable business for your stronghold.","fbmwHHStronghold_1eggSmining_000067ed_3"
"","","Land Deed",Neutral,50,"Yes, you will need a land deed. Baren Alen at the Hlaalu Treasury can sell you one.","Yes, you will need a land deed. Baren Alen at the Hlaalu Treasury can sell you one.","fbmwHHStronghold_1landSdeed_00322451_1"
"","","Yes, here they are.",Neutral,50,"Yes, everything seems to be in order. I will give the orders to being construction.","Yes, everything seems to be in order. I will give the orders to being construction.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold1_0032353e_1"
"","","Yes, here they are.",Neutral,50,"I'm not buying that story, outlander. Either give me the papers or stop wasting my time.","I'm not buying that story, outlander. Either give me the papers or stop wasting my time.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold1_0032353f_1"
"","","No, not yet.",Neutral,50,"I can't build your stronghold without the proper papers.","I can't build your stronghold without the proper papers.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold2_000067ee_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Go see Baren Alen in Vivec and Duke Vedam Dren in Ebonheart.","Go see Baren Alen in Vivec and Duke Vedam Dren in Ebonheart.","fbmwHHStronghold_1stronghold2_000067ee_2"
