Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","King Llethan's death",Neutral,50,"They say he died of old age. That's possible. But is it likely? Have you seen a broadside sheet called "The Common Tongue".","They say he died of old age. That's possible. But is it likely? Have you seen a broadside sheet called "The Common Tongue".","fbmwTR05People_1KingSLlethanAsSdeath_003207b1_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"In there it says Helseth poisoned hundreds of people when he was in the West. So why wouldn't he poison one old man to become king in Morrowind?","In there it says Helseth poisoned hundreds of people when he was in the West. So why wouldn't he poison one old man to become king in Morrowind?","fbmwTR05People_1KingSLlethanAsSdeath_003207b1_2"
"","","King Llethan's death",Neutral,50,"[He looks at you and smiles unpleasantly.] The King is dead. Long live the King.","[He looks at you and smiles unpleasantly.] The King is dead. Long live the King.","fbmwTR05People_1KingSLlethanAsSdeath_003207b2_1"
"","","King Llethan's death",Neutral,50,"They say he died of old age. That's possible. But is it likely? Have you seen a broadside sheet called "The Common Tongue". In there it says Helseth poisoned hundreds of people when he was in the West.","They say he died of old age. That's possible. But is it likely? Have you seen a broadside sheet called "The Common Tongue". In there it says Helseth poisoned hundreds of people when he was in the West.","fbmwTRDBHunt_1KingSLlethanAsSdeath_00f8ba33_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"So why wouldn't he poison one old man to become king in Morrowind?","So why wouldn't he poison one old man to become king in Morrowind?","fbmwTRDBHunt_1KingSLlethanAsSdeath_00f8ba33_2"
"","","King Llethan's death",Neutral,50,"[He looks at you and smiles unpleasantly.] The King is dead. Long live the King.","[He looks at you and smiles unpleasantly.] The King is dead. Long live the King.","fbmwTRDBHunt_1KingSLlethanAsSdeath_00f8ba34_1"
