Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Falanu is dead? No! I can't speak about this anymore.","Falanu is dead? No! I can't speak about this anymore.","fbmwMSGreetings_GREETING_00f8872c_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"You've spoken to Falanu? Then she's alive! Let's get back to her quickly!","You've spoken to Falanu? Then she's alive! Let's get back to her quickly!","fbmwMSGreetings_GREETING_00f8872d_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"You. Stranger. Please, can you help me? While traveling with my wife, we were set upon by a pack of wild nix hounds!","You. Stranger. Please, can you help me? While traveling with my wife, we were set upon by a pack of wild nix hounds!","fbmwMSGreetings_GREETING_00f8872e_1"
"","","GREETING",Sad,100,"No, no, no, she can't be dead! My Falanu is dead! I can't go on. Goodbye, outlander, and may the gods grant you a better fortune than mine.","No, no, no, she can't be dead! My Falanu is dead! I can't go on. Goodbye, outlander, and may the gods grant you a better fortune than mine.","fbmwMVMissingCompanion_GREETING_000084a7_1"
"","","GREETING",Happy,50,"Thank the gods! We've found her! I never thought I'd see her again. You finding me has truly been a blessing.","Thank the gods! We've found her! I never thought I'd see her again. You finding me has truly been a blessing.","fbmwMVMissingCompanion_GREETING_000084a8_1"
"","","",Happy,50,"Thank you so much for your help, outlander. I wish I had more to offer you, but please take this book. It has meant so much to the two of us.","Thank you so much for your help, outlander. I wish I had more to offer you, but please take this book. It has meant so much to the two of us.","fbmwMVMissingCompanion_GREETING_000084a8_2"
"","","",Happy,50,"I can only hope you find as much enjoyment in it as we have. Take care!","I can only hope you find as much enjoyment in it as we have. Take care!","fbmwMVMissingCompanion_GREETING_000084a8_3"
"","","Wild Nix Hounds",Neutral,50,"I must get back to my wife before they return. Go!","I must get back to my wife before they return. Go!","fbmwMVMissingCompanion_1wildSnixShounds_00aa5355_1"
"","","Wild Nix Hounds",Neutral,50,"Yes, there must have been three at least. It was hard to tell in all of the confusion. Perhaps you've seen them around here.","Yes, there must have been three at least. It was hard to tell in all of the confusion. Perhaps you've seen them around here.","fbmwMVMissingCompanion_1wildSnixShounds_00aa5356_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Anyway, Falanu smartly tried to play dead while I fought them off. They were too much for me, though, and they chased me off.","Anyway, Falanu smartly tried to play dead while I fought them off. They were too much for me, though, and they chased me off.","fbmwMVMissingCompanion_1wildSnixShounds_00aa5356_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I ran away from where my wife was lying, so as not to draw them closer to her. I fear, however, that they could have gone back for her.","I ran away from where my wife was lying, so as not to draw them closer to her. I fear, however, that they could have gone back for her.","fbmwMVMissingCompanion_1wildSnixShounds_00aa5356_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Can you help me? The two of us together can certainly find her, and kill the foul beasts should they show themselves again.","Can you help me? The two of us together can certainly find her, and kill the foul beasts should they show themselves again.","fbmwMVMissingCompanion_1wildSnixShounds_00aa5356_4"
"","","Yes, let's go try and find your wife.",Neutral,50,"Excellent. Let us go quickly, then. I don't want those hounds to return before we do.","Excellent. Let us go quickly, then. I don't want those hounds to return before we do.","fbmwMVMissingCompanion_1wildSnixShounds3_00323220_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I believe I came from the east, but in all the confusion, it was difficult to tell. Though I am injured, I'm sure I can make it there with you.","I believe I came from the east, but in all the confusion, it was difficult to tell. Though I am injured, I'm sure I can make it there with you.","fbmwMVMissingCompanion_1wildSnixShounds3_00323220_2"
"","","I'm sorry. I can't help you.",Neutral,50,"Go on your way, then. I can find her myself, if need be. You could have helped, stranger.","Go on your way, then. I can find her myself, if need be. You could have helped, stranger.","fbmwMVMissingCompanion_1wildSnixShounds4_00323221_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Pray to your gods that if you are ever in need, you'll meet someone more charitable than yourself!","Pray to your gods that if you are ever in need, you'll meet someone more charitable than yourself!","fbmwMVMissingCompanion_1wildSnixShounds4_00323221_2"
