Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"Riekling","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"You stopped Krish, and that is good. Grahl are gone. Krish is gone. Nasty grahl. Nasty Krish. The master will be pleased when he comes home.","You stopped Krish, and that is good. Grahl are gone. Krish is gone. Nasty grahl. Nasty Krish. The master will be pleased when he comes home.","fbmwBMFrostGiant2_GREETING_00f8b8e7_1"
"Riekling","","",Neutral,50,"Your master will be pleased you have helped Dulk! Good good! Now go. Dulk has much to do before his master comes back. Go!","Your master will be pleased you have helped Dulk! Good good! Now go. Dulk has much to do before his master comes back. Go!","fbmwBMFrostGiant2_GREETING_00f8b8e7_2"
"Riekling","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"You are here! The master told me there would be one coming! You must help. Krish is trying to take control of the castle. He has found nasty grahl to help him! You must kill them all! My master will be pleased! Your master will be pleased.","You are here! The master told me there would be one coming! You must help. Krish is trying to take control of the castle. He has found nasty grahl to help him! You must kill them all! My master will be pleased! Your master will be pleased.","fbmwBMFrostGiant2_GREETING_00f8b8e8_1"
"Riekling","","",Neutral,50,"Go now, through the Banquet Hall to the caverns. They wait down there! Go now or the master will not be happy!","Go now, through the Banquet Hall to the caverns. They wait down there! Go now or the master will not be happy!","fbmwBMFrostGiant2_GREETING_00f8b8e8_2"
"Riekling","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"You go now! Master will be back soon. I am sure of this! And I must keep things right for him. Back soon. He will be back soon.","You go now! Master will be back soon. I am sure of this! And I must keep things right for him. Back soon. He will be back soon.","fbmwBMFrostGiant1_GREETING_00f8b8e5_1"
"Riekling","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"What are you doing here? The master will not be pleased! And you come with Krish! Evil, evil Krish! Krish is bad, and you are bad for helping him. What is it you want? You should leave.","What are you doing here? The master will not be pleased! And you come with Krish! Evil, evil Krish! Krish is bad, and you are bad for helping him. What is it you want? You should leave.","fbmwBMFrostGiant1_GREETING_00f8b8e6_1"
"Riekling","","Death of the Horkers",Neutral,50,"No time for your questions! Krish must be stopped!","No time for your questions! Krish must be stopped!","fbmwBMFrostGiant2_1deathSofStheShorkers_00f8baa2_1"
"Riekling","","Death of the Horkers",Neutral,50,"No more to say. No more to say. The fat ones are dead, but we know nothing of it!","No more to say. No more to say. The fat ones are dead, but we know nothing of it!","fbmwBMFrostGiant1_1deathSofStheShorkers_00f8baa0_1"
"Riekling","","Death of the Horkers",Neutral,50,"This was not our doing. Not even Krish could have done this! He was too busy here. I was too busy here! The master is gone, gone with the wolves! Big wolves! Evil wolves! Wolves that walk like men! Took the Master days ago! No time for the fat horkers!","This was not our doing. Not even Krish could have done this! He was too busy here. I was too busy here! The master is gone, gone with the wolves! Big wolves! Evil wolves! Wolves that walk like men! Took the Master days ago! No time for the fat horkers!","fbmwBMFrostGiant1_1deathSofStheShorkers_00f8baa1_1"
"Riekling","","",Neutral,50,"And Dulk did none of this!","And Dulk did none of this!","fbmwBMFrostGiant1_1deathSofStheShorkers_00f8baa1_2"
"Riekling","","Master is Gone",Neutral,50,"Yes, yes, the master is gone. He must return soon. The wolves came and took him away. Big wolves, evil wolves! Wolves that walk like men! Left Dulk all alone!","Yes, yes, the master is gone. He must return soon. The wolves came and took him away. Big wolves, evil wolves! Wolves that walk like men! Left Dulk all alone!","fbmwBMFrostGiant2_1masterSisSgone_00f8bae4_1"
"Riekling","","",Neutral,50,"But the master will be back soon. The master must come back soon!","But the master will be back soon. The master must come back soon!","fbmwBMFrostGiant2_1masterSisSgone_00f8bae4_2"
"Riekling","","Master is Gone",Neutral,50,"No time to talk now! Not with Krish still on the loose!","No time to talk now! Not with Krish still on the loose!","fbmwBMFrostGiant2_1masterSisSgone_00f8bae5_1"
"Riekling","","Revolt",Neutral,50,"That is done. Master will be happy.","That is done. Master will be happy.","fbmwBMFrostGiant2_1revolt_00f8bc10_1"
"Riekling","","Revolt",Neutral,50,"Yes! Krish is in revolt!","Yes! Krish is in revolt!","fbmwBMFrostGiant2_1revolt_00f8bc11_1"
"Riekling","","Revolt",Neutral,50,"Many of them are. Not me, though. Not loyal Dulk. I serve the master still. But Krish and the others have surrounded the castle. I am but one, and he is many! He says he is the master now. You must help. You must make Krish stop! ","Many of them are. Not me, though. Not loyal Dulk. I serve the master still. But Krish and the others have surrounded the castle. I am but one, and he is many! He says he is the master now. You must help. You must make Krish stop!","fbmwBMFrostGiant1_1revolt_00f8bc0f_1"
"Riekling","","",Neutral,50,"The master will not be pleased.","The master will not be pleased.","fbmwBMFrostGiant1_1revolt_00f8bc0f_2"
