Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Nerevarine Prophecies",Neutral,50,"You must forgive us. Perhaps these are great days. Perhaps the prophecies are fulfilled.","You must forgive us. Perhaps these are great days. Perhaps the prophecies are fulfilled.","fbmwMQ11u_1NerevarineSprophecies_0001dd68_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But to the Ahemmusa, all we know is that hunger and disease stalks us, and monsters prey upon us. A hero reborn may be a wonderful thing.","But to the Ahemmusa, all we know is that hunger and disease stalks us, and monsters prey upon us. A hero reborn may be a wonderful thing.","fbmwMQ11u_1NerevarineSprophecies_0001dd68_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But it means little to us, unless we have a safe place.","But it means little to us, unless we have a safe place.","fbmwMQ11u_1NerevarineSprophecies_0001dd68_3"
"","","Nerevarine",Neutral,50,"Speak to the wise woman, Sinnammu Mirpal. Tell her you will find a safe place for the Ahemmusa.","Speak to the wise woman, Sinnammu Mirpal. Tell her you will find a safe place for the Ahemmusa.","fbmwMQ11a_1Nerevarine_000104b8_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"That is what I would wish to hear from one who wants to be named Nerevarine.","That is what I would wish to hear from one who wants to be named Nerevarine.","fbmwMQ11a_1Nerevarine_000104b8_2"
"","","Healer",Neutral,50,"Mamaea is our healer. You'll find her in her tent.","Mamaea is our healer. You'll find her in her tent.","MorroDefaultQuest_1healer_00322c11_1"
