Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"What did you find at Huleen's hut? Was it worth all these intolerable interruptions?","What did you find at Huleen's hut? Was it worth all these intolerable interruptions?","fbmwMGApprentice_GREETING_00f852b3_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I am glad Vvardenfell finally has an Arch-Mage who cares about scholarship.","I am glad Vvardenfell finally has an Arch-Mage who cares about scholarship.","fbmwMGBethamez_GREETING_00f84a35_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"My studies are at a critical phase. I do not have any more duties for you, but I will put in a word with Arch-Mage Trebonius.","My studies are at a critical phase. I do not have any more duties for you, but I will put in a word with Arch-Mage Trebonius.","fbmwMGBethamez_GREETING_00f84a36_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Did you find any plans or blueprints in Bethamez?","Did you find any plans or blueprints in Bethamez?","fbmwMGBethamez_GREETING_00f84a37_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Did you get the excavation report from Nchuleftingth?","Did you get the excavation report from Nchuleftingth?","fbmwMGExcavation_GREETING_00f84a39_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Did you find any plans or blueprints in Mzuleft?","Did you find any plans or blueprints in Mzuleft?","fbmwMGMzuleft_GREETING_00f84a38_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Well, don't just stand there. Have you found a copy of Chronicles of Nchuleft or not?","Well, don't just stand there. Have you found a copy of Chronicles of Nchuleft or not?","fbmwMGNchuleftBook_GREETING_00f852b5_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Did you get the Detect Creatures Potion from Skink?","Did you get the Detect Creatures Potion from Skink?","fbmwMGPotion_GREETING_00f852b6_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Did you return Chimarvamidium?","Did you return Chimarvamidium?","fbmwMGReturnBook_GREETING_00f852b8_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Have you found a Dwemer Tube? Many of my studies cannot continue until I have one in my possession.","Have you found a Dwemer Tube? Many of my studies cannot continue until I have one in my possession.","fbmwMGScience_GREETING_00f84a3a_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Did you get Chimarvamidium?","Did you get Chimarvamidium?","fbmwMGStealBook_GREETING_00f852b7_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"What's so important that you would interrupt my studies? If you must have duties for the Mages Guild, I suppose I could think of something.","What's so important that you would interrupt my studies? If you must have duties for the Mages Guild, I suppose I could think of something.","fbmwMGAdvancement_GREETING_00f852b4_1"
"","","Antecedents of Dwemer Law",Neutral,50,"I know I purchased my own copy from Codus Callonus here in town. I think someone else asked for a copy, some local servant of House Redoran.","I know I purchased my own copy from Codus Callonus here in town. I think someone else asked for a copy, some local servant of House Redoran.","fbmwHTDwemerLaw_1AntecedentsSofSDwemerSLaw_00320451_1"
"","","Detect Creatures Potion",Neutral,50,"Are you still a member of the guild? Once Trebonius gives the authorization, we can discuss guild matters again.","Are you still a member of the guild? Once Trebonius gives the authorization, we can discuss guild matters again.","fbmwMGPotion_1DetectSCreaturesSPotion_003204e1_1"
"","","Detect Creatures Potion",Neutral,50,"Were you expelled? Or did you clear that up already? You ought to make amends with Guildmaster Trebonius just to be sure.","Were you expelled? Or did you clear that up already? You ought to make amends with Guildmaster Trebonius just to be sure.","fbmwMGPotion_1DetectSCreaturesSPotion_003204e2_1"
"","","Detect Creatures Potion",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled, outlander. If you want to make amends, you should speak with Guildmaster Trebonius.","You have been expelled, outlander. If you want to make amends, you should speak with Guildmaster Trebonius.","fbmwMGPotion_1DetectSCreaturesSPotion_003204e3_1"
"","","Detect Creatures Potion",Neutral,50,"I appreciated the potion. It will prove very useful.","I appreciated the potion. It will prove very useful.","fbmwMGPotion_1DetectSCreaturesSPotion_00f8a223_1"
"","","Detect Creatures Potion",Neutral,50,"What's that? Skink-in-Tree's-Shade is dead? This is just terrible news. I don't think I'll have any more duties for you if Skink is dead.","What's that? Skink-in-Tree's-Shade is dead? This is just terrible news. I don't think I'll have any more duties for you if Skink is dead.","fbmwMGPotion_1DetectSCreaturesSPotion_003204e4_1"
"","","Detect Creatures Potion",Neutral,50,"Ah, at last, you've brought me a Detect Creatures potion. Will you give the potion to me now?","Ah, at last, you've brought me a Detect Creatures potion. Will you give the potion to me now?","fbmwMGPotion_1DetectSCreaturesSPotion_00f8a224_1"
"","","Detect Creatures Potion",Neutral,50,"Just go talk to Skink-in-Tree's-Shade in Sadrith Mora and bring back the Detect Creatures potion.","Just go talk to Skink-in-Tree's-Shade in Sadrith Mora and bring back the Detect Creatures potion.","fbmwMGPotion_1DetectSCreaturesSPotion_00f8a225_1"
"","","Detect Creatures Potion",Neutral,50,"It's simply taking Skink-in-Tree's-Shade forever to finish it. Go to Wolverine Hall in Sadrith Mora and bring the potion back to me as soon as Skink is finished.","It's simply taking Skink-in-Tree's-Shade forever to finish it. Go to Wolverine Hall in Sadrith Mora and bring the potion back to me as soon as Skink is finished.","fbmwMGPotion_1DetectSCreaturesSPotion_00f8a226_1"
"","","Chair of Dwemer Studies",Neutral,50,"Currently, the Chair is empty and the Great Houses can't agree on a replacement. I believe Hasphat Antabolis was nominated...","Currently, the Chair is empty and the Great Houses can't agree on a replacement. I believe Hasphat Antabolis was nominated...","MorroDefaultQuest_1ChairSofSDwemerSStudies_003204eb_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I'd try to get the position myself, but I fear all the meetings and bookkeeping would take time away from my research.","I'd try to get the position myself, but I fear all the meetings and bookkeeping would take time away from my research.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ChairSofSDwemerSStudies_003204eb_2"
"","","Chronicles of Nchuleft",Neutral,50,"Are you still a member of the guild? Once Trebonius gives the authorization, we can discuss guild matters again.","Are you still a member of the guild? Once Trebonius gives the authorization, we can discuss guild matters again.","fbmwMGNchuleftBook_1ChroniclesSofSNchuleft_003205c7_1"
"","","Chronicles of Nchuleft",Neutral,50,"Were you expelled? Or did you clear that up already? You ought to make amends with Guildmaster Trebonius just to be sure.","Were you expelled? Or did you clear that up already? You ought to make amends with Guildmaster Trebonius just to be sure.","fbmwMGNchuleftBook_1ChroniclesSofSNchuleft_003205c8_1"
"","","Chronicles of Nchuleft",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled, outlander. If you want to make amends, you should speak with Guildmaster Trebonius.","You have been expelled, outlander. If you want to make amends, you should speak with Guildmaster Trebonius.","fbmwMGNchuleftBook_1ChroniclesSofSNchuleft_003205c9_1"
"","","Chronicles of Nchuleft",Neutral,50,"Chronicles of Nchuleft has been invaluable in my research.","Chronicles of Nchuleft has been invaluable in my research.","fbmwMGNchuleftBook_1ChroniclesSofSNchuleft_00f8a24b_1"
"","","Chronicles of Nchuleft",Neutral,50,"What? You already have a copy of Chronicles of Nchuleft? I am impressed with your scholarship. Are you willing to part with the book?","What? You already have a copy of Chronicles of Nchuleft? I am impressed with your scholarship. Are you willing to part with the book?","fbmwMGNchuleftBook_1ChroniclesSofSNchuleft_00f8a24c_1"
"","","Chronicles of Nchuleft",Neutral,50,"You actually found a copy? Excellent, now give the book to me.","You actually found a copy? Excellent, now give the book to me.","fbmwMGNchuleftBook_1ChroniclesSofSNchuleft_003205ce_1"
"","","Chronicles of Nchuleft",Neutral,50,"I simply *must* have this book for my research. Use the gold I gave you to find a copy. Maybe one of the booksellers has one.","I simply *must* have this book for my research. Use the gold I gave you to find a copy. Maybe one of the booksellers has one.","fbmwMGNchuleftBook_1ChroniclesSofSNchuleft_00f8a24f_1"
"","","Chronicles of Nchuleft",Neutral,50,"It is a rare Dwarven tome. None of the Mages Guild branches have a copy, and it is simply *essential* to my research.","It is a rare Dwarven tome. None of the Mages Guild branches have a copy, and it is simply *essential* to my research.","fbmwMGNchuleftBook_1ChroniclesSofSNchuleft_003205d1_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Would you be willing to find a copy for me?","Would you be willing to find a copy for me?","fbmwMGNchuleftBook_1ChroniclesSofSNchuleft_003205d1_2"
"","","Divine Metaphysics",Neutral,50,"I cannot make sense of this. Even when I try using this "Hanging Gardens" you've found as a translation key, the words simply do not make any sense.","I cannot make sense of this. Even when I try using this "Hanging Gardens" you've found as a translation key, the words simply do not make any sense.","fbmwMGDwarves_1DivineSMetaphysics_00320999_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I am certain the author did not know any magic himself. Yes, these are probably just the ramblings of some Dwarven lunatic.","I am certain the author did not know any magic himself. Yes, these are probably just the ramblings of some Dwarven lunatic.","fbmwMGDwarves_1DivineSMetaphysics_00320999_2"
"","","Divine Metaphysics",Neutral,50,"Hm. I do not know what to tell you about that book. I can make sense of Dwemer plans, but I cannot read their language.","Hm. I do not know what to tell you about that book. I can make sense of Dwemer plans, but I cannot read their language.","fbmwMGDwarves_1DivineSMetaphysics_0032099a_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You might want to ask Hasphat Antabolis in Balmora.","You might want to ask Hasphat Antabolis in Balmora.","fbmwMGDwarves_1DivineSMetaphysics_0032099a_2"
"","","Divine Metaphysics",Neutral,50,"You have this book translated? What does it say? What? I'm not sure I quite understand... something about making a new god? No, this is useless to my research.","You have this book translated? What does it say? What? I'm not sure I quite understand... something about making a new god? No, this is useless to my research.","fbmwMGDwarves_1DivineSMetaphysics_00f8a2be_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Now if I had the plans for how to make a steam centurion, that would be of much more practical use.","Now if I had the plans for how to make a steam centurion, that would be of much more practical use.","fbmwMGDwarves_1DivineSMetaphysics_00f8a2be_2"
"","","Excavation report",Neutral,50,"Are you still a member of the guild? Once Trebonius gives the authorization, we can discuss guild matters again.","Are you still a member of the guild? Once Trebonius gives the authorization, we can discuss guild matters again.","fbmwMGExcavation_1excavationSreport_00320c74_1"
"","","Excavation report",Neutral,50,"Were you expelled? Or did you clear that up already? You ought to make amends with Guildmaster Trebonius just to be sure.","Were you expelled? Or did you clear that up already? You ought to make amends with Guildmaster Trebonius just to be sure.","fbmwMGExcavation_1excavationSreport_00320c75_1"
"","","Excavation report",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled, outlander. If you want to make amends, you should speak with Guildmaster Trebonius.","You have been expelled, outlander. If you want to make amends, you should speak with Guildmaster Trebonius.","fbmwMGExcavation_1excavationSreport_00320c76_1"
"","","Excavation report",Neutral,50,"Senilias is dead? I am sorry to hear that. I will have to change my entire plan of research.","Senilias is dead? I am sorry to hear that. I will have to change my entire plan of research.","fbmwMGExcavation_1excavationSreport_00f8a30e_1"
"","","Excavation report",Neutral,50,"The latest excavation report was right on schedule.","The latest excavation report was right on schedule.","fbmwMGExcavation_1excavationSreport_00f8a30f_1"
"","","Excavation report",Neutral,50,"This is interesting... The excavation report mentions another Dwemer ruin, Mzuleft. Would you go there and look for some blueprints?","This is interesting... The excavation report mentions another Dwemer ruin, Mzuleft. Would you go there and look for some blueprints?","fbmwMGExcavation_1excavationSreport_00f8a310_1"
"","","Excavation report",Neutral,50,"If you have such a keen interest in scholarship, perhaps you'd like to join the Mages Guild.","If you have such a keen interest in scholarship, perhaps you'd like to join the Mages Guild.","fbmwMGExcavation_1excavationSreport_00f8a311_1"
"","","Excavation report",Neutral,50,"I have the excavation report already.","I have the excavation report already.","fbmwMGExcavation_1excavationSreport_00f8a312_1"
"","","Excavation report",Neutral,50,"Did you get the excavation report? Do you have it with you?","Did you get the excavation report? Do you have it with you?","fbmwMGExcavation_1excavationSreport_00f8a313_1"
"","","Excavation report",Neutral,50,"He doesn't have a report for me? Why not? What kind of setbacks? This sounds suspicious. I absolutely must have that excavation report. Go back to Nchuleftingth and find out what is really going on.","He doesn't have a report for me? Why not? What kind of setbacks? This sounds suspicious. I absolutely must have that excavation report. Go back to Nchuleftingth and find out what is really going on.","fbmwMGExcavation_1excavationSreport_00f8a314_1"
"","","Excavation report",Neutral,50,"Go to Nchuleftingth and talk with Senilias Cadiusus. Find out why he hasn't delivered his excavation report.","Go to Nchuleftingth and talk with Senilias Cadiusus. Find out why he hasn't delivered his excavation report.","fbmwMGExcavation_1excavationSreport_00f8a315_1"
"","","Excavation report",Neutral,50,"One of my colleagues, Senilias Cadiusus, is engaged in official Imperial research in Nchuleftingth. He was supposed to give me an excavation report every month, but has not sent one this month.","One of my colleagues, Senilias Cadiusus, is engaged in official Imperial research in Nchuleftingth. He was supposed to give me an excavation report every month, but has not sent one this month.","fbmwMGExcavation_1excavationSreport_00f8a316_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Go to Nchuleftingth and find out what is going on.","Go to Nchuleftingth and find out what is going on.","fbmwMGExcavation_1excavationSreport_00f8a316_2"
"","","Alms for the poor",Neutral,50,"You have my contribution.","You have my contribution.","fbmwICBuckmothAlms_1almsSforStheSpoor_00f8a367_1"
"","","Alms for the poor",Neutral,50,"Of course. I'm happy to donate for such a worthy cause.","Of course. I'm happy to donate for such a worthy cause.","fbmwICBuckmothAlms_1almsSforStheSpoor_00f8a368_1"
"","","Alms for the poor",Neutral,50,"You're right. We all must do our part. Here. It's not much, but it's all I can spare.","You're right. We all must do our part. Here. It's not much, but it's all I can spare.","fbmwICBuckmothAlms_1almsSforStheSpoor_00f8a369_1"
"","","Dwemer Animunculi",Neutral,50,"Yes, you've shown me the book already. It was a quite a find. I'm sure I'll have a working centurion any day now.","Yes, you've shown me the book already. It was a quite a find. I'm sure I'll have a working centurion any day now.","MorroDefaultQuest_1DwemerSAnimunculi_00320c59_1"
"","","Dwemer Animunculi",Neutral,50,"Let me see it at once!","Let me see it at once!","MorroDefaultQuest_1DwemerSAnimunculi_00320c5c_1"
"","","Hanging Gardens",Neutral,50,"Now this is an interesting book, outlander. It appears to be written in both Dwemer and Aldmeris.","Now this is an interesting book, outlander. It appears to be written in both Dwemer and Aldmeris.","MorroDefaultQuest_1HangingSGardens_003210a3_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If you could find a scholar of the Dwemer who knew Aldmeris, you might be able to translate portions of the Dwemer text.","If you could find a scholar of the Dwemer who knew Aldmeris, you might be able to translate portions of the Dwemer text.","MorroDefaultQuest_1HangingSGardens_003210a3_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"This book is priceless in the right hands.","This book is priceless in the right hands.","MorroDefaultQuest_1HangingSGardens_003210a3_3"
"","","Chimarvamidium",Neutral,50,"Are you still a member of the guild? Once Trebonius gives the authorization, we can discuss guild matters again.","Are you still a member of the guild? Once Trebonius gives the authorization, we can discuss guild matters again.","fbmwMGReturnBook_1Chimarvamidium_003214c0_1"
"","","Chimarvamidium",Neutral,50,"While Chimarvamidium was not as useful as I'd hoped, I do appreciate your efforts.","While Chimarvamidium was not as useful as I'd hoped, I do appreciate your efforts.","fbmwMGReturnBook_1Chimarvamidium_00f8a490_1"
"","","Chimarvamidium",Neutral,50,"The book has been returned? Good work, friend. Once I know the locations of some Dwemer ruins, I will be asking you to travel to some dangerous places. These amulets will help you return to safety.","The book has been returned? Good work, friend. Once I know the locations of some Dwemer ruins, I will be asking you to travel to some dangerous places. These amulets will help you return to safety.","fbmwMGReturnBook_1Chimarvamidium_00f8a491_1"
"","","Chimarvamidium",Neutral,50,"Like I said, take Chimarvamidium back to the Mages Guild in Vivec. Make sure you put it back exactly where you found it.","Like I said, take Chimarvamidium back to the Mages Guild in Vivec. Make sure you put it back exactly where you found it.","fbmwMGReturnBook_1Chimarvamidium_00f8a492_1"
"","","Chimarvamidium",Neutral,50,"Can you believe this isn't about a Dwemer construct at all? This book was completely useless. In any case, I need you to return the book before Sirilonwe suspects anything. Return the book to wherever you found it.","Can you believe this isn't about a Dwemer construct at all? This book was completely useless. In any case, I need you to return the book before Sirilonwe suspects anything. Return the book to wherever you found it.","fbmwMGReturnBook_1Chimarvamidium_00f8a493_1"
"","","Chimarvamidium",Neutral,50,"Were you expelled? Or did you clear that up already? You ought to make amends with Guildmaster Trebonius just to be sure.","Were you expelled? Or did you clear that up already? You ought to make amends with Guildmaster Trebonius just to be sure.","fbmwMGStealBook_1Chimarvamidium_003214c1_1"
"","","Chimarvamidium",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled, outlander. If you want to make amends, you should speak with Guildmaster Trebonius.","You have been expelled, outlander. If you want to make amends, you should speak with Guildmaster Trebonius.","fbmwMGStealBook_1Chimarvamidium_003214c2_1"
"","","Chimarvamidium",Neutral,50,"I have not had a chance to study the book. Have patience.","I have not had a chance to study the book. Have patience.","fbmwMGStealBook_1Chimarvamidium_00f8a494_1"
"","","Chimarvamidium",Neutral,50,"You have a copy of Chimarvamidium? Will you let me borrow the book?","You have a copy of Chimarvamidium? Will you let me borrow the book?","fbmwMGStealBook_1Chimarvamidium_00f8a495_1"
"","","Chimarvamidium",Neutral,50,"Just go to the Mages Guild in Vivec, find the book Chimarvamidium, and return it to me. I'm certain that Sirilonwe has a copy, though she may claim otherwise.","Just go to the Mages Guild in Vivec, find the book Chimarvamidium, and return it to me. I'm certain that Sirilonwe has a copy, though she may claim otherwise.","fbmwMGStealBook_1Chimarvamidium_00f8a496_1"
"","","Chimarvamidium",Neutral,50,"It is the sixth volume of Marobar Sul's "Ancient Tales of the Dwemer." Most of the "Ancient Tales" are not truly Dwemer in origin, but this one may be an exception.","It is the sixth volume of Marobar Sul's "Ancient Tales of the Dwemer." Most of the "Ancient Tales" are not truly Dwemer in origin, but this one may be an exception.","fbmwMGStealBook_1Chimarvamidium_00f8a497_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"It deals with some sort of golem or centurion. Would you be willing to "borrow" this book for me?","It deals with some sort of golem or centurion. Would you be willing to "borrow" this book for me?","fbmwMGStealBook_1Chimarvamidium_00f8a497_2"
"","","Nchuleftingth",Neutral,50,"You can get there by going around the mountains near Suran and heading northeast along the Foyada Nadanat, or you can start in Molag Mar and head northwest towards Mount Kand.","You can get there by going around the mountains near Suran and heading northeast along the Foyada Nadanat, or you can start in Molag Mar and head northwest towards Mount Kand.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Nchuleftingth_003217e9_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Go north around Mount Kand and along the north side of the Foyada.","Go north around Mount Kand and along the north side of the Foyada.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Nchuleftingth_003217e9_2"
"","","Huleen's hut",Neutral,50,"Are you still a member of the guild? Once Trebonius gives the authorization, we can discuss guild matters again.","Are you still a member of the guild? Once Trebonius gives the authorization, we can discuss guild matters again.","fbmwMGApprentice_1HuleenAsShut_00321b63_1"
"","","Huleen's hut",Neutral,50,"Were you expelled? Or did you clear that up already? You ought to make amends with Guildmaster Trebonius just to be sure.","Were you expelled? Or did you clear that up already? You ought to make amends with Guildmaster Trebonius just to be sure.","fbmwMGApprentice_1HuleenAsShut_00321b64_1"
"","","Huleen's hut",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled, outlander. If you want to make amends, you should speak with Guildmaster Trebonius.","You have been expelled, outlander. If you want to make amends, you should speak with Guildmaster Trebonius.","fbmwMGApprentice_1HuleenAsShut_00321b65_1"
"","","Huleen's hut",Neutral,50,"I'm trying to forget about it.","I'm trying to forget about it.","fbmwMGApprentice_1HuleenAsShut_00f8a5d4_1"
"","","Huleen's hut",Neutral,50,"You've been to Huleen's Hut? What happened? Is her apprentice okay?","You've been to Huleen's Hut? What happened? Is her apprentice okay?","fbmwMGApprentice_1HuleenAsShut_00321b6b_1"
"","","Huleen's hut",Neutral,50,"So Huleen's apprentice summoned a scamp? Is that all? I can't believe I was distracted from my studies for something so trivial. Speaking of which, I discovered these scrolls during my research. You may find them useful.","So Huleen's apprentice summoned a scamp? Is that all? I can't believe I was distracted from my studies for something so trivial. Speaking of which, I discovered these scrolls during my research. You may find them useful.","fbmwMGApprentice_1HuleenAsShut_00f8a5d5_1"
"","","Huleen's hut",Neutral,50,"There was a Scamp loose in Huleen's hut? This needs more investigation. Go back to Huleen's hut and see if you can find Huleen's apprentice, Listien Bierles.","There was a Scamp loose in Huleen's hut? This needs more investigation. Go back to Huleen's hut and see if you can find Huleen's apprentice, Listien Bierles.","fbmwMGApprentice_1HuleenAsShut_00f8a5d6_1"
"","","Huleen's hut",Neutral,50,"Just go to Huleen's hut in Maar Gan and find out what's going on. Don't distract me from my work.","Just go to Huleen's hut in Maar Gan and find out what's going on. Don't distract me from my work.","fbmwMGApprentice_1HuleenAsShut_00f8a5d7_1"
"","","Huleen's hut",Neutral,50,"Since Huleen is a member of the Guild, we really ought to do something about the disturbance. I simply haven't had time to do it myself. My research is at an absolutely critical phase. Would you go to Maar Gan and take a look for me?","Since Huleen is a member of the Guild, we really ought to do something about the disturbance. I simply haven't had time to do it myself. My research is at an absolutely critical phase. Would you go to Maar Gan and take a look for me?","fbmwMGApprentice_1HuleenAsShut_00f8a5d8_1"
"","","Ald Velothi",Neutral,50,"Take the Silt Strider to Gnisis and follow the roads north. I will mark Ald Velothi on your map.","Take the Silt Strider to Gnisis and follow the roads north. I will mark Ald Velothi on your map.","MorroDefaultQuest_1AldSVelothi_003220d3_1"
"","","Egg of Time",Neutral,50,"This book is puzzling to me. You might want to ask Hasphat Antabolis in Balmora.","This book is puzzling to me. You might want to ask Hasphat Antabolis in Balmora.","fbmwMGDwarves_1EggSofSTime_00321d2c_1"
"","","Egg of Time",Neutral,50,"So you translated this book and it says the Dwarves were destroyed by Lorkhan's heart? That's a very interesting theory, but I don't believe it. In any case, it is not going to help me in my own research.","So you translated this book and it says the Dwarves were destroyed by Lorkhan's heart? That's a very interesting theory, but I don't believe it. In any case, it is not going to help me in my own research.","fbmwMGDwarves_1EggSofSTime_00f8a619_1"
"","","Dwemer Tube",Neutral,50,"Are you still a member of the guild? Once Trebonius gives the authorization, we can discuss guild matters again.","Are you still a member of the guild? Once Trebonius gives the authorization, we can discuss guild matters again.","fbmwMGScience_1DwemerSTube_00321fbc_1"
"","","Dwemer Tube",Neutral,50,"Were you expelled? Or did you clear that up already? You ought to make amends with Guildmaster Trebonius just to be sure.","Were you expelled? Or did you clear that up already? You ought to make amends with Guildmaster Trebonius just to be sure.","fbmwMGScience_1DwemerSTube_00321fbd_1"
"","","Dwemer Tube",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled, outlander. If you want to make amends, you should speak with Guildmaster Trebonius.","You have been expelled, outlander. If you want to make amends, you should speak with Guildmaster Trebonius.","fbmwMGScience_1DwemerSTube_00321fbe_1"
"","","Dwemer Tube",Neutral,50,"Your delivery of the Dwemer Tube was commendable.","Your delivery of the Dwemer Tube was commendable.","fbmwMGScience_1DwemerSTube_00f8a655_1"
"","","Dwemer Tube",Neutral,50,"Have you found a Dwemer Tube?","Have you found a Dwemer Tube?","fbmwMGScience_1DwemerSTube_00f8a656_1"
"","","Dwemer Tube",Neutral,50,"Dwemer Tubes shouldn't be too hard to find. Go to Ald Velothi and travel along the coast to the west. You'll cross a bridge and you'll see Arkngthunch-Sturdumz ahead of you. You can't miss it.","Dwemer Tubes shouldn't be too hard to find. Go to Ald Velothi and travel along the coast to the west. You'll cross a bridge and you'll see Arkngthunch-Sturdumz ahead of you. You can't miss it.","fbmwMGScience_1DwemerSTube_00f8a657_1"
"","","Dwemer Tube",Neutral,50,"They're easy enough to find. I believe I saw some in Arkngthunch-Sturdumz when I was last there. Would you be willing to travel there and bring back the Dwemer Tube?","They're easy enough to find. I believe I saw some in Arkngthunch-Sturdumz when I was last there. Would you be willing to travel there and bring back the Dwemer Tube?","fbmwMGScience_1DwemerSTube_00f8a658_1"
"","","Blueprints",Neutral,50,"Are you still a member of the guild? Once Trebonius gives the authorization, we can discuss guild matters again.","Are you still a member of the guild? Once Trebonius gives the authorization, we can discuss guild matters again.","fbmwMGBethamez_1blueprints_00f8a67a_1"
"","","Blueprints",Neutral,50,"Were you expelled? Or did you clear that up already? You ought to make amends with Guildmaster Trebonius just to be sure.","Were you expelled? Or did you clear that up already? You ought to make amends with Guildmaster Trebonius just to be sure.","fbmwMGBethamez_1blueprints_00322288_1"
"","","Blueprints",Neutral,50,"Both of these plans seem to be for some kind of metal insect. I do not know what to make of them yet. I will keep you fully informed of any discoveries.","Both of these plans seem to be for some kind of metal insect. I do not know what to make of them yet. I will keep you fully informed of any discoveries.","fbmwMGBethamez_1blueprints_00f8a67b_1"
"","","Blueprints",Neutral,50,"I believe there are more blueprints in Bethamez.","I believe there are more blueprints in Bethamez.","fbmwMGBethamez_1blueprints_00f8a67c_1"
"","","Blueprints",Neutral,50,"Are you still a member of the guild? Once Trebonius gives the authorization, we can discuss guild matters again.","Are you still a member of the guild? Once Trebonius gives the authorization, we can discuss guild matters again.","fbmwMGMzuleft_1blueprints_00322287_1"
"","","Blueprints",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled, outlander. If you want to make amends, you should speak with Guildmaster Trebonius.","You have been expelled, outlander. If you want to make amends, you should speak with Guildmaster Trebonius.","fbmwMGMzuleft_1blueprints_00322289_1"
"","","Blueprints",Neutral,50,"They seem to be the plans for some kind of large metal insect. I will have to study them further.","They seem to be the plans for some kind of large metal insect. I will have to study them further.","fbmwMGMzuleft_1blueprints_00f8a67d_1"
"","","Blueprints",Neutral,50,"Well, have you found any Dwemer plans yet?","Well, have you found any Dwemer plans yet?","fbmwMGMzuleft_1blueprints_00f8a67e_1"
"","","Blueprints",Neutral,50,"Senilias already sent the blueprints he found in Nchuleftingth to the Emperor... But the excavation report mentioned Mzuleft, which is southwest of Dagon Fel.","Senilias already sent the blueprints he found in Nchuleftingth to the Emperor... But the excavation report mentioned Mzuleft, which is southwest of Dagon Fel.","fbmwMGMzuleft_1blueprints_00f8a67f_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You will need to swim or fly across parts of the Sea of Ghosts. Bring back any plans or blueprints you find.","You will need to swim or fly across parts of the Sea of Ghosts. Bring back any plans or blueprints you find.","fbmwMGMzuleft_1blueprints_00f8a67f_2"
"","","Trebonius",Neutral,50,"The Guildmaster? Well, he's certainly a powerful Battlemage, but what has he accomplished?","The Guildmaster? Well, he's certainly a powerful Battlemage, but what has he accomplished?","MorroDefaultQuest_1Trebonius_00322482_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I wish the Guild were led by someone who showed more respect for scholarship...","I wish the Guild were led by someone who showed more respect for scholarship...","MorroDefaultQuest_1Trebonius_00322482_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Especially with all the interesting things to study here in Vvardenfell.","Especially with all the interesting things to study here in Vvardenfell.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Trebonius_00322482_3"
"","","Bethamez",Neutral,50,"Are you still a member of the guild? Once Trebonius gives the authorization, we can discuss guild matters again.","Are you still a member of the guild? Once Trebonius gives the authorization, we can discuss guild matters again.","fbmwMGBethamez_1Bethamez_003226ff_1"
"","","Bethamez",Neutral,50,"Were you expelled? Or did you clear that up already? You ought to make amends with Guildmaster Trebonius just to be sure.","Were you expelled? Or did you clear that up already? You ought to make amends with Guildmaster Trebonius just to be sure.","fbmwMGBethamez_1Bethamez_00322700_1"
"","","Bethamez",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled, outlander. If you want to make amends, you should speak with Guildmaster Trebonius.","You have been expelled, outlander. If you want to make amends, you should speak with Guildmaster Trebonius.","fbmwMGBethamez_1Bethamez_00322701_1"
"","","Bethamez",Neutral,50,"Someday your work in Dwemer archeology may surpass even myself or Hasphat Antabolis.","Someday your work in Dwemer archeology may surpass even myself or Hasphat Antabolis.","fbmwMGBethamez_1Bethamez_00f8a72f_1"
"","","Bethamez",Neutral,50,"Have you found any more Dwemer plans or blueprints?","Have you found any more Dwemer plans or blueprints?","fbmwMGBethamez_1Bethamez_00f8a730_1"
"","","Bethamez",Neutral,50,"Officially, the Gnisis eggmine was closed because of blight, but I heard that miners broke into the lost Dwemer ruin of Bethamez.","Officially, the Gnisis eggmine was closed because of blight, but I heard that miners broke into the lost Dwemer ruin of Bethamez.","fbmwMGBethamez_1Bethamez_00322707_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I have also heard that they found Dwemer plans similar to the blueprints you brought me before.","I have also heard that they found Dwemer plans similar to the blueprints you brought me before.","fbmwMGBethamez_1Bethamez_00322707_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Go to the Gnisis eggmine and bring back any plans or blueprints you find.","Go to the Gnisis eggmine and bring back any plans or blueprints you find.","fbmwMGBethamez_1Bethamez_00322707_3"
"","","Duties",Neutral,50,"Why, it would be inappropriate for me to give you orders, Arch-Mage.","Why, it would be inappropriate for me to give you orders, Arch-Mage.","fbmwMGAdvancement_1duties_00f8a7ec_1"
"","","Duties",Neutral,50,"It's a shame the Mages Guild isn't led by someone with your devotion to Scholarship. Perhaps if you speak with Trebonius, you can make him listen to reason.","It's a shame the Mages Guild isn't led by someone with your devotion to Scholarship. Perhaps if you speak with Trebonius, you can make him listen to reason.","fbmwMGAdvancement_1duties_00f8a7ed_1"
"","","Duties",Neutral,50,"I do not have any more duties for you. Perhaps you should speak with the guild stewards in Balmora or Sadrith Mora.","I do not have any more duties for you. Perhaps you should speak with the guild stewards in Balmora or Sadrith Mora.","fbmwMGAdvancement_1duties_00f8a7ee_1"
"","","Duties",Neutral,50,"I have heard that the miners in the Gnisis Eggmine broke into the ruins of Bethamez.","I have heard that the miners in the Gnisis Eggmine broke into the ruins of Bethamez.","fbmwMGAdvancement_1duties_00f8a7ef_1"
"","","Duties",Neutral,50,"I want you to find some Dwemer plans or blueprints.","I want you to find some Dwemer plans or blueprints.","fbmwMGAdvancement_1duties_00f8a7f0_1"
"","","Duties",Neutral,50,"Yes, I was wondering if you might check up on one of my colleagues in the Dwemer ruin of Nchuleftingth. The last excavation report is long overdue...","Yes, I was wondering if you might check up on one of my colleagues in the Dwemer ruin of Nchuleftingth. The last excavation report is long overdue...","fbmwMGAdvancement_1duties_00f8a7f1_1"
"","","Duties",Neutral,50,"I'm so glad you asked. At this delicate phase of my research, I need to study a Dwemer Tube.","I'm so glad you asked. At this delicate phase of my research, I need to study a Dwemer Tube.","fbmwMGAdvancement_1duties_00f8a7f2_1"
"","","Duties",Neutral,50,"I have no duties for you now, but speak with me again when you have earned the rank of Conjurer.","I have no duties for you now, but speak with me again when you have earned the rank of Conjurer.","fbmwMGAdvancement_1duties_00f8a7f3_1"
"","","Duties",Neutral,50,"Yes, I have finished my study of Chimarvamidium.","Yes, I have finished my study of Chimarvamidium.","fbmwMGAdvancement_1duties_00f8a7f4_1"
"","","Duties",Neutral,50,"I have been distracted from my studies by several reports from Maar Gan. Apparently there is some sort of disturbance at Huleen's hut.","I have been distracted from my studies by several reports from Maar Gan. Apparently there is some sort of disturbance at Huleen's hut.","fbmwMGAdvancement_1duties_00f8a7f5_1"
"","","Duties",Neutral,50,"Sirilonwe in the Mages Guild in Vivec has somehow acquired a copy of Chimarvamidium.","Sirilonwe in the Mages Guild in Vivec has somehow acquired a copy of Chimarvamidium.","fbmwMGAdvancement_1duties_00f8a7f6_1"
"","","Duties",Neutral,50,"I have been waiting for *ages* to get a Detect Creatures potion from Skink-in-Tree's-Shade in Sadrith Mora.","I have been waiting for *ages* to get a Detect Creatures potion from Skink-in-Tree's-Shade in Sadrith Mora.","fbmwMGAdvancement_1duties_00f8a7f7_1"
"","","Duties",Neutral,50,"Yes, there is something you could do for me. I am looking for a copy of the rare Dwarven book, Chronicles of Nchuleft.","Yes, there is something you could do for me. I am looking for a copy of the rare Dwarven book, Chronicles of Nchuleft.","fbmwMGAdvancement_1duties_00322bc0_1"
"","","Duties",Neutral,50,"Speak with Edwinna. She's the guild steward here.","Speak with Edwinna. She's the guild steward here.","fbmwMGAdvancement_1duties_00322bcd_1"
"","","Give her the potion.",Neutral,50,"Excellent. Why don't I give you a potion more useful in the field?","Excellent. Why don't I give you a potion more useful in the field?","fbmwMGPotion_1DetectSCreaturesSPotion1_00322f44_1"
"","","Give her the potion.",Neutral,50,"Oh? Where is the potion? Do you have it with you?","Oh? Where is the potion? Do you have it with you?","fbmwMGPotion_1DetectSCreaturesSPotion1_00322f45_1"
"","","Keep the potion.",Neutral,50,"Unlike a proper member, you do not keep your word.","Unlike a proper member, you do not keep your word.","fbmwMGPotion_1DetectSCreaturesSPotion2_00322f46_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I certainly am not going to give you any more duties until you deliver a Detect Creatures potion to me.","I certainly am not going to give you any more duties until you deliver a Detect Creatures potion to me.","fbmwMGPotion_1DetectSCreaturesSPotion2_00322f46_2"
"","","Keep the potion.",Neutral,50,"Unlike a proper member, you do not keep your word.","Unlike a proper member, you do not keep your word.","fbmwMGPotion_1DetectSCreaturesSPotion2_00322f47_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I certainly am not going to give you any more duties until you deliver a Detect Creatures potion to me.","I certainly am not going to give you any more duties until you deliver a Detect Creatures potion to me.","fbmwMGPotion_1DetectSCreaturesSPotion2_00322f47_2"
"","","Yes.",Neutral,0,"Excellent. Here's 250 septims to cover your expenses. Time is of the essence.","Excellent. Here's 250 septims to cover your expenses. Time is of the essence.","fbmwMGNchuleftBook_1ChroniclesSofSNchuleft1_00004be4_0"
"","","No.",Neutral,50,"I guess I'll have to get Bribanne Erien to do it.","I guess I'll have to get Bribanne Erien to do it.","fbmwMGNchuleftBook_1ChroniclesSofSNchuleft2_00322f90_1"
"","","Give her the book.",Neutral,50,"I'm impressed, outlander. I hope you are always this efficient.","I'm impressed, outlander. I hope you are always this efficient.","fbmwMGNchuleftBook_1ChroniclesSofSNchuleft3_00322f91_1"
"","","Keep the book.",Neutral,50,"I thought we had an agreement, outlander. Apparently your word cannot be trusted.","I thought we had an agreement, outlander. Apparently your word cannot be trusted.","fbmwMGNchuleftBook_1ChroniclesSofSNchuleft4_00322f92_1"
"","","Give her the book.",Neutral,50,"Yes! This is what I've been looking for. I suppose you wouldn't be willing to part with it... Let me just make a few notes, then... There.","Yes! This is what I've been looking for. I suppose you wouldn't be willing to part with it... Let me just make a few notes, then... There.","MorroDefaultQuest_1DwemerSAnimunculi1_0032312d_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I now have most of what I need to make my own centurions. You've made me... that is, us, famous. Wait until I tell Ocato.","I now have most of what I need to make my own centurions. You've made me... that is, us, famous. Wait until I tell Ocato.","MorroDefaultQuest_1DwemerSAnimunculi1_0032312d_2"
"","","Keep the book.",Neutral,50,"How can you do this to me?! I've spent my whole life looking for this!!","How can you do this to me?! I've spent my whole life looking for this!!","MorroDefaultQuest_1DwemerSAnimunculi2_00007a88_1"
"","","Yes, here it is.",Neutral,50,"Thank you, outlander. This report will be helpful, I'm sure.","Thank you, outlander. This report will be helpful, I'm sure.","fbmwMGExcavation_1excavationSreport1_00323132_1"
"","","Yes, here it is.",Neutral,50,"Well, where is it? I don't see any excavation report.","Well, where is it? I don't see any excavation report.","fbmwMGExcavation_1excavationSreport1_00323133_1"
"","","No, not yet.",Neutral,50,"I need that report. I cannot work with all these meaningless delays.","I need that report. I cannot work with all these meaningless delays.","fbmwMGExcavation_1excavationSreport2_00f8ab8b_1"
"","","Give her the book.",Neutral,50,"Thank you, outlander. I will return the book to you soon, but in the meantime, I have more duties for you.","Thank you, outlander. I will return the book to you soon, but in the meantime, I have more duties for you.","fbmwMGStealBook_1Chimarvamidium1_00323322_1"
"","","Keep the book.",Neutral,50,"That is very disappointing, outlander.","That is very disappointing, outlander.","fbmwMGStealBook_1Chimarvamidium2_00323324_1"
"","","Yes.",Neutral,50,"Thank you, outlander. Sirilonwe probably keeps the book near her in the Mages Guild in Vivec.","Thank you, outlander. Sirilonwe probably keeps the book near her in the Mages Guild in Vivec.","fbmwMGStealBook_1Chimarvamidium3_00323326_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Do whatever it takes to get the book and then return it to me. If you're caught stealing, of course, it is a crime against the guild, so be careful.","Do whatever it takes to get the book and then return it to me. If you're caught stealing, of course, it is a crime against the guild, so be careful.","fbmwMGStealBook_1Chimarvamidium3_00323326_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And take these scrolls just in case.","And take these scrolls just in case.","fbmwMGStealBook_1Chimarvamidium3_00323326_3"
"","","No.",Neutral,50,"Don't think of it as breaking your oath to the Guild, outlander. It is just a small favor. For the advancement of the art and science of magic.","Don't think of it as breaking your oath to the Guild, outlander. It is just a small favor. For the advancement of the art and science of magic.","fbmwMGStealBook_1Chimarvamidium4_00323327_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If you're caught, of course, you will have to accept the consequences.","If you're caught, of course, you will have to accept the consequences.","fbmwMGStealBook_1Chimarvamidium4_00323327_2"
"","","I killed the little runt.",Neutral,50,"You what?! You killed Listien? I don't care what he summoned. The Mages Guild does not kill its own members, except in a few rare and extreme cases.","You what?! You killed Listien? I don't care what he summoned. The Mages Guild does not kill its own members, except in a few rare and extreme cases.","fbmwMGApprentice_1HuleenAsShut3_00323415_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I will see that you are expelled for this.","I will see that you are expelled for this.","fbmwMGApprentice_1HuleenAsShut3_00323415_2"
"","","He summoned a Scamp and it killed him.",Neutral,50,"That is unfortunate. If he could summon as scamp with such little training, he had promise.","That is unfortunate. If he could summon as scamp with such little training, he had promise.","fbmwMGApprentice_1HuleenAsShut4_00323416_1"
"","","He summoned a Scamp and it killed him.",Neutral,50,"I might believe that story if I knew you better. What did you really find at Huleen's hut?","I might believe that story if I knew you better. What did you really find at Huleen's hut?","fbmwMGApprentice_1HuleenAsShut4_00323417_1"
"","","Yes.",Neutral,50,"Excellent, outlander. Go to Maar Gan. I'm sure someone there can give you further directions.","Excellent, outlander. Go to Maar Gan. I'm sure someone there can give you further directions.","fbmwMGApprentice_1HuleenAsShut1_00323418_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Take care of this for me so I can continue my studies in peace.","Take care of this for me so I can continue my studies in peace.","fbmwMGApprentice_1HuleenAsShut1_00323418_2"
"","","No.",Neutral,50,"Well, maybe Tarandur can do it. I'll ask next time I see him. You're not the only one we have, you know.","Well, maybe Tarandur can do it. I'll ask next time I see him. You're not the only one we have, you know.","fbmwMGApprentice_1HuleenAsShut2_00323419_1"
"","","No.",Neutral,50,"Well, maybe Tarandur can do it. I'll ask next time I see him. You're not the only one we have, you know.","Well, maybe Tarandur can do it. I'll ask next time I see him. You're not the only one we have, you know.","fbmwMGApprentice_1HuleenAsShut2_0032341a_1"
"","","Give her the Dwemer Tube.",Neutral,50,"Yes, this is what I wanted. Now I can finally study these "bthurkz" the Dwarves wrote about. I am impressed by your dedication to scholarship.","Yes, this is what I wanted. Now I can finally study these "bthurkz" the Dwarves wrote about. I am impressed by your dedication to scholarship.","fbmwMGScience_1DwemerSTube1_003234bb_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Good work, outlander.","Good work, outlander.","fbmwMGScience_1DwemerSTube1_003234bb_2"
"","","Keep the Dwemer Tube.",Neutral,50,"It is not a toy, outlander. It is a valuable Dwemer artifact that is simply essential to my research.","It is not a toy, outlander. It is a valuable Dwemer artifact that is simply essential to my research.","fbmwMGScience_1DwemerSTube2_003234bc_1"
"","","Yes.",Neutral,50,"I appreciate your dedication, outlander. Arkngthunch-Sturdumz is northwest of Gnisis, but there's an easier way to get there.","I appreciate your dedication, outlander. Arkngthunch-Sturdumz is northwest of Gnisis, but there's an easier way to get there.","fbmwMGScience_1DwemerSTube3_003234bd_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Go to Ald Velothi and follow the coast to the west.","Go to Ald Velothi and follow the coast to the west.","fbmwMGScience_1DwemerSTube3_003234bd_2"
"","","No.",Neutral,50,"I'm disappointed, outlander. You are obviously not truly dedicated to research. If you're concerned about Imperial Law, there's no need to worry.","I'm disappointed, outlander. You are obviously not truly dedicated to research. If you're concerned about Imperial Law, there's no need to worry.","fbmwMGScience_1DwemerSTube4_003234be_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I will, of course, turn the device over to the Chair of Dwemer Studies... just as soon as I've finished my research.","I will, of course, turn the device over to the Chair of Dwemer Studies... just as soon as I've finished my research.","fbmwMGScience_1DwemerSTube4_003234be_2"
"","","Give her the plans.",Neutral,50,"Yes, this is exactly what I was looking for. Excellent work, outlander.","Yes, this is exactly what I was looking for. Excellent work, outlander.","fbmwMGMzuleft_1blueprints1_00323524_1"
"","","Give her the plans.",Neutral,50,"Did you drop them on the way back? Where are they?","Did you drop them on the way back? Where are they?","fbmwMGMzuleft_1blueprints1_00323525_1"
"","","Keep the plans.",Neutral,50,"If you refuse to hand the blueprints over, I will have no choice but to report this to the rest of the Mages Guild and the Imperial Authorities.","If you refuse to hand the blueprints over, I will have no choice but to report this to the rest of the Mages Guild and the Imperial Authorities.","fbmwMGMzuleft_1blueprints2_00323526_1"
"","","Yes, here they are.",Neutral,50,"This is truly remarkable. These plans are very similar. Perhaps with both of them in my possession, I can discover their secrets. It's a shame Arch Trebonius doesn't share your dedication to scholarship.","This is truly remarkable. These plans are very similar. Perhaps with both of them in my possession, I can discover their secrets. It's a shame Arch Trebonius doesn't share your dedication to scholarship.","fbmwMGBethamez_1Bethamez1_00f8abac_1"
"","","Yes, here they are.",Neutral,50,"Well, where are they? Didn't you bring the plans with you?","Well, where are they? Didn't you bring the plans with you?","fbmwMGBethamez_1Bethamez1_00f8abad_1"
"","","No, not yet.",Neutral,50,"I understand the temptations of scholarship, but this is not the time to joke around.","I understand the temptations of scholarship, but this is not the time to joke around.","fbmwMGBethamez_1Bethamez2_00f8abae_1"
