Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I haven't seen your face around here before. Would you like a little advice? Or are you looking for someone in particular?","I haven't seen your face around here before. Would you like a little advice? Or are you looking for someone in particular?","fbmwMSGreetings_GREETING_0001010c_1"
"","","Little Advice",Neutral,50,"You look like you can take care of yourself. Then why don't you do something about those smugglers in Addamasartus cave?","You look like you can take care of yourself. Then why don't you do something about those smugglers in Addamasartus cave?","MorroDefaultQuest_1littleSadvice_00321889_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"It's right over there near the silt strider port. Yet these guards! Look at them. Just strutting around.","It's right over there near the silt strider port. Yet these guards! Look at them. Just strutting around.","MorroDefaultQuest_1littleSadvice_00321889_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Someone must have paid them to ignore the smuggling going on here.","Someone must have paid them to ignore the smuggling going on here.","MorroDefaultQuest_1littleSadvice_00321889_3"
"","","Slavery",Neutral,50,"It's shameful in this day and age. But it's legal here in Morrowind. Many Dark Elves own Argonian and Khajiit slaves. Their treatment is disgraceful.","It's shameful in this day and age. But it's legal here in Morrowind. Many Dark Elves own Argonian and Khajiit slaves. Their treatment is disgraceful.","MorroDefaultQuest_1slavery_00322ad5_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You would think the practice would die out as Morrowind adopts Imperial ways, but the natives persist in their cruel and barbaric 'traditions'.","You would think the practice would die out as Morrowind adopts Imperial ways, but the natives persist in their cruel and barbaric 'traditions'.","MorroDefaultQuest_1slavery_00322ad5_2"
"","","Slaves",Neutral,50,"You didn't know that slavery was legal in Morrowind?","You didn't know that slavery was legal in Morrowind?","MorroDefaultQuest_1slaves_00322b41_1"
