Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","-Travel",Neutral,50,"May I teleport you to another guild?","May I teleport you to another guild?","mwServices_AAADestination_00f8b226_1"
"","","Destination",Neutral,50,"I can teleport you instantly from our Mages Guild here in Caldera to the Vivec Mages Guild, or the Ald'ruhn Mages Guild, or the Balmora Mages Guild, or the Sadrith Mora Mages Guild.","I can teleport you instantly from our Mages Guild here in Caldera to the Vivec Mages Guild, or the Ald'ruhn Mages Guild, or the Balmora Mages Guild, or the Sadrith Mora Mages Guild.","MorroDefaultQuest_1destination_00321ef8_1"
