Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Attack on Guar Hide Trader",Neutral,50,"You are suggesting we have done this thing? That is fine, for it is true.","You are suggesting we have done this thing? That is fine, for it is true.","fbmwMVOutcastAshlanders_1attackSonSaSguarShideStrader_003203f6_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Kashtes and I have taken the hides, and in our possession they will remain. Prepare to meet your gods, for no one may take what is now ours.","Kashtes and I have taken the hides, and in our possession they will remain. Prepare to meet your gods, for no one may take what is now ours.","fbmwMVOutcastAshlanders_1attackSonSaSguarShideStrader_003203f6_2"
