Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Telvanni Hortator",Neutral,50,"I think a Hortator is a special champion and war leader among the Great Houses. House Telvanni unites under a Telvanni Hortator in times of war.","I think a Hortator is a special champion and war leader among the Great Houses. House Telvanni unites under a Telvanni Hortator in times of war.","fbmwMQ10_1TelvanniSHortator_00025afd_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Or something like that. Why?","Or something like that. Why?","fbmwMQ10_1TelvanniSHortator_00025afd_2"
"","","Baladas",Neutral,50,"Baladas Demnevanni is my patron. I speak for him on the Telvanni Council. If you have business with him, you should visit Arvs Drelen in Gnisis.","Baladas Demnevanni is my patron. I speak for him on the Telvanni Council. If you have business with him, you should visit Arvs Drelen in Gnisis.","fbmwHTBaladasAlly_1Baladas_00322a66_1"
"","","Baladas",Neutral,50,"Baladas Demnevanni is my patron. I speak for him on the Telvanni Council. If you have business with him, you should visit Arvs Drelen in Gnisis.","Baladas Demnevanni is my patron. I speak for him on the Telvanni Council. If you have business with him, you should visit Arvs Drelen in Gnisis.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Baladas_00322a71_1"
"","","Patron",Neutral,50,"I do not think my own patron, Baladas Demnevanni, would be able to sponsor another, but you can ask him if you want.","I do not think my own patron, Baladas Demnevanni, would be able to sponsor another, but you can ask him if you want.","fbmwHTAdvancement_1patron_00322b6d_1"
"","","How is a Hortator chosen?",Neutral,50,"I'm not sure. I think I recall that all the Telvanni councilors must vote to choose a Hortator, and the vote must be unanimous. Why?","I'm not sure. I think I recall that all the Telvanni councilors must vote to choose a Hortator, and the vote must be unanimous. Why?","fbmwMQ10_1TelvanniSHortator1_003230d6_1"
"","","Tell your story and ask to be confirmed as Hortator.",Neutral,50,"You'll have to speak directly to Master Baladas about this. I can't help you. This is too important for me to act without his approval.","You'll have to speak directly to Master Baladas about this. I can't help you. This is too important for me to act without his approval.","fbmwMQTelvanniBaladas_1TelvanniSHortator2_003230e2_1"
