Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Investigate a crime",Neutral,50,"I know what I am accused of, and I know that it is a lie! I have no need for the furs of Rigmor Halfhand. I am a Skaal warrior. My honor and the honor of the Skaal are my life. But I will bear this injustice as any warrior should--with dignity.","I know what I am accused of, and I know that it is a lie! I have no need for the furs of Rigmor Halfhand. I am a Skaal warrior. My honor and the honor of the Skaal are my life. But I will bear this injustice as any warrior should--with dignity.","fbmwBMTrial_1investigateSaScrime_00f8b1e7_1"
"","","Engar Ice-Mane",Neutral,50,"I am Engar Ice-Mane, warrior of the Skaal.","I am Engar Ice-Mane, warrior of the Skaal.","MorroDefaultQuest_1EngarSIceTMane_0032157a_1"
"","","Risi Ice-Mane",Neutral,50,"She is my wife, a wise and beautiful woman.","She is my wife, a wise and beautiful woman.","MorroDefaultQuest_1RisiSIceTMane_00321a85_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Her life is not an easy one, as I am often gone for weeks on a hunt, but she is strong, and our children will be fine warriors.","Her life is not an easy one, as I am often gone for weeks on a hunt, but she is strong, and our children will be fine warriors.","MorroDefaultQuest_1RisiSIceTMane_00321a85_2"
