Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Have you killed Feruren Oran? Are you ready to join the Morag Tong?","Have you killed Feruren Oran? Are you ready to join the Morag Tong?","fbmwMTWritOran_GREETING_00f2a3fc_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Welcome, in finding this place you have shown your potential to me. If you wish, you may request to join the Morag Tong.","Welcome, in finding this place you have shown your potential to me. If you wish, you may request to join the Morag Tong.","fbmwMTWritOran_GREETING_00f2a3fd_1"
"","","Sanguine Impaling Thrust",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSImpalingSThrust_003204c2_1"
"","","Sanguine Impaling Thrust",Neutral,50,"You have in your possession the Belt of Sanguine Impaling Thrust, one of Mephala's Threads.","You have in your possession the Belt of Sanguine Impaling Thrust, one of Mephala's Threads.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSImpalingSThrust_003204c3_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Will you deliver the belt back to the service of the Morag Tong?","Will you deliver the belt back to the service of the Morag Tong?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSImpalingSThrust_003204c3_2"
"","","Sanguine Impaling Thrust",Neutral,50,"You have returned the Belt of Sanguine Impaling Thrust.","You have returned the Belt of Sanguine Impaling Thrust.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSImpalingSThrust_00f8ce1d_1"
"","","Sanguine Balanced Armor",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSBalancedSArmor_00f8ce1e_1"
"","","Sanguine Balanced Armor",Neutral,50,"I see you have the Belt of Sanguine Balanced Armor, one of the Threads of the Webspinner that Mephala dedicated to our cause long ago.","I see you have the Belt of Sanguine Balanced Armor, one of the Threads of the Webspinner that Mephala dedicated to our cause long ago.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSBalancedSArmor_003204ff_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Will you return this Thread to the custody of the Morag Tong?","Will you return this Thread to the custody of the Morag Tong?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSBalancedSArmor_003204ff_2"
"","","Sanguine Balanced Armor",Neutral,50,"You have returned the Belt of Sanguine Balanced Armor.","You have returned the Belt of Sanguine Balanced Armor.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSBalancedSArmor_00f8ce1f_1"
"","","Sanguine Sublime Wisdom",Neutral,50,"You have returned the Ring of Sanguine Sublime Wisdom.","You have returned the Ring of Sanguine Sublime Wisdom.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSublimeSWisdom_00f2a3fe_1"
"","","Sanguine Sublime Wisdom",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSublimeSWisdom_00320508_1"
"","","Sanguine Sublime Wisdom",Neutral,50,"So you have found the Ring of Sanguine Sublime Wisdom. Is it time for this ring to be reunited with its brothers in Mephala's service?","So you have found the Ring of Sanguine Sublime Wisdom. Is it time for this ring to be reunited with its brothers in Mephala's service?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSublimeSWisdom_00f2a3ff_1"
"","","Sanguine Sublime Wisdom",Neutral,50,"The Ring of Sanguine Sublime Wisdom is held by Anel Rethelas.","The Ring of Sanguine Sublime Wisdom is held by Anel Rethelas.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSublimeSWisdom_00f2a400_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"He may be found in the Daedric ruins of Yasammidan west of Ald Velothi, past the Dwemer ruins.","He may be found in the Daedric ruins of Yasammidan west of Ald Velothi, past the Dwemer ruins.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSublimeSWisdom_00f2a400_2"
"","","Sanguine Fluid Evasion",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSFluidSEvasion_00320647_1"
"","","Sanguine Fluid Evasion",Neutral,50,"So you have the Ring of Sanguine Fluid Evasion. Will you deliver this ring to Mephala's service?","So you have the Ring of Sanguine Fluid Evasion. Will you deliver this ring to Mephala's service?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSFluidSEvasion_00320648_1"
"","","Sanguine Fluid Evasion",Neutral,50,"You have returned the Ring of Sanguine Fluid Evasion.","You have returned the Ring of Sanguine Fluid Evasion.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSFluidSEvasion_00f8ce20_1"
"","","Sanguine Unseen Wisdom",Neutral,50,"I see you have the Ring of Sanguine Unseen Wisdom, one of the Threads of the Webspinner that Mephala dedicated to our cause long ago.","I see you have the Ring of Sanguine Unseen Wisdom, one of the Threads of the Webspinner that Mephala dedicated to our cause long ago.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSUnseenSWisdom_00320660_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Will you return this Thread to the custody of the Morag Tong?","Will you return this Thread to the custody of the Morag Tong?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSUnseenSWisdom_00320660_2"
"","","Sanguine Unseen Wisdom",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSUnseenSWisdom_0032065f_1"
"","","Sanguine Unseen Wisdom",Neutral,50,"You have returned the Ring of Sanguine Unseen Wisdom.","You have returned the Ring of Sanguine Unseen Wisdom.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSUnseenSWisdom_00f8ce21_1"
"","","Sanguine Transfiguring",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSTransfiguring_00320525_1"
"","","Sanguine Transfiguring",Neutral,50,"So you have the Ring of Sanguine Transfiguring. Will you deliver this ring to Mephala's service?","So you have the Ring of Sanguine Transfiguring. Will you deliver this ring to Mephala's service?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSTransfiguring_00320526_1"
"","","Sanguine Transfiguring",Neutral,50,"You have returned the Ring of Sanguine Transfiguring.","You have returned the Ring of Sanguine Transfiguring.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSTransfiguring_00f8ce22_1"
"","","Sanguine Golden Wisdom",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSGoldenSWisdom_0032052c_1"
"","","Sanguine Golden Wisdom",Neutral,50,"So you have the Ring of Sanguine Golden Wisdom. Will you deliver this ring to Mephala's service?","So you have the Ring of Sanguine Golden Wisdom. Will you deliver this ring to Mephala's service?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSGoldenSWisdom_0032052d_1"
"","","Sanguine Golden Wisdom",Neutral,50,"You have returned the Ring of Sanguine Golden Wisdom.","You have returned the Ring of Sanguine Golden Wisdom.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSGoldenSWisdom_00f8ce23_1"
"","","Sanguine Martial Craft",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSMartialSCraft_00320533_1"
"","","Sanguine Martial Craft",Neutral,50,"So you have found the Belt of Sanguine Martial Craft, another Thread of the Webspinner. Are you ready to return the belt to Mephala's black hands?","So you have found the Belt of Sanguine Martial Craft, another Thread of the Webspinner. Are you ready to return the belt to Mephala's black hands?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSMartialSCraft_00320534_1"
"","","Sanguine Martial Craft",Neutral,50,"You have returned the Belt of Sanguine Martial Craft.","You have returned the Belt of Sanguine Martial Craft.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSMartialSCraft_00f8ce24_1"
"","","Sanguine Silver Wisdom",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSilverSWisdom_0032053a_1"
"","","Sanguine Silver Wisdom",Neutral,50,"So you have found the Ring of Sanguine Silver Wisdom, another Thread of the Webspinner. Are you ready to return the ring to Mephala's black hands?","So you have found the Ring of Sanguine Silver Wisdom, another Thread of the Webspinner. Are you ready to return the ring to Mephala's black hands?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSilverSWisdom_0032053b_1"
"","","Sanguine Silver Wisdom",Neutral,50,"You have returned the Ring of Sanguine Silver Wisdom.","You have returned the Ring of Sanguine Silver Wisdom.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSilverSWisdom_00f8ce25_1"
"","","Sanguine Transcendence",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled, but you have the Ring of Sanguine Transcendence, one of the Threads of the Webspinner.","You have been expelled, but you have the Ring of Sanguine Transcendence, one of the Threads of the Webspinner.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSTranscendence_00320541_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Return the ring to me so that it may once again be dedicated to Mephala's service.","Return the ring to me so that it may once again be dedicated to Mephala's service.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSTranscendence_00320541_2"
"","","Sanguine Transcendence",Neutral,50,"You have the Ring of Sanguine Transcendence, one of the Threads of the Webspinner.","You have the Ring of Sanguine Transcendence, one of the Threads of the Webspinner.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSTranscendence_00320542_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Return the ring to me so that it may once again be dedicated to Mephala's service.","Return the ring to me so that it may once again be dedicated to Mephala's service.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSTranscendence_00320542_2"
"","","Sanguine Transcendence",Neutral,50,"You have returned the Ring of Sanguine Transcendence, one of the 27 Threads of the Webspinner.","You have returned the Ring of Sanguine Transcendence, one of the 27 Threads of the Webspinner.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSTranscendence_00f8ce26_1"
"","","Sanguine Green Wisdom",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSGreenSWisdom_003206d3_1"
"","","Sanguine Green Wisdom",Neutral,50,"I see you have the Ring of Sanguine Green Wisdom, one of the Threads of the Webspinner that Mephala dedicated to our cause long ago.","I see you have the Ring of Sanguine Green Wisdom, one of the Threads of the Webspinner that Mephala dedicated to our cause long ago.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSGreenSWisdom_003206d4_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Will you return this Thread to the custody of the Morag Tong?","Will you return this Thread to the custody of the Morag Tong?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSGreenSWisdom_003206d4_2"
"","","Sanguine Green Wisdom",Neutral,50,"You have returned the Ring of Sanguine Green Wisdom.","You have returned the Ring of Sanguine Green Wisdom.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSGreenSWisdom_00f8ce27_1"
"","","Sanguine Stolid Armor",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSStolidSArmor_003206da_1"
"","","Sanguine Stolid Armor",Neutral,50,"I see you have the Belt of Sanguine Stolid Armor, one of the Threads of the Webspinner that Mephala dedicated to our cause long ago.","I see you have the Belt of Sanguine Stolid Armor, one of the Threads of the Webspinner that Mephala dedicated to our cause long ago.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSStolidSArmor_003206db_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Will you return this Thread to the custody of the Morag Tong?","Will you return this Thread to the custody of the Morag Tong?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSStolidSArmor_003206db_2"
"","","Sanguine Stolid Armor",Neutral,50,"You have returned the Belt of Sanguine Stolid Armor.","You have returned the Belt of Sanguine Stolid Armor.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSStolidSArmor_00f8ce28_1"
"","","Sanguine Nimble Armor",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSNimbleSArmor_003206e1_1"
"","","Sanguine Nimble Armor",Neutral,50,"I see you have the Amulet of Sanguine Nimble Armor, one of the Threads of the Webspinner that Mephala dedicated to our cause long ago.","I see you have the Amulet of Sanguine Nimble Armor, one of the Threads of the Webspinner that Mephala dedicated to our cause long ago.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSNimbleSArmor_003206e2_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Will you return this Thread to the custody of the Morag Tong?","Will you return this Thread to the custody of the Morag Tong?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSNimbleSArmor_003206e2_2"
"","","Sanguine Nimble Armor",Neutral,50,"You have returned the Amulet of Sanguine Nimble Armor.","You have returned the Amulet of Sanguine Nimble Armor.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSNimbleSArmor_00f8ce29_1"
"","","Sanguine Deep Biting",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSDeepSBiting_00320781_1"
"","","Sanguine Deep Biting",Neutral,50,"You have in your possession the Belt of Sanguine Deep Biting, one of Mephala's Threads.","You have in your possession the Belt of Sanguine Deep Biting, one of Mephala's Threads.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSDeepSBiting_00320782_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Will you deliver the belt back to the service of the Morag Tong?","Will you deliver the belt back to the service of the Morag Tong?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSDeepSBiting_00320782_2"
"","","Sanguine Deep Biting",Neutral,50,"You have returned the Belt of Sanguine Deep Biting.","You have returned the Belt of Sanguine Deep Biting.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSDeepSBiting_00f8ce2a_1"
"","","Sanguine Glib Speech",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSGlibSSpeech_0032078c_1"
"","","Sanguine Glib Speech",Neutral,50,"So you have found the Amulet of Sanguine Glib Speech. Is it time for this Amulet to be reunited with its brothers in Mephala's service?","So you have found the Amulet of Sanguine Glib Speech. Is it time for this Amulet to be reunited with its brothers in Mephala's service?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSGlibSSpeech_0032078d_1"
"","","Sanguine Glib Speech",Neutral,50,"You have returned the Amulet of Sanguine Glib Speech.","You have returned the Amulet of Sanguine Glib Speech.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSGlibSSpeech_00f8ce2b_1"
"","","Sanguine Safekeeping",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSafekeeping_00320793_1"
"","","Sanguine Safekeeping",Neutral,50,"So you have found the Gloves of Sanguine Safekeeping, another Thread of the Webspinner. Are you ready to return the gloves to Mephala's black hands?","So you have found the Gloves of Sanguine Safekeeping, another Thread of the Webspinner. Are you ready to return the gloves to Mephala's black hands?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSafekeeping_00320794_1"
"","","Sanguine Safekeeping",Neutral,50,"You have returned the Gloves of Sanguine Safekeeping.","You have returned the Gloves of Sanguine Safekeeping.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSafekeeping_00f8ce2c_1"
"","","Sanguine Enterprise",Neutral,50,"You have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner.","You have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSEnterprise_00320860_1"
"","","Sanguine Enterprise",Neutral,50,"The amulet of Sanguine Enterprise is one of the threads of the Webspinner. I already have this thread. Perhaps you will find other threads.","The amulet of Sanguine Enterprise is one of the threads of the Webspinner. I already have this thread. Perhaps you will find other threads.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSEnterprise_00320861_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"When you do, bring them to me.","When you do, bring them to me.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSEnterprise_00320861_2"
"","","Sanguine Enterprise",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong. I would rather not discuss it.","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong. I would rather not discuss it.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSEnterprise_00f8ce2d_1"
"","","Sanguine Red Wisdom",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSRedSWisdom_00320884_1"
"","","Sanguine Red Wisdom",Neutral,50,"You have in your possession the Ring of Sanguine Red Wisdom, one of Mephala's Threads.","You have in your possession the Ring of Sanguine Red Wisdom, one of Mephala's Threads.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSRedSWisdom_00320885_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Will you deliver the belt back to the service of the Morag Tong?","Will you deliver the belt back to the service of the Morag Tong?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSRedSWisdom_00320885_2"
"","","Sanguine Red Wisdom",Neutral,50,"You have returned the Ring of Sanguine Red Wisdom.","You have returned the Ring of Sanguine Red Wisdom.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSRedSWisdom_00f8ce2e_1"
"","","Sanguine Sureflight",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSureflight_0032088b_1"
"","","Sanguine Sureflight",Neutral,50,"You have in your possession the Belt of Sanguine Sureflight, one of Mephala's Threads.","You have in your possession the Belt of Sanguine Sureflight, one of Mephala's Threads.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSureflight_0032088c_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Will you deliver the belt back to the service of the Morag Tong?","Will you deliver the belt back to the service of the Morag Tong?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSureflight_0032088c_2"
"","","Sanguine Sureflight",Neutral,50,"You have returned the Belt of Sanguine Sureflight.","You have returned the Belt of Sanguine Sureflight.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSureflight_00f8ce2f_1"
"","","Sanguine Horny Fist",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSHornySFist_00320892_1"
"","","Sanguine Horny Fist",Neutral,50,"So you have found the Gloves of Sanguine Horny Fist. Is it time for this glove to be reunited with its brothers in Mephala's service?","So you have found the Gloves of Sanguine Horny Fist. Is it time for this glove to be reunited with its brothers in Mephala's service?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSHornySFist_00320893_1"
"","","Sanguine Horny Fist",Neutral,50,"You have returned the Gloves of Sanguine Horny Fist.","You have returned the Gloves of Sanguine Horny Fist.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSHornySFist_00f8ce30_1"
"","","Sanguine Swiftblade",Neutral,50,"Even though you have been expelled, you have the Gloves of Sanguine Swiftblade, one of the Threads of the Webspinner.","Even though you have been expelled, you have the Gloves of Sanguine Swiftblade, one of the Threads of the Webspinner.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSwiftblade_00320899_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Return the gloves to me so that it may once again be dedicated to Mephala's service.","Return the gloves to me so that it may once again be dedicated to Mephala's service.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSwiftblade_00320899_2"
"","","Sanguine Swiftblade",Neutral,50,"You have the Gloves of Sanguine Swiftblade one of the Threads of the Webspinner.","You have the Gloves of Sanguine Swiftblade one of the Threads of the Webspinner.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSwiftblade_0032089a_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Return the gloves to me so that it may once again be dedicated to Mephala's service.","Return the gloves to me so that it may once again be dedicated to Mephala's service.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSwiftblade_0032089a_2"
"","","Sanguine Swiftblade",Neutral,50,"You have returned the Gloves of Sanguine Swiftblade, one of the 27 Threads of the Webspinner.","You have returned the Gloves of Sanguine Swiftblade, one of the 27 Threads of the Webspinner.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSwiftblade_00f8ce31_1"
"","","Join the Morag Tong",Neutral,50,"So you have found our headquarters. This speaks well of you. Perhaps you should speak with Grandmaster Eno Hlaalu.","So you have found our headquarters. This speaks well of you. Perhaps you should speak with Grandmaster Eno Hlaalu.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1joinStheSMoragSTong_003208f1_1"
"","","Join the Morag Tong",Neutral,50,"By tradition, the Grandmaster of the Morag Tong lives in the Arena Canton here in Vivec.","By tradition, the Grandmaster of the Morag Tong lives in the Arena Canton here in Vivec.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1joinStheSMoragSTong_003208f3_1"
"","","Join the Morag Tong",Neutral,50,"Grandmaster Eno Hlaalu may be found in the Arena Canton here in Vivec.","Grandmaster Eno Hlaalu may be found in the Arena Canton here in Vivec.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1joinStheSMoragSTong_003208f5_1"
"","","Join the Morag Tong",Neutral,50,"I see them from time to time, but I do not know where to find them.","I see them from time to time, but I do not know where to find them.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1joinStheSMoragSTong_003208fa_1"
"","","Join the Morag Tong",Neutral,50,"If you wish to join us, you must seek out Eno Hlaalu, the Grandmaster of the Morag Tong in Vivec.","If you wish to join us, you must seek out Eno Hlaalu, the Grandmaster of the Morag Tong in Vivec.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1joinStheSMoragSTong_003208fb_1"
"","","Join the Morag Tong",Neutral,50,"Feruren Oran is dead? Then welcome, to the Morag Tong.","Feruren Oran is dead? Then welcome, to the Morag Tong.","fbmwMTWritOran_1joinStheSMoragSTong_00f2a409_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Any Master of the Morag Tong can tell you what writs are available and weather you are a candidate for advancement.","Any Master of the Morag Tong can tell you what writs are available and weather you are a candidate for advancement.","fbmwMTWritOran_1joinStheSMoragSTong_00f2a409_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"When you have proven yourself, I will have special duties for you, Writs of execution.","When you have proven yourself, I will have special duties for you, Writs of execution.","fbmwMTWritOran_1joinStheSMoragSTong_00f2a409_3"
"","","Join the Morag Tong",Neutral,50,"I have given you the authority to act in the name of the Morag Tong. You are charged with the honorable execution of Feruren Oran.","I have given you the authority to act in the name of the Morag Tong. You are charged with the honorable execution of Feruren Oran.","fbmwMTWritOran_1joinStheSMoragSTong_00f2a40a_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Succeed and join us. Fail and die.","Succeed and join us. Fail and die.","fbmwMTWritOran_1joinStheSMoragSTong_00f2a40a_2"
"","","Join the Morag Tong",Neutral,50,"The Morag Tong has been watching you, and we are pleased. One of your exceptional talent cannot go unmastered. Join us.","The Morag Tong has been watching you, and we are pleased. One of your exceptional talent cannot go unmastered. Join us.","fbmwMTWritOran_1joinStheSMoragSTong_003208eb_1"
"","","Join the Morag Tong",Neutral,50,"Your skills are weak and your discipline is untempered.","Your skills are weak and your discipline is untempered.","fbmwMTWritOran_1joinStheSMoragSTong_003208ec_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Still, you have found me, so perhaps I will let you ask again when you have something to offer.","Still, you have found me, so perhaps I will let you ask again when you have something to offer.","fbmwMTWritOran_1joinStheSMoragSTong_003208ec_2"
"","","Sanguine Fleetness",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled, outlander. Make amends, and perhaps we will speak again.","You have been expelled, outlander. Make amends, and perhaps we will speak again.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSFleetness_003209ea_1"
"","","Sanguine Fleetness",Neutral,50,"You have returned the Belt of Sanguine Fleetness, but this is only one of the Threads of the Webspinner.","You have returned the Belt of Sanguine Fleetness, but this is only one of the Threads of the Webspinner.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSFleetness_00f2a40b_1"
"","","Sanguine Fleetness",Neutral,50,"You have the Belt of Sanguine Fleetness, one of the Threads of the Webspinner.","You have the Belt of Sanguine Fleetness, one of the Threads of the Webspinner.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSFleetness_00f2a40c_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Now then, return the Belt to me so that it may once again be dedicated to Mephala's service.","Now then, return the Belt to me so that it may once again be dedicated to Mephala's service.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSFleetness_00f2a40c_2"
"","","Sanguine Fleetness",Neutral,50,"Over the years, the Threads of the Webspinner have found the way into the hands of our enemies.","Over the years, the Threads of the Webspinner have found the way into the hands of our enemies.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSFleetness_00f2a40d_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"By Mephala's subtle manipulations, all these Threads shall return to us.","By Mephala's subtle manipulations, all these Threads shall return to us.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSFleetness_00f2a40d_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Hrordis has this belt. She is a Nord, a Sorceress, and a member of the Dark Brotherhood.","Hrordis has this belt. She is a Nord, a Sorceress, and a member of the Dark Brotherhood.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSFleetness_00f2a40d_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Find her in Pelagiad at the Halfway Inn. Return the belt to me.","Find her in Pelagiad at the Halfway Inn. Return the belt to me.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSFleetness_00f2a40d_4"
"","","Sanguine Stalking",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSStalking_00320b83_1"
"","","Sanguine Stalking",Neutral,50,"You have in your possession the Shoes of Sanguine Stalking, one of Mephala's Threads. Will you deliver the shoes to the service of the Morag Tong?","You have in your possession the Shoes of Sanguine Stalking, one of Mephala's Threads. Will you deliver the shoes to the service of the Morag Tong?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSStalking_00320b84_1"
"","","Sanguine Stalking",Neutral,50,"You have returned the Shoes of Sanguine Stalking.","You have returned the Shoes of Sanguine Stalking.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSStalking_00f8ce32_1"
"","","Sanguine Smiting",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSmiting_00320cce_1"
"","","Sanguine Smiting",Neutral,50,"So you have the Belt of Sanguine Smiting. Will you deliver this belt to Mephala's service?","So you have the Belt of Sanguine Smiting. Will you deliver this belt to Mephala's service?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSmiting_00320ccf_1"
"","","Sanguine Smiting",Neutral,50,"You have returned the Belt of Sanguine Smiting.","You have returned the Belt of Sanguine Smiting.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSmiting_00f8ce33_1"
"","","Dark Brotherhood",Neutral,50,"The Dark Brotherhood rebelled against the Morag Tong many years ago. Since then they have been our enemy.","The Dark Brotherhood rebelled against the Morag Tong many years ago. Since then they have been our enemy.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1DarkSBrotherhood_00320cd0_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I want you to speak with Miun-Gei, a Mehrunes Dagon cultist who has an Enchantment shop in the Lower Waistworks of the Foreign Quarter.","I want you to speak with Miun-Gei, a Mehrunes Dagon cultist who has an Enchantment shop in the Lower Waistworks of the Foreign Quarter.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1DarkSBrotherhood_00320cd0_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I believe he knows of a contact in the Dark Brotherhood. When you have taken a name from him, bring that name to me.","I believe he knows of a contact in the Dark Brotherhood. When you have taken a name from him, bring that name to me.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1DarkSBrotherhood_00320cd0_3"
"","","Dark Brotherhood",Neutral,50,"We are still at war with the Dark Brotherhood. Do not forget that.","We are still at war with the Dark Brotherhood. Do not forget that.","fbmwMTDBContact_1DarkSBrotherhood_00f2a417_1"
"","","Dark Brotherhood",Neutral,50,"So Tsrazami was an agent of the Dark Brotherhood. Alas, she left Vvardenfell or is dead. Perhaps we can find another contact.","So Tsrazami was an agent of the Dark Brotherhood. Alas, she left Vvardenfell or is dead. Perhaps we can find another contact.","fbmwMTDBContact_1DarkSBrotherhood_00f2a418_1"
"","","Dark Brotherhood",Neutral,50,"So Tsrazami is an agent of the Dark Brotherhood. And you have already questioned her yourself. I will certainly be interested in meeting her.","So Tsrazami is an agent of the Dark Brotherhood. And you have already questioned her yourself. I will certainly be interested in meeting her.","fbmwMTDBContact_1DarkSBrotherhood_00f2a419_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"At a place and time of my own choosing, of course. Please take these scrolls. I have found them useful at times.","At a place and time of my own choosing, of course. Please take these scrolls. I have found them useful at times.","fbmwMTDBContact_1DarkSBrotherhood_00f2a419_2"
"","","Dark Brotherhood",Neutral,50,"So Tsrazami is an agent of the Dark Brotherhood. You have done well. I will send agents to question Tsrazami.","So Tsrazami is an agent of the Dark Brotherhood. You have done well. I will send agents to question Tsrazami.","fbmwMTDBContact_1DarkSBrotherhood_00f2a41a_1"
"","","Dark Brotherhood",Neutral,50,"That is an interesting note you have there. I believe I know this Tsrazami. I will have agents sent to find her if she still lives.","That is an interesting note you have there. I believe I know this Tsrazami. I will have agents sent to find her if she still lives.","fbmwMTDBContact_1DarkSBrotherhood_00f2a41b_1"
"","","Dark Brotherhood",Neutral,50,"Is Miun-Gei dead? Hm. Try searching his shop. Perhaps you can find some clues there about who his contact was.","Is Miun-Gei dead? Hm. Try searching his shop. Perhaps you can find some clues there about who his contact was.","fbmwMTDBContact_1DarkSBrotherhood_00f2a41c_1"
"","","Sanguine Leaping",Neutral,50,"I see you have the Shoes of Sanguine Leaping, one of the Threads of the Webspinner that Mephala dedicated to our cause long ago.","I see you have the Shoes of Sanguine Leaping, one of the Threads of the Webspinner that Mephala dedicated to our cause long ago.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSLeaping_00320cf4_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Will you return this Thread to the custody of the Morag Tong?","Will you return this Thread to the custody of the Morag Tong?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSLeaping_00320cf4_2"
"","","Sanguine Leaping",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSLeaping_00320cf3_1"
"","","Sanguine Leaping",Neutral,50,"You have returned the Shoes of Sanguine Leaping.","You have returned the Shoes of Sanguine Leaping.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSLeaping_00f8ce34_1"
"","","Sanguine Denial",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSDenial_00320f38_1"
"","","Sanguine Denial",Neutral,50,"So Movis Darys had this belt. Shall it be returned to Mephala's black hands?","So Movis Darys had this belt. Shall it be returned to Mephala's black hands?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSDenial_00320f39_1"
"","","Sanguine Denial",Neutral,50,"You have returned the Belt of Sanguine Denial.","You have returned the Belt of Sanguine Denial.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSDenial_00f8ce35_1"
"","","Sanguine Hewing",Neutral,50,"You have the Belt of Sanguine Hewing, one of the Threads of the Webspinner.","You have the Belt of Sanguine Hewing, one of the Threads of the Webspinner.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSHewing_00320f5e_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Return the Belt to me and it shall once again be dedicated to Mephala's service.","Return the Belt to me and it shall once again be dedicated to Mephala's service.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSHewing_00320f5e_2"
"","","Sanguine Hewing",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But I see you have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Will you return this Thread?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSHewing_00f8ce36_1"
"","","Sanguine Hewing",Neutral,50,"You have returned the Belt of Sanguine Hewing, one of the 27 Threads of the Webspinner.","You have returned the Belt of Sanguine Hewing, one of the 27 Threads of the Webspinner.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSHewing_00f8ce37_1"
"","","Nalvilie Saren",Neutral,50,"Yes, she is 'much blown upon' as the Ashlanders would say. A disgrace... Though I must admit I enjoyed her favors myself many years ago.","Yes, she is 'much blown upon' as the Ashlanders would say. A disgrace... Though I must admit I enjoyed her favors myself many years ago.","fbmwHROldFlame_1NalvilieSSaren_00321515_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"She lives in the St. Olms Canton now. I believe she runs a shop there.","She lives in the St. Olms Canton now. I believe she runs a shop there.","fbmwHROldFlame_1NalvilieSSaren_00321515_2"
"","","Special Duties",Neutral,50,"You're the Grandmaster now,","You're the Grandmaster now,","fbmwMTAdvancement_1specialSduties_00f2a423_1"
"","","Special Duties",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong for breaking our rules. You must make amends if you can.","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong for breaking our rules. You must make amends if you can.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1specialSduties_00f2a424_1"
"","","Special Duties",Neutral,50,"You have the talent and the drive to be the new Grandmaster.","You have the talent and the drive to be the new Grandmaster.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1specialSduties_00f2a425_1"
"","","Special Duties",Neutral,50,"Speak with me again when you are an Exalted Master in the Morag Tong.","Speak with me again when you are an Exalted Master in the Morag Tong.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1specialSduties_00f2a426_1"
"","","Special Duties",Neutral,50,"Many have fought in our private war against the Dark Brotherhood and the cult of Mehrunes Dagon.","Many have fought in our private war against the Dark Brotherhood and the cult of Mehrunes Dagon.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1specialSduties_00f2a427_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Now the Night Mother of the Dark Brotherhood in Vvardenfell has fled to the ruins of Ald Sotha.","Now the Night Mother of the Dark Brotherhood in Vvardenfell has fled to the ruins of Ald Sotha.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1specialSduties_00f2a427_2"
"","","Special Duties",Neutral,50,"One of the leaders of the Dark Brotherhood here in Vvardenfell is Durus Marius. He and his followers have retreated to Assernerairan.","One of the leaders of the Dark Brotherhood here in Vvardenfell is Durus Marius. He and his followers have retreated to Assernerairan.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1specialSduties_00f2a428_1"
"","","Special Duties",Neutral,50,"I do not have any special duties for you, but there may be some Writs for you to execute.","I do not have any special duties for you, but there may be some Writs for you to execute.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1specialSduties_00f2a429_1"
"","","Special Duties",Neutral,50,"I have heard of another Thread of the Webspinner. This one is the Ring of Sanguine Sublime Wisdom.","I have heard of another Thread of the Webspinner. This one is the Ring of Sanguine Sublime Wisdom.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1specialSduties_00f2a42a_1"
"","","Special Duties",Neutral,50,"Worshippers of Mehrunes Dagon here in Morrowind are sheltering members of the Dark Brotherhood.","Worshippers of Mehrunes Dagon here in Morrowind are sheltering members of the Dark Brotherhood.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1specialSduties_00f2a42b_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I want you to speak with one of these cultists, Carecalmo, and give him an ultimatum.","I want you to speak with one of these cultists, Carecalmo, and give him an ultimatum.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1specialSduties_00f2a42b_2"
"","","Special Duties",Neutral,50,"Sometimes an agent of the Dark Brotherhood is honorable enough to join the Morag Tong. One such candidate has come to my attention.","Sometimes an agent of the Dark Brotherhood is honorable enough to join the Morag Tong. One such candidate has come to my attention.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1specialSduties_00f2a42c_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I want you to speak with Movis Darys.","I want you to speak with Movis Darys.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1specialSduties_00f2a42c_2"
"","","Special Duties",Disgust,100,"Many years ago, Black Hands Mephala made a deal with Sanguine for twenty seven tokens she could give to her devoted followers.","Many years ago, Black Hands Mephala made a deal with Sanguine for twenty seven tokens she could give to her devoted followers.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1specialSduties_00f2a42d_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The Dark Brotherhood stole these tokens from us, but Mephala has arranged for them to return here to Vvardenfell one by one.","The Dark Brotherhood stole these tokens from us, but Mephala has arranged for them to return here to Vvardenfell one by one.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1specialSduties_00f2a42d_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I want you to bring me one of these tokens, the Belt of Sanguine Fleetness.","I want you to bring me one of these tokens, the Belt of Sanguine Fleetness.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1specialSduties_00f2a42d_3"
"","","Special Duties",Disgust,100,"Many years ago, Black Hands Mephala made a deal with Sanguine for twenty seven tokens she could give to her devoted followers.","Many years ago, Black Hands Mephala made a deal with Sanguine for twenty seven tokens she could give to her devoted followers.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1specialSduties_00f2a42e_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The Dark Brotherhood stole these tokens from us, but Mephala has arranged for them to return here to Vvardenfell one by one.","The Dark Brotherhood stole these tokens from us, but Mephala has arranged for them to return here to Vvardenfell one by one.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1specialSduties_00f2a42e_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I want you to bring me one of these tokens, the Belt of Sanguine Fleetness.","I want you to bring me one of these tokens, the Belt of Sanguine Fleetness.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1specialSduties_00f2a42e_3"
"","","Special Duties",Neutral,50,"The Dark Brotherhood is operating here in Morrowind. I want you to contact the Dark Brotherhood.","The Dark Brotherhood is operating here in Morrowind. I want you to contact the Dark Brotherhood.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1specialSduties_00f2a42f_1"
"","","Special Duties",Neutral,50,"Come back when you have more experience.","Come back when you have more experience.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1specialSduties_00f2a430_1"
"","","Ashalmimilkala",Neutral,50,"It is a Daedric ruin on an island on the west coast of Vvardenfell.","It is a Daedric ruin on an island on the west coast of Vvardenfell.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Ashalmimilkala_00321485_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Go to Hla Oad and head on the road north until you reach the Stronghold of Hlormaren.","Go to Hla Oad and head on the road north until you reach the Stronghold of Hlormaren.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Ashalmimilkala_00321485_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"When you do, head west to the coast and then south until you see bridges leading to an island. Ashalmimilkala is on that island.","When you do, head west to the coast and then south until you see bridges leading to an island. Ashalmimilkala is on that island.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Ashalmimilkala_00321485_3"
"","","Assernerairan",Neutral,50,"Durus Marius is dead. There is no more to discuss.","Durus Marius is dead. There is no more to discuss.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1Assernerairan_00aa3cd1_1"
"","","Assernerairan",Neutral,50,"So you have already honorably executed Durus Marius. I am pleased that you brought our justice to him as soon as you found him.","So you have already honorably executed Durus Marius. I am pleased that you brought our justice to him as soon as you found him.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1Assernerairan_00aa3cd2_1"
"","","Assernerairan",Neutral,50,"So Durus Marius is dead and the cult in Assernerairan has been crushed. Please take these 2000 drakes as if this were a Writ of Execution.","So Durus Marius is dead and the cult in Assernerairan has been crushed. Please take these 2000 drakes as if this were a Writ of Execution.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1Assernerairan_00aa3cd3_1"
"","","Assernerairan",Neutral,50,"Assernerairan is in the Underworks of the St. Olms Canton here in Vivec City. Find this foul place and honorably execute Durus Marius, the leader of these Mehrunes Dagon cultists.","Assernerairan is in the Underworks of the St. Olms Canton here in Vivec City. Find this foul place and honorably execute Durus Marius, the leader of these Mehrunes Dagon cultists.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1Assernerairan_00aa3cd4_1"
"","","Requirements",Neutral,50,"Swift and agile are the Morag Tong. Silent and unseen they move. Illusions they supply to misdirect their prey.","Swift and agile are the Morag Tong. Silent and unseen they move. Illusions they supply to misdirect their prey.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1Requirements_00321afc_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Close and sure they strike with a blade, or distant and secure they strike from afar with accurate missile fire.","Close and sure they strike with a blade, or distant and secure they strike from afar with accurate missile fire.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1Requirements_00321afc_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Light armor protects them from harm, and the acrobatic discipline finds for them the unseen and unlooked-for path. Have you these virtues?","Light armor protects them from harm, and the acrobatic discipline finds for them the unseen and unlooked-for path. Have you these virtues?","fbmwMTAdvancement_1Requirements_00321afc_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Then, perhaps, your oath and service may please the Morag Tong.","Then, perhaps, your oath and service may please the Morag Tong.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1Requirements_00321afc_4"
"","","Feruren Oran",Neutral,50,"Are you here to report your success? If so, perhaps you can join the Morag Tong.","Are you here to report your success? If so, perhaps you can join the Morag Tong.","fbmwMTWritOran_1FerurenSOran_00321ab3_1"
"","","Feruren Oran",Neutral,50,"He may be found at the Elven Nations Cornerclub in the Hlaalu Plaza here in Vivec. Slay him honorably and you may join the Morag Tong.","He may be found at the Elven Nations Cornerclub in the Hlaalu Plaza here in Vivec. Slay him honorably and you may join the Morag Tong.","fbmwMTWritOran_1FerurenSOran_00321ab4_1"
"","","Advancement",Neutral,50,"You have advanced as far as you can without challenging me, the Grandmaster.","You have advanced as far as you can without challenging me, the Grandmaster.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1Advancement_00322094_1"
"","","Advancement",Neutral,50,"First you must join the Morag Tong.","First you must join the Morag Tong.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1Advancement_00322096_1"
"","","Advancement",Neutral,50,"You have soiled the honor of the Morag Tong. Make amends or you will never be reinstated.","You have soiled the honor of the Morag Tong. Make amends or you will never be reinstated.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1Advancement_00322097_1"
"","","Advancement",Neutral,50,"Honorably execute writs and practice your skills. You are not ready yet.","Honorably execute writs and practice your skills. You are not ready yet.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1Advancement_00322098_1"
"","","Advancement",Neutral,50,"Your technique is superb, but some question your depth of devotion. Perform more honorable executions in the name of the Morag Tong.","Your technique is superb, but some question your depth of devotion. Perform more honorable executions in the name of the Morag Tong.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1Advancement_00322099_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"These writs are currently outstanding.","These writs are currently outstanding.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1Advancement_00322099_2"
"","","Advancement",Neutral,50,"Your honor and devotion to the Morag Tong is unmatched in the guild, but your technique is lacking.","Your honor and devotion to the Morag Tong is unmatched in the guild, but your technique is lacking.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1Advancement_0032209a_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Redouble your training and practice your skills.","Redouble your training and practice your skills.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1Advancement_0032209a_2"
"","","Advancement",Neutral,50,"Excellent, outlander. You are now promoted.","Excellent, outlander. You are now promoted.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1Advancement_0032209b_1"
"","","Grandmaster",Neutral,50,"Yes, I will retire soon. You are the Grandmaster.","Yes, I will retire soon. You are the Grandmaster.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1Grandmaster_00321ebf_1"
"","","Grandmaster",Neutral,50,"Traditionally, the Grandmaster of the Morag Tong is honorably executed by the new Grandmaster. You can certainly fight me if you think you can win...","Traditionally, the Grandmaster of the Morag Tong is honorably executed by the new Grandmaster. You can certainly fight me if you think you can win...","fbmwMTAdvancement_1Grandmaster_00321ec4_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But I am tired. If you allow me to retire peacefully, I will name you the new Grandmaster. No one will question our word.","But I am tired. If you allow me to retire peacefully, I will name you the new Grandmaster. No one will question our word.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1Grandmaster_00321ec4_2"
"","","Ald Sotha",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong. In this dangerous times, I am not sure if you can make amends and regain my trust.","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong. In this dangerous times, I am not sure if you can make amends and regain my trust.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1AldSSotha_00322576_1"
"","","Ald Sotha",Neutral,50,"The Dark Brotherhood can no longer hide from us in Ald Sotha.","The Dark Brotherhood can no longer hide from us in Ald Sotha.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1AldSSotha_0001c686_1"
"","","Ald Sotha",Neutral,50,"The Night Mother is already dead? You have done well,&sUActnQuick1;. This ritual dagger has been passed from one Grandmaster to another for years.","The Night Mother is already dead? You have done well,&sUActnQuick1;. This ritual dagger has been passed from one Grandmaster to another for years.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1AldSSotha_0001c684_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I believe you are the one who should wield it now and darken its blade with blood.","I believe you are the one who should wield it now and darken its blade with blood.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1AldSSotha_0001c684_2"
"","","Ald Sotha",Neutral,50,"The Night Mother is no more. You have done well,&sUActnQuick1;. This ritual dagger has been passed from one Grandmaster to another for years.","The Night Mother is no more. You have done well,&sUActnQuick1;. This ritual dagger has been passed from one Grandmaster to another for years.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1AldSSotha_0001c685_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I believe you are the one who should wield it now and darken its blade with blood.","I believe you are the one who should wield it now and darken its blade with blood.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1AldSSotha_0001c685_2"
"","","Ald Sotha",Neutral,50,"Ald Sotha is northeast of Vivec. Somewhere in Ald Sotha you will find Severa Magia, the Night Mother of the Dark Brotherhood in Vvardenfell.","Ald Sotha is northeast of Vivec. Somewhere in Ald Sotha you will find Severa Magia, the Night Mother of the Dark Brotherhood in Vvardenfell.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1AldSSotha_0001c683_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Slay her and return to me.","Slay her and return to me.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1AldSSotha_0001c683_2"
"","","Ultimatum",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled. Make amends and perhaps we will speak of this again.","You have been expelled. Make amends and perhaps we will speak of this again.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1ultimatum_003225a6_1"
"","","Ultimatum",Neutral,50,"Carecalmo is dead. There is nothing more to discuss.","Carecalmo is dead. There is nothing more to discuss.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1ultimatum_00f2a478_1"
"","","Ultimatum",Neutral,50,"You have already cleansed Ashalmimilka of the Mehrunes Dagon cultists?","You have already cleansed Ashalmimilka of the Mehrunes Dagon cultists?","fbmwMTAdvancement_1ultimatum_00f2a479_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Then a private war against the Dark Brotherhood and their allies in the cult of Mehrunes Dagon is our fate.","Then a private war against the Dark Brotherhood and their allies in the cult of Mehrunes Dagon is our fate.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1ultimatum_00f2a479_2"
"","","Ultimatum",Neutral,50,"So Carecalmo refused to speak with you. Very well. We shall crush the Dark Brotherhood and their allies in the cult of Mehrunes Dagon.","So Carecalmo refused to speak with you. Very well. We shall crush the Dark Brotherhood and their allies in the cult of Mehrunes Dagon.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1ultimatum_003225a7_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Take these 1000 drakes for the execution of Carecalmo.","Take these 1000 drakes for the execution of Carecalmo.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1ultimatum_003225a7_2"
"","","Ultimatum",Neutral,50,"So Carecalmo refused to speak with you. Very well. We shall crush the Dark Brotherhood and their allies in the cult of Mehrunes Dagon.","So Carecalmo refused to speak with you. Very well. We shall crush the Dark Brotherhood and their allies in the cult of Mehrunes Dagon.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1ultimatum_00f2a47a_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Take these 1000 drakes for the execution of Carecalmo.","Take these 1000 drakes for the execution of Carecalmo.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1ultimatum_00f2a47a_2"
"","","Ultimatum",Neutral,50,"Carecalmo can be found in Ashalmimilkala. When you speak to him, give him this ultimatum:","Carecalmo can be found in Ashalmimilkala. When you speak to him, give him this ultimatum:","fbmwMTAdvancement_1ultimatum_00f2a47b_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Stop protecting the Dark Brotherhood or the Morag Tong will declare private war on all cultists of Mehrunes Dagon.","Stop protecting the Dark Brotherhood or the Morag Tong will declare private war on all cultists of Mehrunes Dagon.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1ultimatum_00f2a47b_2"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"With this belt, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","With this belt, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSImpalingSThrust1_00322f3e_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"The Threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","The Threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSImpalingSThrust1_00322f3f_1"
"","","No",Neutral,50,"How can I trust you if you will not do this one simple favor in Mephala's dark name?","How can I trust you if you will not do this one simple favor in Mephala's dark name?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSImpalingSThrust2_00322f40_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"With this, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","With this, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSBalancedSArmor1_00322f4c_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"The threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","The threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSBalancedSArmor1_00322f4d_1"
"","","No",Neutral,50,"If you do not return this Thread, how can I be sure where your true loyalties lie?","If you do not return this Thread, how can I be sure where your true loyalties lie?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSBalancedSArmor2_00322f4e_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"With this, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","With this, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSublimeSWisdom1_00322f4f_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"So the Threads return to us one by one.","So the Threads return to us one by one.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSublimeSWisdom1_00001bc7_1"
"","","No",Neutral,50,"So your true loyalties shine through. Rest assured that the Morag Tong will have all the Threads of the Webspinner very soon.","So your true loyalties shine through. Rest assured that the Morag Tong will have all the Threads of the Webspinner very soon.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSublimeSWisdom2_00322f51_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"The Threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","The Threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSTransfiguring1_00322f5c_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"With this ring, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","With this ring, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSTransfiguring1_00f8ce3f_1"
"","","No",Neutral,50,"Are you loyal to the Morag Tong? Sometimes I wonder.","Are you loyal to the Morag Tong? Sometimes I wonder.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSTransfiguring2_00322f5d_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"With this ring, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","With this ring, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSGoldenSWisdom1_00322f5e_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"The Threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","The Threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSGoldenSWisdom1_00322f5f_1"
"","","No",Neutral,50,"Are you loyal to the Morag Tong? Sometimes I wonder.","Are you loyal to the Morag Tong? Sometimes I wonder.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSGoldenSWisdom2_00322f60_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"With this, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","With this, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSMartialSCraft1_00322f61_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"Thus do Mephala's Threads return to us one by one.","Thus do Mephala's Threads return to us one by one.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSMartialSCraft1_00322f62_1"
"","","No",Neutral,50,"So you do not truly believe in our cause. I shall remember this.","So you do not truly believe in our cause. I shall remember this.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSMartialSCraft2_00322f63_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"With this, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","With this, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSilverSWisdom1_00322f64_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"Thus do Mephala's Threads return to us one by one.","Thus do Mephala's Threads return to us one by one.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSilverSWisdom1_00322f65_1"
"","","No",Neutral,50,"So you do not truly believe in our cause. I shall remember this.","So you do not truly believe in our cause. I shall remember this.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSilverSWisdom2_00322f66_1"
"","","Here it is",Neutral,50,"With the return of the Ring of Sanguine Transcendence, all the Threads of Webspinner have been returned to the Morag Tong.","With the return of the Ring of Sanguine Transcendence, all the Threads of Webspinner have been returned to the Morag Tong.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSTranscendence1_00322f67_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Mephala will bless you with a portion of her skills.","Mephala will bless you with a portion of her skills.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSTranscendence1_00322f67_2"
"","","Here it is",Neutral,50,"The Ring of Sanguine Transcendence will take its place with the rest of the Threads of the Webspinner.","The Ring of Sanguine Transcendence will take its place with the rest of the Threads of the Webspinner.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSTranscendence1_00322f68_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Soon all these Threads will be returned to us by the machinations of Mephala, for all Threads lead to her black hands.","Soon all these Threads will be returned to us by the machinations of Mephala, for all Threads lead to her black hands.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSTranscendence1_00322f68_2"
"","","Keep it",Neutral,50,"So you do not truly care for our cause.","So you do not truly care for our cause.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSTranscendence2_00322f69_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"With this ring, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","With this ring, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSFluidSEvasion1_00001bce_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"The Threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","The Threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSFluidSEvasion1_00f8ce40_1"
"","","No",Neutral,50,"Are you loyal to the Morag Tong? Sometimes I wonder.","Are you loyal to the Morag Tong? Sometimes I wonder.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSFluidSEvasion2_00322fb8_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"With this, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","With this, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSUnseenSWisdom1_00322fbd_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"The threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","The threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSUnseenSWisdom1_00322fbe_1"
"","","No",Neutral,50,"If you do not return this Thread, how can I be sure where your true loyalties lie?","If you do not return this Thread, how can I be sure where your true loyalties lie?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSUnseenSWisdom2_00322fbf_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"With this ring, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","With this ring, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSGreenSWisdom1_00322fcf_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"The threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","The threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSGreenSWisdom1_00322fd0_1"
"","","No",Neutral,50,"If you do not return this Thread, how can I be sure where your true loyalties lie?","If you do not return this Thread, how can I be sure where your true loyalties lie?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSGreenSWisdom2_00322fd1_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"With this, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","With this, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSStolidSArmor1_00322fd2_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"The threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","The threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSStolidSArmor1_00322fd3_1"
"","","No",Neutral,50,"If you do not return this Thread, how can I be sure where your true loyalties lie?","If you do not return this Thread, how can I be sure where your true loyalties lie?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSStolidSArmor2_00322fd4_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"With this, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","With this, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSNimbleSArmor1_00322fd5_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"The threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","The threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSNimbleSArmor1_00322fd6_1"
"","","No",Neutral,50,"If you do not return this Thread, how can I be sure where your true loyalties lie?","If you do not return this Thread, how can I be sure where your true loyalties lie?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSNimbleSArmor2_00322fd7_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"With this belt, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","With this belt, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSDeepSBiting1_0032300a_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"The Threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","The Threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSDeepSBiting1_00f8ce41_1"
"","","No",Neutral,50,"How can I trust you if you will not do this one simple favor in Mephala's dark name?","How can I trust you if you will not do this one simple favor in Mephala's dark name?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSDeepSBiting2_00001bd3_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"With this amulet, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","With this amulet, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSGlibSSpeech1_0032300d_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"So the Threads return to us one by one.","So the Threads return to us one by one.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSGlibSSpeech1_0032300e_1"
"","","No",Neutral,50,"So your true loyalties shine through. Rest assured that the Morag Tong will have all the Threads of the Webspinner very soon.","So your true loyalties shine through. Rest assured that the Morag Tong will have all the Threads of the Webspinner very soon.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSGlibSSpeech2_0032300f_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"With this, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","With this, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSafekeeping1_00323010_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"Thus do Mephala's Threads return to us one by one.","Thus do Mephala's Threads return to us one by one.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSafekeeping1_00323011_1"
"","","No",Neutral,50,"So you do not truly believe in our cause. I shall remember this.","So you do not truly believe in our cause. I shall remember this.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSafekeeping2_00323012_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"With this ring, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","With this ring, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSRedSWisdom1_00001bcb_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"The Threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","The Threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSRedSWisdom1_00f8ce42_1"
"","","No",Neutral,50,"How can I trust you if you will not do this one simple favor in Mephala's dark name?","How can I trust you if you will not do this one simple favor in Mephala's dark name?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSRedSWisdom2_00323044_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"With this Belt, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","With this Belt, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSureflight1_00323045_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"The Threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","The Threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSureflight1_00323046_1"
"","","No",Neutral,50,"How can I trust you if you will not do this one simple favor in Mephala's dark name?","How can I trust you if you will not do this one simple favor in Mephala's dark name?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSureflight2_00323047_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"With these gloves, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","With these gloves, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSHornySFist1_00323048_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"So the Threads return to us one by one.","So the Threads return to us one by one.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSHornySFist1_00323049_1"
"","","No",Neutral,50,"So your true loyalties shine through. Rest assured that the Morag Tong will have all the Threads of the Webspinner very soon.","So your true loyalties shine through. Rest assured that the Morag Tong will have all the Threads of the Webspinner very soon.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSHornySFist2_0032304a_1"
"","","Here it is",Neutral,50,"With the return of the Gloves of Sanguine Swiftblade, all the Threads of Webspinner have been returned to the Morag Tong.","With the return of the Gloves of Sanguine Swiftblade, all the Threads of Webspinner have been returned to the Morag Tong.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSwiftblade1_0032304b_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Mephala will bless you with a portion of her skills.","Mephala will bless you with a portion of her skills.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSwiftblade1_0032304b_2"
"","","Here it is",Neutral,50,"The Gloves of Sanguine Swiftblade will take its place with the rest of the Threads of the Webspinner.","The Gloves of Sanguine Swiftblade will take its place with the rest of the Threads of the Webspinner.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSwiftblade1_0032304c_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Soon all these Threads will be returned to us by the machinations of Mephala, for all Threads lead to her black hands.","Soon all these Threads will be returned to us by the machinations of Mephala, for all Threads lead to her black hands.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSwiftblade1_0032304c_2"
"","","Keep it",Neutral,50,"So you do not truly care for our cause.","So you do not truly care for our cause.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSwiftblade2_0032304d_1"
"","","Yes, I will join.",Neutral,50,"I will let you join as a probationer. To gain full membership, you must pass a test. Here is a writ for the honorable execution of Feruren Oran.","I will let you join as a probationer. To gain full membership, you must pass a test. Here is a writ for the honorable execution of Feruren Oran.","fbmwMTWritOran_1joinStheSMoragSTong1_00f2a496_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You can find him in the Elven Nations Cornerclub, which is in the Hlaalu Plaza. Slay him honorably and report to me.","You can find him in the Elven Nations Cornerclub, which is in the Hlaalu Plaza. Slay him honorably and report to me.","fbmwMTWritOran_1joinStheSMoragSTong1_00f2a496_2"
"","","What do you stand for?",Neutral,50,"The Morag Tong executes writs and performs special duties as the ruling houses direct.","The Morag Tong executes writs and performs special duties as the ruling houses direct.","fbmwMTWritOran_1joinStheSMoragSTong2_00f2a497_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Guild members never harm or steal from any brother or sister - regardless of rank. Never betray our secrets or our identities.","Guild members never harm or steal from any brother or sister - regardless of rank. Never betray our secrets or our identities.","fbmwMTWritOran_1joinStheSMoragSTong2_00f2a497_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If you break any of these rules, you must immediately speak with a Master to regain your good standing or you may be targeted for execution.","If you break any of these rules, you must immediately speak with a Master to regain your good standing or you may be targeted for execution.","fbmwMTWritOran_1joinStheSMoragSTong2_00f2a497_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Do you feel you can succeed within these guidelines?","Do you feel you can succeed within these guidelines?","fbmwMTWritOran_1joinStheSMoragSTong2_00f2a497_4"
"","","No. I don't want any part of this.",Neutral,50,"You were unwise to have contacted me.","You were unwise to have contacted me.","fbmwMTWritOran_1joinStheSMoragSTong4_00323068_1"
"","","Here it is",Neutral,50,"With this, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","With this, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSFleetness1_0032309f_1"
"","","Here it is",Neutral,50,"The Belt of Sanguine Fleetness will take its place with the rest of the Threads of the Webspinner.","The Belt of Sanguine Fleetness will take its place with the rest of the Threads of the Webspinner.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSFleetness1_00f2a498_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Soon all these Threads will be returned to us by the machinations of Mephala, for all Threads lead to her black hands.","Soon all these Threads will be returned to us by the machinations of Mephala, for all Threads lead to her black hands.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSFleetness1_00f2a498_2"
"","","Keep it",Neutral,50,"So. You do not truly care for our cause.","So. You do not truly care for our cause.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSFleetness2_003230a1_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"With this Belt, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","With this Belt, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSStalking1_00001bca_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"The Threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","The Threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSStalking1_00f8ce43_1"
"","","No",Neutral,50,"How can I trust you if you will not do this one simple favor in Mephala's dark name?","How can I trust you if you will not do this one simple favor in Mephala's dark name?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSStalking2_00001bc9_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"With this ring, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","With this ring, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSmiting1_00323143_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"The Threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","The Threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSmiting1_00323144_1"
"","","No",Neutral,50,"Are you loyal to the Morag Tong? Sometimes I wonder.","Are you loyal to the Morag Tong? Sometimes I wonder.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSSmiting2_00323145_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"With this, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","With this, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSLeaping1_0032314d_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"The threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","The threads of the Webspinner return to us one by one.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSLeaping1_00f8ce44_1"
"","","No",Neutral,50,"If you do not return this Thread, how can I be sure where your true loyalties lie?","If you do not return this Thread, how can I be sure where your true loyalties lie?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSLeaping2_0032314f_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"With this, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","With this, you have returned all the Threads of the Webspinner to the Morag Tong. You will be blessed by Mephala's skill.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSDenial1_00001bd2_1"
"","","Yes, here it is",Neutral,50,"Thus do Mephala's Threads return to us one by one.","Thus do Mephala's Threads return to us one by one.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSDenial1_00f8ce45_1"
"","","No",Neutral,50,"So you do not truly believe in our cause. I shall remember this.","So you do not truly believe in our cause. I shall remember this.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSDenial2_00001bd1_1"
"","","Here it is",Neutral,50,"The Belt of Sanguine Hewing will take its place with the rest of the Threads of the Webspinner.","The Belt of Sanguine Hewing will take its place with the rest of the Threads of the Webspinner.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSHewing1_00001bcd_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Soon all these Threads will be returned to us by the machinations of Mephala, for all Threads lead to her black hands.","Soon all these Threads will be returned to us by the machinations of Mephala, for all Threads lead to her black hands.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSHewing1_00001bcd_2"
"","","Here it is",Neutral,50,"With the return of the Belt of Sanguine Hewing, all the Threads of Webspinner have been returned to the Morag Tong.","With the return of the Belt of Sanguine Hewing, all the Threads of Webspinner have been returned to the Morag Tong.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSHewing1_00f8ce46_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Mephala will bless you with a portion of her skills.","Mephala will bless you with a portion of her skills.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSHewing1_00f8ce46_2"
"","","Keep it",Neutral,50,"So you do not truly care for our cause.","So you do not truly care for our cause.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSHewing2_00001bcc_1"
"","","Allow him to retire.",Neutral,50,"So be it. I will leave here soon. You are the new Grandmaster of the Morag Tong.","So be it. I will leave here soon. You are the new Grandmaster of the Morag Tong.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1Grandmaster1_00323497_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Always watch for the Dark Brotherhood, for I am sure they will soon try to regain what you have taken from them here.","Always watch for the Dark Brotherhood, for I am sure they will soon try to regain what you have taken from them here.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1Grandmaster1_00323497_2"
"","","Slay him.",Neutral,50,"So be it.","So be it.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1Grandmaster2_00323498_1"
"","","I wish to bring honor to the Guild",Neutral,50,"I will let you join as a probationer. To gain full membership, you must pass a test. Here is a writ for the honorable execution of Feruren Oran.","I will let you join as a probationer. To gain full membership, you must pass a test. Here is a writ for the honorable execution of Feruren Oran.","fbmwMTWritOran_1joinStheSMoragSTong5_00f2a49c_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You can find him in the Elven Nations Cornerclub, which is in the Hlaalu Plaza. Slay him honorably and report to me.","You can find him in the Elven Nations Cornerclub, which is in the Hlaalu Plaza. Slay him honorably and report to me.","fbmwMTWritOran_1joinStheSMoragSTong5_00f2a49c_2"
"","","Movis Darys",Neutral,50,"Movis Darys has agreed to join the Morag Tong. He will be our eyes and ears in the Dark Brotherhood.","Movis Darys has agreed to join the Morag Tong. He will be our eyes and ears in the Dark Brotherhood.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1darys_00f8ce48_1"
"","","Movis Darys",Neutral,50,"So Movis Darys is dead. It is unfortunate, but if he wouldn't join us... In any case, I shall pay you as if this was a Writ.","So Movis Darys is dead. It is unfortunate, but if he wouldn't join us... In any case, I shall pay you as if this was a Writ.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1darys_00f8ce49_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Take these 1000 drakes with my gratitude.","Take these 1000 drakes with my gratitude.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1darys_00f8ce49_2"
"","","Movis Darys",Neutral,50,"So Movis Darys has agreed to join us. Good. I shall pay you as if you had executed a Writ on Movis Darys. Take these 1000 drakes.","So Movis Darys has agreed to join us. Good. I shall pay you as if you had executed a Writ on Movis Darys. Take these 1000 drakes.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1darys_00f8ce4a_1"
"","","Movis Darys",Neutral,50,"Movis Darys is already dead? Did you know he was a member of the Dark Brotherhood?","Movis Darys is already dead? Did you know he was a member of the Dark Brotherhood?","fbmwMTAdvancement_1darys_00f8ce4b_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Well, perhaps next time you should not be so hasty in your judgements. As long as his execution was honorable, I am not displeased.","Well, perhaps next time you should not be so hasty in your judgements. As long as his execution was honorable, I am not displeased.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1darys_00f8ce4b_2"
"","","Movis Darys",Neutral,50,"Movis Darys is in the Mages Guild in Ald'ruhn. He is posing as a student in the Imperial school there.","Movis Darys is in the Mages Guild in Ald'ruhn. He is posing as a student in the Imperial school there.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1darys_00f8ce4c_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Speak with him and if you cannot convince him to join our cause, end his life.","Speak with him and if you cannot convince him to join our cause, end his life.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1darys_00f8ce4c_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"He is not like the others in the Dark Brotherhood. If you must kill him, make sure his death is honorable.","He is not like the others in the Dark Brotherhood. If you must kill him, make sure his death is honorable.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1darys_00f8ce4c_3"
"","","Movis Darys",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled.","You have been expelled.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1darys_00f8ce4d_1"
"","","Movis Darys",Neutral,50,"Movis Darys is dead. There is no more to discuss.","Movis Darys is dead. There is no more to discuss.","fbmwMTAdvancement_1darys_00f8ce4e_1"
"","","Sanguine Items",Neutral,50,"Have you found more of the Threads of the Webspinner?","Have you found more of the Threads of the Webspinner?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSAll_00f8ce50_1"
"","","Sanguine Items",Neutral,50,"My amulet? This is the Amulet of Sanguine Enterprise, one of the twenty-seven threads of the Webspinner. I already have this thread.","My amulet? This is the Amulet of Sanguine Enterprise, one of the twenty-seven threads of the Webspinner. I already have this thread.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSAll_00f8ce51_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Perhaps you will find other threads. When you do, bring them to me.","Perhaps you will find other threads. When you do, bring them to me.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSAll_00f8ce51_2"
"","","Sanguine Items",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But perhaps you ask because have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Do you?","You have been expelled from the Morag Tong... But perhaps you ask because have one of the Threads of the Webspinner. Do you?","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSAll_00f8ce52_1"
"","","Sanguine Items",Neutral,50,"You have returned all of the Sanguine Items, and Mephala has shown you her favor. I am in awe, blessed one.","You have returned all of the Sanguine Items, and Mephala has shown you her favor. I am in awe, blessed one.","fbmwMTSanguineItems_1SanguineSAll_00f8ce53_1"
