Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Join the Royal Guards",Neutral,50,"Suit yourself. It's Delitian's call. I like it here. I know Tienius Delitian pretty well, and when Helseth became king, Delitian asked me if I was interested.","Suit yourself. It's Delitian's call. I like it here. I know Tienius Delitian pretty well, and when Helseth became king, Delitian asked me if I was interested.","fbmwTR07Guard_1joinStheSRoyalSGuards_00f8ba1e_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"It's respectable, quiet work, and the pay is fine with me.","It's respectable, quiet work, and the pay is fine with me.","fbmwTR07Guard_1joinStheSRoyalSGuards_00f8ba1e_2"
"","","Mention your Hlaalu connections.",Neutral,50,"That may be a strike against you... but it depends. Some of the old guard Hlaalu are quite upset about Helseth becoming king instead of some Hlaalu noble.","That may be a strike against you... but it depends. Some of the old guard Hlaalu are quite upset about Helseth becoming king instead of some Hlaalu noble.","fbmwTR07Guard_fbmwtr07hlaalu_00f8bc94_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But sensible Hlaalu know the future is with the Empire, and King Helseth has excellent Imperial connections.","But sensible Hlaalu know the future is with the Empire, and King Helseth has excellent Imperial connections.","fbmwTR07Guard_fbmwtr07hlaalu_00f8bc94_2"
"","","Ask about King Helseth.",Neutral,50,"He's smart. Serious. Good personal touch. He's making a real effort to win over the people of Mournhold. From what I hear, that's more than King Llethan ever did.","He's smart. Serious. Good personal touch. He's making a real effort to win over the people of Mournhold. From what I hear, that's more than King Llethan ever did.","fbmwTR07Guard_fbmwtr07helseth_00f8bc9d_1"
"","","Ask about King Llethan.",Neutral,50,"He was an old fool, they tell me. Don't know any more than that. Never saw him in my life.","He was an old fool, they tell me. Don't know any more than that. Never saw him in my life.","fbmwTR07Guard_fbmwtr07llethan_00f8bca6_1"
