Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Need Wives",Neutral,50,"Yes, you were right. These men need wives. Have you seen how they dress? Perhaps I will stay here a few days.","Yes, you were right. These men need wives. Have you seen how they dress? Perhaps I will stay here a few days.","fbmwHRStronghold_1needSwives_00322245_1"
"","","Need Wives",Neutral,50,"I have some things to do here in town, but I will come visit Indarys Manor as soon as I can.","I have some things to do here in town, but I will come visit Indarys Manor as soon as I can.","fbmwHRStronghold_1needSwives_00322247_1"
"","","Need Wives",Neutral,50,"Wait. If I understand you, you're saying that this "Indarys Manor" has a dozen eligible men. And there are only a few women there.","Wait. If I understand you, you're saying that this "Indarys Manor" has a dozen eligible men. And there are only a few women there.","fbmwHRStronghold_1needSwives_0032224c_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And you want me to move there to find a husband, right?","And you want me to move there to find a husband, right?","fbmwHRStronghold_1needSwives_0032224c_2"
"","","Need Wives",Neutral,50,"I understand what you're asking, and I'm not offended. But I'm not sure I should leave Ald'ruhn.","I understand what you're asking, and I'm not offended. But I'm not sure I should leave Ald'ruhn.","fbmwHRStronghold_1needSwives_0032224d_1"
"","","Need Wives",Neutral,50,"What? Why would I leave here with a complete stranger to marry a man I've never met?","What? Why would I leave here with a complete stranger to marry a man I've never met?","fbmwHRStronghold_1needSwives_0032224e_1"
"","","That's right.",Neutral,50,"Okay. I agree. Just let me take care of a few things here in town, and I'll pay a visit to Indarys Manor.","Okay. I agree. Just let me take care of a few things here in town, and I'll pay a visit to Indarys Manor.","fbmwHRStronghold_1needSwives1fathusa_0032351b_1"
"","","Well, um, not exactly.",Neutral,50,"I'm sorry, but I'm confused. I don't think I will ever understand what you're asking.","I'm sorry, but I'm confused. I don't think I will ever understand what you're asking.","fbmwHRStronghold_1needSwives2fathusa_00323520_1"
