Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"These Redoran have not heard the last of Faves Andas!","These Redoran have not heard the last of Faves Andas!","fbmwHTShishi_GREETING_000068e0_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Is the way clear of Redoran?","Is the way clear of Redoran?","fbmwHTShishi_GREETING_000068e1_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Thank you for helping me out of there, outlander.  I can make my own way from here.","Thank you for helping me out of there, outlander.  I can make my own way from here.","fbmwHTShishi_GREETING_000068d2_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Thank you for taking care of Brerama Selas for me, outlander.","Thank you for taking care of Brerama Selas for me, outlander.","fbmwHTShishi_GREETING_000068e2_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I'm glad to finally see a friendly face! The Redoran overwhelmed us!","I'm glad to finally see a friendly face! The Redoran overwhelmed us!","fbmwHTShishi_GREETING_000068e3_1"
"","","Kill Brerama Selas.",Neutral,50,"Once Brerama Selas is dead, I will take care of the other Redorans in my time.","Once Brerama Selas is dead, I will take care of the other Redorans in my time.","fbmwHTShishi_1Shishi1_000068db_1"
"","","Get me out of here.",Neutral,50,"I would rather you kill Brerama Selas, but perhaps there are too many Redoran for just the two of us to handle.","I would rather you kill Brerama Selas, but perhaps there are too many Redoran for just the two of us to handle.","fbmwHTShishi_1Shishi2_000068dc_1"
"","","Travel Together",Neutral,50,"Is the way clear of Redoran?","Is the way clear of Redoran?","fbmwHTShishi_1travelStogether_000068d3_1"
"","","Shishi",Neutral,50,"Thank you for getting me out of there, outlander.  I can take care of myself from here.","Thank you for getting me out of there, outlander.  I can take care of myself from here.","fbmwHTShishi_1Shishi_000068df_1"
"","","Shishi",Neutral,50,"Let's just get out of here, outlander.","Let's just get out of here, outlander.","fbmwHTShishi_1Shishi_000068de_1"
"","","Shishi",Neutral,50,"You already dealt with Brerama Selas, the only Redoran I was worried about.","You already dealt with Brerama Selas, the only Redoran I was worried about.","fbmwHTShishi_1Shishi_000068dd_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Report back to Aryon and I will handle any Redorans still here in my own time.","Report back to Aryon and I will handle any Redorans still here in my own time.","fbmwHTShishi_1Shishi_000068dd_2"
"","","Shishi",Neutral,50,"Have you killed Brerama Selas? Excellent. I can handle the other Redorans on my own. I will tell Master Aryon that you assisted me.","Have you killed Brerama Selas? Excellent. I can handle the other Redorans on my own. I will tell Master Aryon that you assisted me.","fbmwHTShishi_1Shishi_00322c08_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You might find these books of interest, outlander. I have already studied them.","You might find these books of interest, outlander. I have already studied them.","fbmwHTShishi_1Shishi_00322c08_2"
"","","Shishi",Neutral,50,"You must kill Brerama Selas, or get me out of here.","You must kill Brerama Selas, or get me out of here.","fbmwHTShishi_1Shishi_00322c09_1"
"","","Wait here.",Neutral,50,"If you would just take care of Brerama Selas for me I could handle the rest myself, but I'll wait here if you want to poke around.","If you would just take care of Brerama Selas for me I could handle the rest myself, but I'll wait here if you want to poke around.","fbmwHTShishi_1travelStogether2_000068d5_1"
"","","Follow me.",Neutral,50,"I don't like the idea of leaving Shishi to the Redoran, but I'll be right behind you, outlander.","I don't like the idea of leaving Shishi to the Redoran, but I'll be right behind you, outlander.","fbmwHTShishi_1travelStogether1_000068d4_1"
