Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Send your slaves to Indarys Manor.",Neutral,50,"You want us to send some of the slaves we get to your manor? Hm. That might work, though I doubt your men want to marry Khajiit or Argonians.","You want us to send some of the slaves we get to your manor? Hm. That might work, though I doubt your men want to marry Khajiit or Argonians.","fbmwHRStronghold_1needSwives1galyn_0032351c_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I will send you the next suitable slaves that pass through here, but it is up to you to protect them.","I will send you the next suitable slaves that pass through here, but it is up to you to protect them.","fbmwHRStronghold_1needSwives1galyn_0032351c_2"
"","","I'm sorry. I will ask someone else.",Neutral,50,"I don't know anyone around here you could ask. Try Ald'ruhn instead.","I don't know anyone around here you could ask. Try Ald'ruhn instead.","fbmwHRStronghold_1needSwives2galyn_00323521_1"
"","","Slavehunters",Neutral,50,"J'Saddha arrived safely.","J'Saddha arrived safely.","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1slavehunters_00010197_1"
"","","Slavehunters",Neutral,50,"Yes, the slavehunters are Anes Hlaren, Garyn Girith, and Sadal Doren.","Yes, the slavehunters are Anes Hlaren, Garyn Girith, and Sadal Doren.","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1slavehunters_00010198_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"They have been patrolling in town and near the docks since they heard of J'Saddha's escape.","They have been patrolling in town and near the docks since they heard of J'Saddha's escape.","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1slavehunters_00010198_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You will need to get rid of them or avoid being seen. Remember it is J'Saddha they are looking for, not you.","You will need to get rid of them or avoid being seen. Remember it is J'Saddha they are looking for, not you.","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1slavehunters_00010198_3"
"","","Twin Lamps",Neutral,50,"So, you know the Twin Lamps. We could use your aid in our struggle against slavery.","So, you know the Twin Lamps. We could use your aid in our struggle against slavery.","fbmwHHAdvancement_1TwinSLamps_00010a2b_1"
"","","Need Wives",Neutral,50,"I will send the next slaves we get to your manor. I am sure they will be happier as wives than slaves.","I will send the next slaves we get to your manor. I am sure they will be happier as wives than slaves.","fbmwHRStronghold_1needSwives_0000fc9b_1"
"","","Need Wives",Neutral,50,"Yes, I know. You're the lord of Indarys Manor. You said you needed wives there?","Yes, I know. You're the lord of Indarys Manor. You said you needed wives there?","fbmwHRStronghold_1needSwives_0000fc9c_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Why are you asking me? I'm not looking for a husband.","Why are you asking me? I'm not looking for a husband.","fbmwHRStronghold_1needSwives_0000fc9c_2"
"","","J'Saddha",Neutral,50,"We have taken him to friends on the mainland. He will return to his homeland.","We have taken him to friends on the mainland. He will return to his homeland.","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1JASaddha_00010a30_1"
"","","J'Saddha",Neutral,50,"Thank you for bringing him here. He will have a better life back in his native land.","Thank you for bringing him here. He will have a better life back in his native land.","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1JASaddha_00010a2f_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You should report back to Ilmeni Dren that the slave has arrived safely.","You should report back to Ilmeni Dren that the slave has arrived safely.","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1JASaddha_00010a2f_2"
"","","J'Saddha",Neutral,50,"He is hiding in some Daedric ruins east of here. Find him and escort him back to town.","He is hiding in some Daedric ruins east of here. Find him and escort him back to town.","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1JASaddha_00010a2e_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Make sure the slavehunters do not see him.","Make sure the slavehunters do not see him.","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1JASaddha_00010a2e_2"
"","","Slavery",Neutral,50,"Continue your work to end slavery here in Morrowind!","Continue your work to end slavery here in Morrowind!","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1slavery_000100df_1"
"","","Slavery",Neutral,50,"Thank you for bringing J'Saddha here safely.","Thank you for bringing J'Saddha here safely.","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1slavery_000100de_1"
"","","Slavery",Neutral,50,"You know the Twin Lamps? Well then, yes, we are having some trouble here.","You know the Twin Lamps? Well then, yes, we are having some trouble here.","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1slavery_000100dd_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"A Khajiiti slave, J'Saddha, was supposed to meet us at our boat.","A Khajiiti slave, J'Saddha, was supposed to meet us at our boat.","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1slavery_000100dd_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"He sent us a message that he is hiding in some ruins east of here, but there are three slavehunters in town, and we cannot risk being discovered.","He sent us a message that he is hiding in some ruins east of here, but there are three slavehunters in town, and we cannot risk being discovered.","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1slavery_000100dd_3"
