Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I can't talk now. I'm waiting for our escort to show up. 'Sides, Gidar is in charge.","I can't talk now. I'm waiting for our escort to show up. 'Sides, Gidar is in charge.","fbmwMSGreetings_GREETING_00f8b99d_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Another day, another hundred piles of ore.... What can I do for you?","Another day, another hundred piles of ore.... What can I do for you?","fbmwCO2_GREETING_00f8b969_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I'd like to stop and chat, but there's much to be done.","I'd like to stop and chat, but there's much to be done.","fbmwCO1_GREETING_00f8b9c6_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Thanks for making sure we got here safely. I appreciate it. I'd better get to work. Excuse me.","Thanks for making sure we got here safely. I appreciate it. I'd better get to work. Excuse me.","fbmwCO1_GREETING_00f8b9c7_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Don't look at me; I'm just following Gidar.","Don't look at me; I'm just following Gidar.","fbmwCO1_GREETING_00f8b9c8_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Oh, you're the escort? Better talk to Gidar, then. We're supposed to follow him.","Oh, you're the escort? Better talk to Gidar, then. We're supposed to follow him.","fbmwCO1_GREETING_00f8b9c9_1"
"","","Hire Guards",Neutral,50,"You want me to guard this place? No, I don't think so. Sorry.","You want me to guard this place? No, I don't think so. Sorry.","fbmwCO11_1hireSguards_00027777_1"
"","","Carnius Magius",Neutral,50,"He's the boss. Stays here at the Fort, from what I understand.","He's the boss. Stays here at the Fort, from what I understand.","MorroDefaultQuest_1CarniusSMagius_003215c5_1"
"","","Seen Anything",Neutral,50,"So that was the ship, huh?","So that was the ship, huh?","fbmwCO3_1seenSanything_00f8bae6_1"
"","","Seen Anything",Neutral,50,"I already told you what I can. Just that light to the northwest. Maybe you should go take a look.","I already told you what I can. Just that light to the northwest. Maybe you should go take a look.","fbmwCO3_1seenSanything_00f8bae7_1"
"","","Seen Anything",Neutral,50,"Well, maybe I did see something, now that you mention it. Night before last, I saw a light off to the northwest. Thought maybe it was a reaver boat, or a raiding party or something, and I wasn't about to go check it out, but maybe it was our supply ship.","Well, maybe I did see something, now that you mention it. Night before last, I saw a light off to the northwest. Thought maybe it was a reaver boat, or a raiding party or something, and I wasn't about to go check it out, but maybe it was our supply ship.","fbmwCO3_1seenSanything_00f8bae8_1"
"","","Decision",Neutral,50,"I hear it's been taken care of already. Doesn't matter what I think now.","I hear it's been taken care of already. Doesn't matter what I think now.","fbmwCO4_1decision_00f8bbe8_1"
"","","Decision",Neutral,50,"Well, if you ask me, we need a Smith here. If the equipment breaks down, we could just get it fixed here, instead of shipping it off to the mainland. But that's just my opinion.","Well, if you ask me, we need a Smith here. If the equipment breaks down, we could just get it fixed here, instead of shipping it off to the mainland. But that's just my opinion.","fbmwCO4_1decision_00f8bbe9_1"
