Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I'm afraid that I have nothing for you, outlander. You will need to speak with the Lady Almalexia if you have further questions.","I'm afraid that I have nothing for you, outlander. You will need to speak with the Lady Almalexia if you have further questions.","fbmwTRBamz_GREETING_00013563_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"What is it? I have been told of no tasks that you may perform in the Lady Almalexia's service.","What is it? I have been told of no tasks that you may perform in the Lady Almalexia's service.","fbmwTRMazedBand_GREETING_00013560_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"You're to retrieve Barilzar's Mazed Band, are you not?","You're to retrieve Barilzar's Mazed Band, are you not?","fbmwTRMazedBand_GREETING_00013561_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Ahhh...Fedris sent you to me, did he? You would like to know more about Barilzar's Mazed Band? I suppose I can tell you something.","Ahhh...Fedris sent you to me, did he? You would like to know more about Barilzar's Mazed Band? I suppose I can tell you something.","fbmwTRMazedBand_GREETING_00013562_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Yes...have you come to be of service to our Lady?","Yes...have you come to be of service to our Lady?","fbmwTRShrineDead_GREETING_00013564_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"What is it? Have you settled that business with the Shrine of the Dead?","What is it? Have you settled that business with the Shrine of the Dead?","fbmwTRShrineDead_GREETING_00013565_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Hmmm...yes. You are the one that Hler mentioned. Interesting. You are to be of service to our Lady.","Hmmm...yes. You are the one that Hler mentioned. Interesting. You are to be of service to our Lady.","fbmwTRShrineDead_GREETING_00013566_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"It is essential, and all would be displeased were you to fail.","It is essential, and all would be displeased were you to fail.","fbmwTRShrineDead_GREETING_00013566_2"
"","","Sotha Sil is dead, I killed Almalexia",Neutral,50,"[Anxious, but prepared and controlled.] I'm not sure you understand.","[Anxious, but prepared and controlled.] I'm not sure you understand.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1Almalexia1_00009dd9_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The Tribunal are Living Gods -- but that doesn't mean you can come see them any time you want.","The Tribunal are Living Gods -- but that doesn't mean you can come see them any time you want.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1Almalexia1_00009dd9_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"In happier times, the Tribunal appeared before the people, just like us priests. But times have changed, and no one sees the Tribunal any more.","In happier times, the Tribunal appeared before the people, just like us priests. But times have changed, and no one sees the Tribunal any more.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1Almalexia1_00009dd9_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"So... of course... you could not have 'killed' Almalexia. That's simply... impossible.","So... of course... you could not have 'killed' Almalexia. That's simply... impossible.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1Almalexia1_00009dd9_4"
"","","[Lie]I found Almal. and SothaSil dead",Neutral,50,"[Anxious, but prepared and controlled.] I'm not sure you understand.","[Anxious, but prepared and controlled.] I'm not sure you understand.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1Almalexia2_00009ddc_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The Tribunal are Living Gods -- but that doesn't mean you can come see them any time you want.","The Tribunal are Living Gods -- but that doesn't mean you can come see them any time you want.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1Almalexia2_00009ddc_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"In happier times, the Tribunal appeared before the people, just like us priests. But times have changed, and no one sees the Tribunal any more.","In happier times, the Tribunal appeared before the people, just like us priests. But times have changed, and no one sees the Tribunal any more.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1Almalexia2_00009ddc_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"So... of course... you could not have found Almalexia and Sotha Sil 'dead'. That's simply... impossible.","So... of course... you could not have found Almalexia and Sotha Sil 'dead'. That's simply... impossible.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1Almalexia2_00009ddc_4"
"","","[Lie]I found the Tribunal dead",Neutral,50,"[Anxious, but prepared and controlled.] I'm not sure you understand.","[Anxious, but prepared and controlled.] I'm not sure you understand.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1Almalexia5_00009ddb_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The Tribunal are Living Gods -- but that doesn't mean you can come see them any time you want.","The Tribunal are Living Gods -- but that doesn't mean you can come see them any time you want.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1Almalexia5_00009ddb_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"In happier times, the Tribunal appeared before the people, just like us priests. But times have changed, and no one sees the Tribunal any more.","In happier times, the Tribunal appeared before the people, just like us priests. But times have changed, and no one sees the Tribunal any more.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1Almalexia5_00009ddb_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"So... of course... you could not have found Almalexia, Sotha Sil, and Vivec 'dead'. That's simply... impossible.","So... of course... you could not have found Almalexia, Sotha Sil, and Vivec 'dead'. That's simply... impossible.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1Almalexia5_00009ddb_4"
"","","I killed the Tribunal",Neutral,50,"[Anxious, but prepared and controlled.] I'm not sure you understand.","[Anxious, but prepared and controlled.] I'm not sure you understand.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1Almalexia6_00009dde_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The Tribunal are Living Gods -- but that doesn't mean you can come see them any time you want.","The Tribunal are Living Gods -- but that doesn't mean you can come see them any time you want.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1Almalexia6_00009dde_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"In happier times, the Tribunal appeared before the people, just like us priests. But times have changed, and no one sees the Tribunal any more.","In happier times, the Tribunal appeared before the people, just like us priests. But times have changed, and no one sees the Tribunal any more.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1Almalexia6_00009dde_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"So... of course... you could not have 'killed' Almalexia. That's simply... impossible.","So... of course... you could not have 'killed' Almalexia. That's simply... impossible.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1Almalexia6_00009dde_4"
"","","I killed Vivec.",Neutral,50,"[Anxious, but prepared and controlled.] I'm not sure you understand.","[Anxious, but prepared and controlled.] I'm not sure you understand.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1Almalexia7_00009ddd_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The Tribunal are Living Gods -- but that doesn't mean you can come see them any time you want.","The Tribunal are Living Gods -- but that doesn't mean you can come see them any time you want.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1Almalexia7_00009ddd_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"In happier times, the Tribunal appeared before the people, just like us priests. But times have changed, and no one sees the Tribunal any more.","In happier times, the Tribunal appeared before the people, just like us priests. But times have changed, and no one sees the Tribunal any more.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1Almalexia7_00009ddd_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"So... of course... you could not have 'killed' Vivec. That's simply... impossible.","So... of course... you could not have 'killed' Vivec. That's simply... impossible.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1Almalexia7_00009ddd_4"
"","","[Lie] I found Vivec dead.",Neutral,50,"[Anxious, but prepared and controlled.] I'm not sure you understand.","[Anxious, but prepared and controlled.] I'm not sure you understand.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1Almalexia8_00009dda_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The Tribunal are Living Gods -- but that doesn't mean you can come see them any time you want.","The Tribunal are Living Gods -- but that doesn't mean you can come see them any time you want.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1Almalexia8_00009dda_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"In happier times, the Tribunal appeared before the people, just like us priests. But times have changed, and no one sees the Tribunal any more.","In happier times, the Tribunal appeared before the people, just like us priests. But times have changed, and no one sees the Tribunal any more.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1Almalexia8_00009dda_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"So... of course... you could not have found Vivec 'dead'. That's simply... impossible.","So... of course... you could not have found Vivec 'dead'. That's simply... impossible.","fbmwTRSothaSil_1Almalexia8_00009dda_4"
"","","I killed Vivec.",Neutral,50,"[Anxious, but prepared and controlled.] I'm not sure you understand. The Tribunal are Living Gods -- but that doesn't mean you can come see them any time you want. In happier times, the Tribunal appeared before the people, just like us priests.","[Anxious, but prepared and controlled.] I'm not sure you understand. The Tribunal are Living Gods -- but that doesn't mean you can come see them any time you want. In happier times, the Tribunal appeared before the people, just like us priests.","MorroDefaultQuest_fbmwTRikilledvivec_0002d8ba_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But times have changed, and no one sees the Tribunal any more. So... of course... you could not have 'killed' Vivec. That's simply... impossible.","But times have changed, and no one sees the Tribunal any more. So... of course... you could not have 'killed' Vivec. That's simply... impossible.","MorroDefaultQuest_fbmwTRikilledvivec_0002d8ba_2"
"","","I found Vivec dead.",Neutral,50,"[Anxious, but prepared and controlled.] I'm not sure you understand. The Tribunal are Living Gods -- but that doesn't mean you can come see them any time you want. In happier times, the Tribunal appeared before the people, just like us priests.","[Anxious, but prepared and controlled.] I'm not sure you understand. The Tribunal are Living Gods -- but that doesn't mean you can come see them any time you want. In happier times, the Tribunal appeared before the people, just like us priests.","MorroDefaultQuest_fbmwTRifoundvivecdead_0002d8c0_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But times have changed, and no one sees the Tribunal any more. So... of course... you could not have 'killed' Vivec. That's simply... impossible.","But times have changed, and no one sees the Tribunal any more. So... of course... you could not have 'killed' Vivec. That's simply... impossible.","MorroDefaultQuest_fbmwTRifoundvivecdead_0002d8c0_2"
"","","Almalexia",Neutral,50,"The Most Blessed Lady Almalexia guides and protects us all. We bask in her glory and are glad.","The Most Blessed Lady Almalexia guides and protects us all. We bask in her glory and are glad.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Almalexia_0001c68f_1"
"","","Sotha Sil",Neutral,50,"The Lord Sotha Sil is a great mage and a member of the Blessed Tribunal. He lives in his Clockwork City, and is rarely seen in Morrowind.","The Lord Sotha Sil is a great mage and a member of the Blessed Tribunal. He lives in his Clockwork City, and is rarely seen in Morrowind.","MorroDefaultQuest_1SothaSSil_0032265b_1"
"","","Sotha Sil",Neutral,50,"The Lord Sotha Sil is one of the Blessed Tribunal. He is a mighty wizard, and is a source of inspiration for us all.","The Lord Sotha Sil is one of the Blessed Tribunal. He is a mighty wizard, and is a source of inspiration for us all.","MorroDefaultQuest_1SothaSSil_0032265c_1"
"","","Shrine has been corrupted",Neutral,50,"The Shrine of the Dead was once a place of great power. It served as a channel to the ancestors, allowing the faithful to learn from them...to harnes their power.","The Shrine of the Dead was once a place of great power. It served as a channel to the ancestors, allowing the faithful to learn from them...to harnes their power.","fbmwTRShrineDead_1shrineShasSbeenScorrupted_00f8ba03_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Over the years, it has been forgotten, and it has grown sour. The power that radiates from the shrine has drawn hordes of the undead to it. The Shrine of the Dead must be cleansed.","Over the years, it has been forgotten, and it has grown sour. The power that radiates from the shrine has drawn hordes of the undead to it. The Shrine of the Dead must be cleansed.","fbmwTRShrineDead_1shrineShasSbeenScorrupted_00f8ba03_2"
"","","Speak with her directly",Neutral,50,"Yes, the Lady requests your presence at once. It is best not to keep her waiting. You will find her in the High Chapel.","Yes, the Lady requests your presence at once. It is best not to keep her waiting. You will find her in the High Chapel.","fbmwTRMazedBand_1speakSwithSherSdirectly_00001bb0_1"
"","","Barilzar's Mazed Band",Neutral,50,"Speak with the Lady directly.","Speak with the Lady directly.","fbmwTRMazedBand_1BarilzarAsSMazedSBand_00f8ab56_1"
"","","Barilzar's Mazed Band",Neutral,50,"You've been able to retrieve the Mazed Band? Amazing...Almalexia will want to hear about this immediately. You are to speak with her directly.","You've been able to retrieve the Mazed Band? Amazing...Almalexia will want to hear about this immediately. You are to speak with her directly.","fbmwTRMazedBand_1BarilzarAsSMazedSBand_00f8ab57_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I hope you realize what an honor you're receiving.","I hope you realize what an honor you're receiving.","fbmwTRMazedBand_1BarilzarAsSMazedSBand_00f8ab57_2"
"","","Barilzar's Mazed Band",Neutral,50,"You'll need to retrieve the Band from the Temple ruins. Quickly. The goddess wishes to have it in her possession.","You'll need to retrieve the Band from the Temple ruins. Quickly. The goddess wishes to have it in her possession.","fbmwTRMazedBand_1BarilzarAsSMazedSBand_00f8ab58_1"
"","","Barilzar's Mazed Band",Neutral,50,"Yes...the Mazed Band. Barilzar himself was a powerful mage...quite powerful, in fact. He created the band sometime in the middle of the Second Era, and soon after disappeared.","Yes...the Mazed Band. Barilzar himself was a powerful mage...quite powerful, in fact. He created the band sometime in the middle of the Second Era, and soon after disappeared.","fbmwTRMazedBand_1BarilzarAsSMazedSBand_00f8ab59_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The purpose of the artifact is unknown to me. All I know is that the Lady wants it. I can only assume it will allow her to better minister to her people, though I find that hard to imagine.","The purpose of the artifact is unknown to me. All I know is that the Lady wants it. I can only assume it will allow her to better minister to her people, though I find that hard to imagine.","fbmwTRMazedBand_1BarilzarAsSMazedSBand_00f8ab59_2"
"","","Service to our Lady",Neutral,50,"Unfortunately, I know of nothing you may do for the Lady now. Speak with Fedris Hler. He usually has errands that must be completed by the lowly.","Unfortunately, I know of nothing you may do for the Lady now. Speak with Fedris Hler. He usually has errands that must be completed by the lowly.","fbmwTRShrineDead_1serviceStoSourSLady_00f8ba39_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Don't let him tell you he has nothing to be done. I'm sure there's something.","Don't let him tell you he has nothing to be done. I'm sure there's something.","fbmwTRShrineDead_1serviceStoSourSLady_00f8ba39_2"
"","","Service to our Lady",Neutral,50,"Finish your task at hand, and then maybe we will speak about it.","Finish your task at hand, and then maybe we will speak about it.","fbmwTRShrineDead_1serviceStoSourSLady_00f8ba3a_1"
"","","Service to our Lady",Neutral,50,"Yes. Beneath this Temple, there is a large sewer system, built around the ruins of Old Mournhold. You smell like you may have spent some time there.... Regardless, in these ruins, there lies a shrine. This shrine has been corrupted.","Yes. Beneath this Temple, there is a large sewer system, built around the ruins of Old Mournhold. You smell like you may have spent some time there.... Regardless, in these ruins, there lies a shrine. This shrine has been corrupted.","fbmwTRShrineDead_1serviceStoSourSLady_00f8ba3b_1"
"","","Shrine of the Dead",Neutral,50,"There is nothing further to say about that.","There is nothing further to say about that.","fbmwTRShrineDead_1ShrineSofStheSDead_00f8ba40_1"
"","","Shrine of the Dead",Neutral,50,"Interesting. You've performed your duty well. The goddess is very pleased. Take this Blessed Spear as a gift from the Lady Almalexia. It is good that you have been of service to our Lady.","Interesting. You've performed your duty well. The goddess is very pleased. Take this Blessed Spear as a gift from the Lady Almalexia. It is good that you have been of service to our Lady.","fbmwTRShrineDead_1ShrineSofStheSDead_00f8ba41_1"
"","","Shrine of the Dead",Neutral,50,"Urvel Dulni is dead, and there is no one to cleanse the shrine. This is a disappointment.","Urvel Dulni is dead, and there is no one to cleanse the shrine. This is a disappointment.","fbmwTRShrineDead_1ShrineSofStheSDead_00f8ba42_1"
"","","Shrine of the Dead",Neutral,50,"You allowed Urvel Dulni to die? Fool...but at least you managed to get the Shrine cleansed. He wasn't the best of priests, anyway. You were to be of service to our Lady, not get one of her followers killed.","You allowed Urvel Dulni to die? Fool...but at least you managed to get the Shrine cleansed. He wasn't the best of priests, anyway. You were to be of service to our Lady, not get one of her followers killed.","fbmwTRShrineDead_1ShrineSofStheSDead_00f8ba43_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But, the Lady demands you be rewarded for your troubles. Her wisdom be praised. Take this.","But, the Lady demands you be rewarded for your troubles. Her wisdom be praised. Take this.","fbmwTRShrineDead_1ShrineSofStheSDead_00f8ba43_2"
"","","Shrine of the Dead",Neutral,50,"You allowed Urvel Dulni to die? Fool! The Lady will not be pleased by this. And you did not get the Shrine cleansed. Pathetic. You were to be of service to our Lady, yet you have failed miserably. Pathetic and typical.","You allowed Urvel Dulni to die? Fool! The Lady will not be pleased by this. And you did not get the Shrine cleansed. Pathetic. You were to be of service to our Lady, yet you have failed miserably. Pathetic and typical.","fbmwTRShrineDead_1ShrineSofStheSDead_00f8ba44_1"
"","","Shrine of the Dead",Neutral,50,"Take Urvel Dulni there and allow him to perform the ritual.","Take Urvel Dulni there and allow him to perform the ritual.","fbmwTRShrineDead_1ShrineSofStheSDead_00f8ba45_1"
"","","Shrine of the Dead",Neutral,50,"As I said, it holds immense power to speak with the ancestors and harness their power. The Lady Almalexia wishes to use this power for the good of Morrowind. I realize that ancestor worship falls a bit...","As I said, it holds immense power to speak with the ancestors and harness their power. The Lady Almalexia wishes to use this power for the good of Morrowind. I realize that ancestor worship falls a bit...","fbmwTRShrineDead_1ShrineSofStheSDead_00f8ba46_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"outside traditional Temple doctrine, but the Lady knows best, and her will is law. To find the Shrine, enter the sewers through the Temple basement. ","outside traditional Temple doctrine, but the Lady knows best, and her will is law. To find the Shrine, enter the sewers through the Temple basement.","fbmwTRShrineDead_1ShrineSofStheSDead_00f8ba46_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Then head east to the ruined Temple Gardens, and south to the Shrine of the Dead.","Then head east to the ruined Temple Gardens, and south to the Shrine of the Dead.","fbmwTRShrineDead_1ShrineSofStheSDead_00f8ba46_3"
"","","Shrine of the Dead",Neutral,50,"You allowed Urvel Dulni to die? Fool...but at least you managed to get the Shrine cleansed. He wasn't the best of priests, anyway.","You allowed Urvel Dulni to die? Fool...but at least you managed to get the Shrine cleansed. He wasn't the best of priests, anyway.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ShrineSofStheSDead_00320a53_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You were to be of service to our Lady, not get one of her followers killed. But, the Lady demands you be rewarded for your troubles.","You were to be of service to our Lady, not get one of her followers killed. But, the Lady demands you be rewarded for your troubles.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ShrineSofStheSDead_00320a53_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Her wisdom be praised. Take this.","Her wisdom be praised. Take this.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ShrineSofStheSDead_00320a53_3"
"","","Shrine of the Dead",Neutral,50,"You allowed Urvel Dulni to die? Fool! The Lady will not be pleased by this. And you did not get the Shrine cleansed. Pathetic.","You allowed Urvel Dulni to die? Fool! The Lady will not be pleased by this. And you did not get the Shrine cleansed. Pathetic.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ShrineSofStheSDead_00320a54_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You were to be of service to our Lady, yet you have failed miserably. Pathetic and typical.","You were to be of service to our Lady, yet you have failed miserably. Pathetic and typical.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ShrineSofStheSDead_00320a54_2"
"","","Must be cleansed",Neutral,50,"No...certainly not by you. This task falls to one of Almalexia's chosen. You will escort this young priest, Urvel Dulni, to the shrine. Protect him well.","No...certainly not by you. This task falls to one of Almalexia's chosen. You will escort this young priest, Urvel Dulni, to the shrine. Protect him well.","fbmwTRShrineDead_1mustSbeScleansed_00f8ba50_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"His experience is limited, but he is necessary to complete the ritual. The Shrine is protected by the Profane, powerful liches who feed from the power of the shrine.","His experience is limited, but he is necessary to complete the ritual. The Shrine is protected by the Profane, powerful liches who feed from the power of the shrine.","fbmwTRShrineDead_1mustSbeScleansed_00f8ba50_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You must destroy them for Dulni to perform his duties. I stress again...protect Dulni at all costs. It is he who must perform the ceremony. If he is not able, there are no others.","You must destroy them for Dulni to perform his duties. I stress again...protect Dulni at all costs. It is he who must perform the ceremony. If he is not able, there are no others.","fbmwTRShrineDead_1mustSbeScleansed_00f8ba50_3"
"","","Tienius Delitian",Neutral,50,"I heard Captain Delitian had been murdered. Such is the way of soldiers.","I heard Captain Delitian had been murdered. Such is the way of soldiers.","MorroDefaultQuest_1TieniusSDelitian_00320e05_1"
"","","Tienius Delitian",Neutral,50,"The soldier? I have little use for him. He is concerned only with the physical: how sharp is his blade, how polished his breastplate.","The soldier? I have little use for him. He is concerned only with the physical: how sharp is his blade, how polished his breastplate.","MorroDefaultQuest_1TieniusSDelitian_00320e0d_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"True strength comes from within, by the mercy of our Lady.","True strength comes from within, by the mercy of our Lady.","MorroDefaultQuest_1TieniusSDelitian_00320e0d_2"
"","","High Ordinators",Neutral,50,"The High Ordinators keep the peace here in Mournhold. Only the finest and most devout are chosen to be of their ranks.","The High Ordinators keep the peace here in Mournhold. Only the finest and most devout are chosen to be of their ranks.","MorroDefaultQuest_1HighSOrdinators_00321012_1"
"","","Talen Vandas",Neutral,50,"Oh, I knew young Talen. He was a fine young man. And King Llethan loved him like a son. I wonder if the truth about his death will ever be discovered.","Oh, I knew young Talen. He was a fine young man. And King Llethan loved him like a son. I wonder if the truth about his death will ever be discovered.","MorroDefaultQuest_1TalenSVandas_00321b38_1"
"","","Fedris Hler",Neutral,50,"Fedris Hler has been found dead! This is a very sad time for us here at the Temple. But, by the Grace of Our Lady, we will find the culprit.","Fedris Hler has been found dead! This is a very sad time for us here at the Temple. But, by the Grace of Our Lady, we will find the culprit.","MorroDefaultQuest_1FedrisSHler_00321d8f_1"
"","","Fedris Hler",Neutral,50,"Fedris Hler is the Lady Almalexia's Steward. You may find him in his office in the Temple Reception area.","Fedris Hler is the Lady Almalexia's Steward. You may find him in his office in the Temple Reception area.","MorroDefaultQuest_1FedrisSHler_00321d90_1"
"","","Royal Guard",Neutral,50,"Young King Helseth's handpicked thugs. Ridiculous that they are allowed to dispense justice in the Lady's city.","Young King Helseth's handpicked thugs. Ridiculous that they are allowed to dispense justice in the Lady's city.","MorroDefaultQuest_1RoyalSGuard_00321de4_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The High Ordinators do a fine job of keeping the peace around here.","The High Ordinators do a fine job of keeping the peace around here.","MorroDefaultQuest_1RoyalSGuard_00321de4_2"
"","","Gavas Drin",Neutral,50,"I am the Lord Archcanon Gavas Drin. The grace of the Lady be with you.","I am the Lord Archcanon Gavas Drin. The grace of the Lady be with you.","MorroDefaultQuest_1GavasSDrin_00322104_1"
"","","Barenziah",Neutral,50,"I've not had the pleasure of her company, myself. Perhaps I'm one of the few. I'll say this: she's much loved by the people of the city.","I've not had the pleasure of her company, myself. Perhaps I'm one of the few. I'll say this: she's much loved by the people of the city.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Barenziah_003225e6_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"They should remember who truly deserves their love and admiration. All praise to our Lady of Mercy.","They should remember who truly deserves their love and admiration. All praise to our Lady of Mercy.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Barenziah_003225e6_2"
"","","Helseth",Neutral,50,"So, the young king is dead. I'm sure there will be another to replace him soon.","So, the young king is dead. I'm sure there will be another to replace him soon.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Helseth_00322954_1"
"","","Helseth",Neutral,50,"Helseth is Morrowind's new king, replacing his recently deceased great-uncle, Athyn Llethan.","Helseth is Morrowind's new king, replacing his recently deceased great-uncle, Athyn Llethan.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Helseth_00322955_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"This child king is a fool, raised by Imperials, educated by Altmer. He knows nothing of the Dunmer people. Have you seen his ears?","This child king is a fool, raised by Imperials, educated by Altmer. He knows nothing of the Dunmer people. Have you seen his ears?","MorroDefaultQuest_1Helseth_00322955_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"He had them cropped to look more Imperial! He is a fool, and a dangerous one.","He had them cropped to look more Imperial! He is a fool, and a dangerous one.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Helseth_00322955_3"
