Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"All the trees and plants, tended lawns and paths, are hymns of praise to Almalexia's name. It's humble work, sera, but I'm very proud of it.","All the trees and plants, tended lawns and paths, are hymns of praise to Almalexia's name. It's humble work, sera, but I'm very proud of it.","MorroDefaultQuest_GREETING_00014c43_1"
"","","Trels Varis",Neutral,50,"My wife says she doesn't know where he is? Well, Granny is getting right forgetful in her old age. Of course Trels is in Kragenmoor, like I said.","My wife says she doesn't know where he is? Well, Granny is getting right forgetful in her old age. Of course Trels is in Kragenmoor, like I said.","fbmwTR09_1TrelsSVaris_00f8ba79_1"
"","","Trels Varis",Neutral,50,"My son, Trels Varis? He's in Kragenmoor, out west near Cyrodiil. He's a scholar in a private Temple school.","My son, Trels Varis? He's in Kragenmoor, out west near Cyrodiil. He's a scholar in a private Temple school.","fbmwTR09_1TrelsSVaris_00f8ba7a_1"
