Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Alms for the poor",Neutral,50,"Sorry. I can't help you.","Sorry. I can't help you.","fbmwICBuckmothAlms_1almsSforStheSpoor_00f8a33f_1"
"","","Blades Trainers",Neutral,50,"Certainly I offer basic training at low prices to colleagues. But even at my low prices, advanced training isn't cheap.","Certainly I offer basic training at low prices to colleagues. But even at my low prices, advanced training isn't cheap.","fbmwBladesTrainers_1BladesSTrainers_0032109c_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Sorry, but that's the way it is. Look. Can I make a suggestion? Go see Wayn at the Balmora Guild of Fighters. Know what a jink blade is?","Sorry, but that's the way it is. Look. Can I make a suggestion? Go see Wayn at the Balmora Guild of Fighters. Know what a jink blade is?","fbmwBladesTrainers_1BladesSTrainers_0032109c_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"It has a Paralyze enchantment. And a spider blade has a Poison enchantment. They're not considered honorable weapons, and most smiths don't sell them.","It has a Paralyze enchantment. And a spider blade has a Poison enchantment. They're not considered honorable weapons, and most smiths don't sell them.","fbmwBladesTrainers_1BladesSTrainers_0032109c_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But they sure come in handy.","But they sure come in handy.","fbmwBladesTrainers_1BladesSTrainers_0032109c_4"
"","","Latest Rumors",Neutral,50,"I keep tabs on Redoran's conflicts with Hlaalu and Telvanni. It's fairly easy.","I keep tabs on Redoran's conflicts with Hlaalu and Telvanni. It's fairly easy.","MorroDefaultQuest_1latestSrumors_003215fb_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The Redoran Council is public and above-board, and they openly fund and support strikes against the rogue Telvanni bases.","The Redoran Council is public and above-board, and they openly fund and support strikes against the rogue Telvanni bases.","MorroDefaultQuest_1latestSrumors_003215fb_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The dispute over Caldera with Hlaalu is more subtle.","The dispute over Caldera with Hlaalu is more subtle.","MorroDefaultQuest_1latestSrumors_003215fb_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Redoran feels it should jurisdiction over the ebony mines, but Hlaalu and the Caldera Mining Company out-maneuvered them.","Redoran feels it should jurisdiction over the ebony mines, but Hlaalu and the Caldera Mining Company out-maneuvered them.","MorroDefaultQuest_1latestSrumors_003215fb_4"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Either one of those conflicts could flare into open war. Little we can do about it, but keep the Legion informed.","Either one of those conflicts could flare into open war. Little we can do about it, but keep the Legion informed.","MorroDefaultQuest_1latestSrumors_003215fb_5"
"","","Blades",Neutral,50,"I'm a Blade, too, and I report to Caius, like you. You're welcome to use my bed to rest, but leave my other stuff alone, please.","I'm a Blade, too, and I report to Caius, like you. You're welcome to use my bed to rest, but leave my other stuff alone, please.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Blades_00322b44_1"
