Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"What it is, friend?","What it is, friend?","fbmwCO8_GREETING_00014bff_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"You...  you are not here to hurt us? Then perhaps you are different from the rest. You seek knowledge of the Stalhrim, yes?","You...  you are not here to hurt us? Then perhaps you are different from the rest. You seek knowledge of the Stalhrim, yes?","fbmwCO8_GREETING_00014c04_1"
"","","GREETING",Disgust,50,"We will have no dealings with the likes of you. Begone.","We will have no dealings with the likes of you. Begone.","fbmwCO8a_GREETING_00014c03_1"
"","","Misuse it",Neutral,50,"I do not believe you will put these things to a bad use, Outlander. You are not like the others.","I do not believe you will put these things to a bad use, Outlander. You are not like the others.","fbmwCO8_1misuseSit_00014bfc_1"
"","","Misuse it",Neutral,50,"We learned that Stalhrim can be forged much like iron or steel. We were made outcasts for it;","We learned that Stalhrim can be forged much like iron or steel. We were made outcasts for it;","fbmwCO8_1misuseSit_00014bfe_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The Skaal are too narrow-minded to understand its practical value. Some, like this woman, hear of it and come seeking it, but will not get it from us","The Skaal are too narrow-minded to understand its practical value. Some, like this woman, hear of it and come seeking it, but will not get it from us","fbmwCO8_1misuseSit_00014bfe_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You, however, have earned my respect. We will now see if you can truly be trusted - take this pick axe, and use it to chip off a piece of Stalhrim.","You, however, have earned my respect. We will now see if you can truly be trusted - take this pick axe, and use it to chip off a piece of Stalhrim.","fbmwCO8_1misuseSit_00014bfe_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Bring that piece to me.","Bring that piece to me.","fbmwCO8_1misuseSit_00014bfe_4"
"","","Stalhrim",Neutral,50,"You have some of it? I shall not take it from you; that you were willing to bring it is proof enough.","You have some of it? I shall not take it from you; that you were willing to bring it is proof enough.","fbmwCO8_1Stalhrim_00014c0c_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Now that I now you can be trusted, you may come to us at any time, and we will construct for you armor and weapons. Speak to Aenar and Hidar.","Now that I now you can be trusted, you may come to us at any time, and we will construct for you armor and weapons. Speak to Aenar and Hidar.","fbmwCO8_1Stalhrim_00014c0c_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"They will do these things for you with my blessing.","They will do these things for you with my blessing.","fbmwCO8_1Stalhrim_00014c0c_3"
"","","Stalhrim",Neutral,50,"Bring me some of it, so that I may know you can be trusted. Then, we shall speak more of it.","Bring me some of it, so that I may know you can be trusted. Then, we shall speak more of it.","fbmwCO8_1Stalhrim_00014c0a_1"
"","","Stalhrim",Neutral,50,"You are not the first to seek it. Outsiders like this woman have been here before; always demanding, always offering payment that is useless to us.","You are not the first to seek it. Outsiders like this woman have been here before; always demanding, always offering payment that is useless to us.","fbmwCO8_1Stalhrim_00014c0b_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But they get nothing. The Skaal give them nothing because they call it sacred; we give them nothing because we know they would misuse it.","But they get nothing. The Skaal give them nothing because they call it sacred; we give them nothing because we know they would misuse it.","fbmwCO8_1Stalhrim_00014c0b_2"
"","","Stalhrim",Neutral,50,"You have some with you? Talk to Aenar if you wish to have armor crafted; Hidar will forge weapons for you.","You have some with you? Talk to Aenar if you wish to have armor crafted; Hidar will forge weapons for you.","fbmwCO8_1Stalhrim_00322904_1"
"","","Sacred",Neutral,50,"The Skaal consider the Stalhrim to be holy. During the great war with the Dark Elves, many heroes fell in battle.","The Skaal consider the Stalhrim to be holy. During the great war with the Dark Elves, many heroes fell in battle.","MorroDefaultQuest_1sacred_00322cdc_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Some could not be returned to Skyrim, and were buried here.","Some could not be returned to Skyrim, and were buried here.","MorroDefaultQuest_1sacred_00322cdc_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Great magicks were worked on their tombs to protect their belongings from grave robbers, and their corpses from worse things.","Great magicks were worked on their tombs to protect their belongings from grave robbers, and their corpses from worse things.","MorroDefaultQuest_1sacred_00322cdc_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Energy was drawn from the land itself, and our heroes were encased in tombs of ice. That ice is Stalhrim.","Energy was drawn from the land itself, and our heroes were encased in tombs of ice. That ice is Stalhrim.","MorroDefaultQuest_1sacred_00322cdc_4"
