Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Salutations. Can I help you find something? Looking for beds for rent? Perhaps you'd be interested in helping me with some work I need taken care of?","Salutations. Can I help you find something? Looking for beds for rent? Perhaps you'd be interested in helping me with some work I need taken care of?","fbmwMSGreetings_GREETING_00f8b99a_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Salutations. I don't need any more help right now. Are you maybe looking for beds for rent?","Salutations. I don't need any more help right now. Are you maybe looking for beds for rent?","fbmwMSBouncer_GREETING_00f8b9d0_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Have you taken care of all the problems out there?","Have you taken care of all the problems out there?","fbmwMSBouncer_GREETING_00f8b9d1_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"You still haven't taken care of your bouncer duties. I can spot one drunk from here. Head back out and make sure this place is free from troublemakers like that.","You still haven't taken care of your bouncer duties. I can spot one drunk from here. Head back out and make sure this place is free from troublemakers like that.","fbmwMSBouncer_GREETING_00f8b9d2_1"
"","","Bed",Neutral,50,"Yes, we have one available. It's 10 gold for the rest of the day. Do you want it?","Yes, we have one available. It's 10 gold for the rest of the day. Do you want it?",""
"","","Bed",Happy,20,"Hope it suits you!","Hope it suits you!",""
"","","I'll take it.",Neutral,50,"Very well, the bed is yours for the day. You'll find the room on the bottom floor, at the North end of the bar.","Very well, the bed is yours for the day. You'll find the room on the bottom floor, at the North end of the bar.",""
"","","I'll take it.",Neutral,50,"Sorry. Doesn't look like you can afford it. Maybe another time.","Sorry. Doesn't look like you can afford it. Maybe another time.",""
"","","All the problems out there",Neutral,50,"Thank you for your assistance.","Thank you for your assistance.","fbmwMSBouncer_1allStheSproblemsSoutSthere_0001c687_1"
"","","All the problems out there",Neutral,50,"Yes, you know, the drunks and the vagrants and the ne'er-do-wells. Did you find them all and take care of them?","Yes, you know, the drunks and the vagrants and the ne'er-do-wells. Did you find them all and take care of them?","fbmwMSBouncer_1allStheSproblemsSoutSthere_0032042e_1"
"","","Some Work",Neutral,50,"Yes, well, you see my usual bouncer, Grub, didn't show today. Probably got lost in the Pavilion again, the Orcish ninny.  Anyway, would you be willing to stand in for him?","Yes, well, you see my usual bouncer, Grub, didn't show today. Probably got lost in the Pavilion again, the Orcish ninny.  Anyway, would you be willing to stand in for him?","fbmwMSBouncer_1someSwork_00f8ab7d_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"All you would have to do is make one sweep through the bar crowd. If memory serves, we don't get too many people coming and going this time of day. What do you say? Are you up for it?","All you would have to do is make one sweep through the bar crowd. If memory serves, we don't get too many people coming and going this time of day. What do you say? Are you up for it?","fbmwMSBouncer_1someSwork_00f8ab7d_2"
"","","Yes, I've taken care of everything.",Neutral,50,"Thank you for the assistance, but I really don't appreciate having my patrons KILLED on premises, no matter how drunk they are.","Thank you for the assistance, but I really don't appreciate having my patrons KILLED on premises, no matter how drunk they are.","fbmwMSBouncer_1allStheSproblemsSoutSthere1_0001c68d_1"
"","","",Neutral,50," I'll take that idiot Orc, Grub, over you any day of the week.","I'll take that idiot Orc, Grub, over you any day of the week.","fbmwMSBouncer_1allStheSproblemsSoutSthere1_0001c68d_2"
"","","",Neutral,50," At least you got Galms to stop hustling, so I suppose you're worth something after all.  Here, take these wages for your work.","At least you got Galms to stop hustling, so I suppose you're worth something after all.  Here, take these wages for your work.","fbmwMSBouncer_1allStheSproblemsSoutSthere1_0001c68d_3"
"","","Yes, I've taken care of everything.",Neutral,50,"Thank you for the assistance, but I really don't appreciate having my patrons KILLED on premises, no matter how drunk they are.","Thank you for the assistance, but I really don't appreciate having my patrons KILLED on premises, no matter how drunk they are.","fbmwMSBouncer_1allStheSproblemsSoutSthere1_0001c68c_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I'll take that idiot Orc, Grub, over you any day of the week. Here, take these wages and get out of my sight.","I'll take that idiot Orc, Grub, over you any day of the week. Here, take these wages and get out of my sight.","fbmwMSBouncer_1allStheSproblemsSoutSthere1_0001c68c_2"
"","","Yes, I've taken care of everything.",Neutral,50,"Thank you for the assistance, but I really don't appreciate having my patrons KILLED on premises, no matter how drunk they are.","Thank you for the assistance, but I really don't appreciate having my patrons KILLED on premises, no matter how drunk they are.","fbmwMSBouncer_1allStheSproblemsSoutSthere1_0001c68b_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I'll take that idiot Orc, Grub, over you any day of the week. At least you got Galms to stop hustling, so I suppose you're worth something after all.","I'll take that idiot Orc, Grub, over you any day of the week. At least you got Galms to stop hustling, so I suppose you're worth something after all.","fbmwMSBouncer_1allStheSproblemsSoutSthere1_0001c68b_2"
"","","Yes, I've taken care of everything.",Neutral,50,"Fantastic. You took care of a drunk and got a hustler to stop hustling. Grub couldn't have done it better himself. Here's your payment.","Fantastic. You took care of a drunk and got a hustler to stop hustling. Grub couldn't have done it better himself. Here's your payment.","fbmwMSBouncer_1allStheSproblemsSoutSthere1_0001c689_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And thank you.","And thank you.","fbmwMSBouncer_1allStheSproblemsSoutSthere1_0001c689_2"
"","","Yes, I've taken care of everything.",Neutral,50,"Great, although I still have a bad feeling about things. Oh, well, here's your payment. Thanks a lot for your help.","Great, although I still have a bad feeling about things. Oh, well, here's your payment. Thanks a lot for your help.","fbmwMSBouncer_1allStheSproblemsSoutSthere1_0001c688_1"
"","","Yes, I've taken care of everything.",Neutral,50,"Look, you still haven't taken care of that drunk.","Look, you still haven't taken care of that drunk.","fbmwMSBouncer_1allStheSproblemsSoutSthere1_00f8e9cc_1"
"","","No, I'm not quite done yet.",Neutral,50,"Well, let me know when you are.","Well, let me know when you are.","fbmwMSBouncer_1allStheSproblemsSoutSthere2_00f8ab85_1"
"","","Yes, I can do that.",Neutral,50,"Fantastic!  Here's all you have to do:  Go around and talk to everyone in the bar.","Fantastic!  Here's all you have to do:  Go around and talk to everyone in the bar.","fbmwMSBouncer_1someSwork1_00323596_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If they're too drunk, or unruly, or just a bad character, throw them out. Report to me when you're done.","If they're too drunk, or unruly, or just a bad character, throw them out. Report to me when you're done.","fbmwMSBouncer_1someSwork1_00323596_2"
"","","No thanks. I don't have the time.",Neutral,50,"Well, that's okay.  I'm sure Grub will be making his way back here... eventually.","Well, that's okay.  I'm sure Grub will be making his way back here... eventually.","fbmwMSBouncer_1someSwork2_00323597_1"
