Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Hail and well met stranger!  As ye can plainly see, I require some assistance if ye be kind enough to grant it. I need help finding the festering witch has robbed me blind and left me for dead.","Hail and well met stranger!  As ye can plainly see, I require some assistance if ye be kind enough to grant it. I need help finding the festering witch has robbed me blind and left me for dead.","fbmwMSGreetings_GREETING_00f8876e_1"
"","","GREETING",Happy,50,"You have Cloudcleaver, my friend. I would like it back.","You have Cloudcleaver, my friend. I would like it back.","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_GREETING_000033fa_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Seems a bit chilly today, doesn't it?","Seems a bit chilly today, doesn't it?","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_GREETING_00f8876f_1"
"","","Taking Cloudcleaver",Neutral,50,"Yes, let me hold her in my hands - ah, my pretty, I've missed you so....","Yes, let me hold her in my hands - ah, my pretty, I've missed you so....","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1takingSCloudcleaver_00f8aa4a_1"
"","","Festering Witch",Neutral,50,"It is good she is dead.","It is good she is dead.","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1festeringSwitch_00f8aab0_1"
"","","Festering Witch",Neutral,50,"I've no more to say to you, coward. Get out of my sight.","I've no more to say to you, coward. Get out of my sight.","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1festeringSwitch_00f8aab1_1"
"","","Festering Witch",Neutral,50,"That she is. She must pay for what she's done to me!","That she is. She must pay for what she's done to me!","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1festeringSwitch_00f8aab2_1"
"","","Festering Witch",Neutral,50,"Onward friend, we must find this witch before she moves again. I can feel Cloudcleaver calling out to me to rescue it from the clutches of evil.","Onward friend, we must find this witch before she moves again. I can feel Cloudcleaver calling out to me to rescue it from the clutches of evil.","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1festeringSwitch_00f8aab3_1"
"","","Festering Witch",Neutral,50,"A witch she had to be. I was on my way to Caldera when I met her. She was a stranger here like myself, and our conversations lightened the burden of travel.","A witch she had to be. I was on my way to Caldera when I met her. She was a stranger here like myself, and our conversations lightened the burden of travel.","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1festeringSwitch_00f8aab4_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"She was quite friendly and, well, y'know, we set up camp together. But that night she revealed the witch inside. Cast a spell on me. I couldn't so much as blink!","She was quite friendly and, well, y'know, we set up camp together. But that night she revealed the witch inside. Cast a spell on me. I couldn't so much as blink!","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1festeringSwitch_00f8aab4_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Stole everything, even my worn out clothes, but most importantly, she took my prized axe Cloudcleaver. Join with me, stranger! And let's find her and extract her entrails together!","Stole everything, even my worn out clothes, but most importantly, she took my prized axe Cloudcleaver. Join with me, stranger! And let's find her and extract her entrails together!","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1festeringSwitch_00f8aab4_3"
"","","Sosia's Offer",Neutral,50,"Well I'll not be waiting another three days to have me bloody axe when it is in the hands of that damned witch!  Are you going to help me, friend, or are you believing the lies spilling out of that witch's face?","Well I'll not be waiting another three days to have me bloody axe when it is in the hands of that damned witch!  Are you going to help me, friend, or are you believing the lies spilling out of that witch's face?","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1SosiaAsSoffer_00f8a5b8_1"
"","","Cloudcleaver",Neutral,50,"I'm not sure how you got your hands on it again, but I'll have that axe back now!","I'm not sure how you got your hands on it again, but I'll have that axe back now!","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1Cloudcleaver_00f8a5fe_1"
"","","Cloudcleaver",Neutral,50,"Yes, let me hold her in my hands. Ah, my pretty, I've missed you so....","Yes, let me hold her in my hands. Ah, my pretty, I've missed you so....","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1Cloudcleaver_00321ce9_1"
"","","Cloudcleaver",Neutral,50,"Yes, let me hold her in my hands. Ah, my pretty, I've missed you so....","Yes, let me hold her in my hands. Ah, my pretty, I've missed you so....","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1Cloudcleaver_00321cea_1"
"","","Cloudcleaver",Neutral,50,"Ah, me axe Cloudcleaver. A fine blade she is, though now I fear what that witch's touch will do to it. Me own father Balmir used it himself to slay the Terror of Wrothgar's Quamire, he did.","Ah, me axe Cloudcleaver. A fine blade she is, though now I fear what that witch's touch will do to it. Me own father Balmir used it himself to slay the Terror of Wrothgar's Quamire, he did.","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1Cloudcleaver_00f8a5ff_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Now granted the Terror turned out to be a new born nix-hound eating the neighbor's marshmerrow, but me father found him and slew him nevertheless in as grand a fashion as I have ever borne witness to.","Now granted the Terror turned out to be a new born nix-hound eating the neighbor's marshmerrow, but me father found him and slew him nevertheless in as grand a fashion as I have ever borne witness to.","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1Cloudcleaver_00f8a5ff_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I cannot wait to have the blade in my hands again, then I'll use it to take that witch's head clean off, I will.","I cannot wait to have the blade in my hands again, then I'll use it to take that witch's head clean off, I will.","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1Cloudcleaver_00f8a5ff_3"
"","","Cloudcleaver",Neutral,50,"A fine axe it is. Perhaps the best ever crafted.","A fine axe it is. Perhaps the best ever crafted.","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1Cloudcleaver_00321ceb_1"
"","","Bloody Lies",Neutral,50,"That's right, they're all damn lies!  Is that a doubting look I see in your eye, friend?  Whose side are you on here?","That's right, they're all damn lies!  Is that a doubting look I see in your eye, friend?  Whose side are you on here?","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1bloodySlies_00f8ab19_1"
"","","My Trade",Neutral,50,"Makes me living as a fighter for hire I do. Learned the way as a lad in the basement of every seedy bar in Windhelm.","Makes me living as a fighter for hire I do. Learned the way as a lad in the basement of every seedy bar in Windhelm.","MorroDefaultQuest_1myStrade_0032277e_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"After me father's life was claimed by the snow elves, I had to provide for meself with odd mercenary jobs.","After me father's life was claimed by the snow elves, I had to provide for meself with odd mercenary jobs.","MorroDefaultQuest_1myStrade_0032277e_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I'm good with me fists, and better with me axe. I came to Vvardenfell once it was opened to search out some new fortune among these damn dark elves.","I'm good with me fists, and better with me axe. I came to Vvardenfell once it was opened to search out some new fortune among these damn dark elves.","MorroDefaultQuest_1myStrade_0032277e_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Now look what's happened to me.","Now look what's happened to me.","MorroDefaultQuest_1myStrade_0032277e_4"
"","","Here's your axe, Hlomar.",Neutral,50,"Ah, thank you friend. I noticed you admiring the way I fought that old witch, even without the aid of a sharp blade.","Ah, thank you friend. I noticed you admiring the way I fought that old witch, even without the aid of a sharp blade.","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1takingSCloudcleaver1_00323062_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I don't have any money or treasure to thank you for your help with, but I can give you a few pointers that will help you be stronger in a fight.","I don't have any money or treasure to thank you for your help with, but I can give you a few pointers that will help you be stronger in a fight.","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1takingSCloudcleaver1_00323062_2"
"","","No. I'm keeping it.",Neutral,50,"That is a poor, poor decision on your part, friend.","That is a poor, poor decision on your part, friend.","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1takingSCloudcleaver2_00323063_1"
"","","I have too much else to do.",Neutral,50,"Bah, I took you for a coward the moment I saw you!  Stand aside then and make way for any real warriors who be walking this path.","Bah, I took you for a coward the moment I saw you!  Stand aside then and make way for any real warriors who be walking this path.","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1festeringSwitch3_0032322b_1"
"","","I will help you find her.",Neutral,50,"I knew you had the bloodlust in you, stranger!","I knew you had the bloodlust in you, stranger!","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1festeringSwitch2_0032322c_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I believe she is still camped where I left her up to the northwest, though I could be wrong as the spell disoriented me a bit, it did.","I believe she is still camped where I left her up to the northwest, though I could be wrong as the spell disoriented me a bit, it did.","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1festeringSwitch2_0032322c_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You know this area better than me -- lead the way! This witch shall rue the day she met Hlormar Wine-Sot!","You know this area better than me -- lead the way! This witch shall rue the day she met Hlormar Wine-Sot!","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1festeringSwitch2_0032322c_3"
"","","I believe Sosia.",Neutral,50,"Then you will die alongside her!","Then you will die alongside her!","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1SosiaAsSoffer5_0032336a_1"
"","","I'll side with you.",Neutral,50,"Then let's show this witch the way to her grave together!","Then let's show this witch the way to her grave together!","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1SosiaAsSoffer4_0032336b_1"
"","","Continue.",Neutral,50,"That is a poor, poor decision on your part, friend.","That is a poor, poor decision on your part, friend.","fbmwTownBalmora_1littleSstory1_0032343f_1"
"","","Here's your axe, Hlormar.",Neutral,50,"Ah, thank you friend. I noticed you admiring the way I fought that old witch, even without the aid of a sharp blade.","Ah, thank you friend. I noticed you admiring the way I fought that old witch, even without the aid of a sharp blade.","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1Cloudcleaver6_00323440_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I don't have any money or treasure to thank you for your help with, but I can give you a few pointers that will help you be stronger in a fight.","I don't have any money or treasure to thank you for your help with, but I can give you a few pointers that will help you be stronger in a fight.","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1Cloudcleaver6_00323440_2"
"","","I'll side with you.",Neutral,50,"Then let's show this witch the way to her grave together!","Then let's show this witch the way to her grave together!","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1bloodySlies4_003234a1_1"
"","","I believe Sosia.",Neutral,50,"Then you will die alongside her!","Then you will die alongside her!","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_1bloodySlies5_00f8aba6_1"
"","","It belongs with a true warrior. Me.",Neutral,50,"That is a poor, poor decision on your part, friend.","That is a poor, poor decision on your part, friend.","fbmwMVAbusedHealer_fbmwmshealerkeepsword_00f8a971_1"
