Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Welcome, Incarnate. I am Hort-Ledd. I was not the one. But I wait and hope. Ask, and I shall tell you my story.","Welcome, Incarnate. I am Hort-Ledd. I was not the one. But I wait and hope. Ask, and I shall tell you my story.","fbmwMQ10_GREETING_0000a231_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I wait and hope. Ask, and I shall tell you my story.","I wait and hope. Ask, and I shall tell you my story.","fbmwMQ10_GREETING_0000a232_1"
"","","Nerevarine",Neutral,50,"You are the Nerevarine. You are the Incarnate. You are the one. You must not fail.","You are the Nerevarine. You are the Incarnate. You are the one. You must not fail.","fbmwMQ10_1Nerevarine_00322272_1"
"","","Background",Neutral,50,"I am Hort Ledd. I was called to the prophecies, but I was not the one.","I am Hort Ledd. I was called to the prophecies, but I was not the one.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Background_0032219c_1"
"","","Background",Neutral,50,"I am Hort-Ledd. I was called to the prophecies, but I was not the one.","I am Hort-Ledd. I was called to the prophecies, but I was not the one.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Background_003221ab_1"
"","","My Story",Neutral,50,"I died four hundred years ago, in the last days of turmoil and unrest after the Empire came to Morrowind.","I died four hundred years ago, in the last days of turmoil and unrest after the Empire came to Morrowind.","fbmwMQ10_1mySstory_00aa2dc6_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I was a thinker, and not a doer, and though I was marked by the stars, I was not a hero. Take these things of mine. My bones won't complain.","I was a thinker, and not a doer, and though I was marked by the stars, I was not a hero. Take these things of mine. My bones won't complain.","fbmwMQ10_1mySstory_00aa2dc6_2"
"","","My Trade",Neutral,50,"An ancestor has no trade, but to guard and counsel the living kin.","An ancestor has no trade, but to guard and counsel the living kin.","MorroDefaultQuest_1myStrade_00322778_1"
