Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I'm in here for some sort of blasphemy or something. Did it all right. Guild says serve your time, and keep your yap shut. So I'm being a good boy, and staying quiet.","I'm in here for some sort of blasphemy or something. Did it all right. Guild says serve your time, and keep your yap shut. So I'm being a good boy, and staying quiet.","fbmwMSGreetings_GREETING_00f88778_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I'm fine. Food's okay.","I'm fine. Food's okay.","fbmwMSGreetings_GREETING_00008779_1"
"","","Blasphemy",Neutral,50,"It was nothing, really. Just regular barracks talk.","It was nothing, really. Just regular barracks talk.","MorroDefaultQuest_1blasphemy_003224f4_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But there was a lady present, and this Redoran lord got up on his hind legs and was gonna slit me like a sturgeon. Better this way. Damn sight better.","But there was a lady present, and this Redoran lord got up on his hind legs and was gonna slit me like a sturgeon. Better this way. Damn sight better.","MorroDefaultQuest_1blasphemy_003224f4_2"
