Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Is that my glove?","Is that my glove?","fbmwILMaidenToken_GREETING_00f886ec_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Together we will work to end slavery in Vvardenfell.","Together we will work to end slavery in Vvardenfell.","fbmwHHAdvancement_GREETING_000100d3_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Yes, it's a shame so many people cannot read.","Yes, it's a shame so many people cannot read.","fbmwHHAdvancement_GREETING_000100d4_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I am Ilmeni Dren, daughter of Duke Vedam Dren. Who are you and what are you doing here?","I am Ilmeni Dren, daughter of Duke Vedam Dren. Who are you and what are you doing here?","fbmwHHAdvancement_GREETING_000100d5_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Yes, outlander?","Yes, outlander?","fbmwHHAdvancement_GREETING_000100d6_1"
"","","People Cannot Read",Neutral,50,"Vala Catraso is dead? Am I to believe that you are not responsible somehow? No, I shall not have any more business with you.","Vala Catraso is dead? Am I to believe that you are not responsible somehow? No, I shall not have any more business with you.","fbmwHHLiteracyCampaign_1peopleScannotSread_003209c7_1"
"","","People Cannot Read",Neutral,50,"You have done a good deed for Vala Catraso's students. You have my gratitude.","You have done a good deed for Vala Catraso's students. You have my gratitude.","fbmwHHLiteracyCampaign_1peopleScannotSread_000100d7_1"
"","","People Cannot Read",Neutral,50,"There are teachers in the Mages Guilds, but they often do not have enough books to teach from.","There are teachers in the Mages Guilds, but they often do not have enough books to teach from.","fbmwHHLiteracyCampaign_1peopleScannotSread_003209c8_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Go to a bookstore and find the books "Annotated Anuad' and "ABCs for Barbarians."","Go to a bookstore and find the books "Annotated Anuad' and "ABCs for Barbarians."","fbmwHHLiteracyCampaign_1peopleScannotSread_003209c8_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Bring a copy of each of these to Vala Catraso in the Ald'ruhn Guild of Mages.","Bring a copy of each of these to Vala Catraso in the Ald'ruhn Guild of Mages.","fbmwHHLiteracyCampaign_1peopleScannotSread_003209c8_3"
"","","Brallion's Ring",Neutral,50,"I sold the ring. Soon more slaves will be on their way back to Black Marsh or Elsweyr.","I sold the ring. Soon more slaves will be on their way back to Black Marsh or Elsweyr.","fbmwTGssGreedySlaver_1BrallionAsSRing_00f8a449_1"
"","","Brallion's Ring",Neutral,50,"Thank you.","Thank you.","fbmwTGssGreedySlaver_1BrallionAsSRing_00f8a44a_1"
"","","Brallion's Ring",Neutral,50,"What do I want with a slaver's ring?","What do I want with a slaver's ring?","fbmwTGssGreedySlaver_1BrallionAsSRing_00f8a44b_1"
"","","Maiden's Token",Neutral,50,"Yes, it is my glove.","Yes, it is my glove.","fbmwILMaidenToken_1maidenAsStoken_00321448_1"
"","","Ilmeni Dren",Neutral,50,"Yes?","Yes?","fbmwTGssGreedySlaver_1IlmeniSDren_00321ee5_1"
"","","Need Wives",Neutral,50,"I am spoken for, but if you have the idea I think you have, you should speak with Galyn Arvel in Ald Velothi.","I am spoken for, but if you have the idea I think you have, you should speak with Galyn Arvel in Ald Velothi.","fbmwHRStronghold_1needSwives_0000fc9d_1"
"","","Business",Neutral,50,"How can I trust you if you cannot stick to the simple rules of House Hlaalu?","How can I trust you if you cannot stick to the simple rules of House Hlaalu?","fbmwHHAdvancement_1business_0032270d_1"
"","","Business",Neutral,50,"You have done all that I would ask. Speak with Crassius Curio or my father, Duke Dren.","You have done all that I would ask. Speak with Crassius Curio or my father, Duke Dren.","fbmwHHAdvancement_1business_000100d0_1"
"","","Business",Neutral,50,"The real business of Vvardenfell is slavery.","The real business of Vvardenfell is slavery.","fbmwHHAdvancement_1business_000100cf_1"
"","","Business",Neutral,50,"Business? How can you talk about business when people cannot read?","Business? How can you talk about business when people cannot read?","fbmwHHAdvancement_1business_000100ce_1"
"","","Business",Neutral,50,"What business? Prove yourself in House Hlaalu and then perhaps we can discuss business.","What business? Prove yourself in House Hlaalu and then perhaps we can discuss business.","fbmwHHAdvancement_1business_0032270e_1"
"","","My glove",Neutral,50,"We won't be so careless in the future.","We won't be so careless in the future.","fbmwILMaidenToken_1mySglove_00f8a745_1"
"","","My glove",Neutral,50,"Where did you... No, I need not ask. Will you return the glove to me?","Where did you... No, I need not ask. Will you return the glove to me?","fbmwILMaidenToken_1mySglove_003228ca_1"
"","","Slavery",Neutral,50,"You have done all that I would ask. Continue to do the work of the Twin Lamps.","You have done all that I would ask. Continue to do the work of the Twin Lamps.","fbmwHHTwinLamps3_1slavery_00010a36_1"
"","","Slavery",Neutral,50,"I heard that you killed Sterdecan. You do not belong in the Twin Lamps.","I heard that you killed Sterdecan. You do not belong in the Twin Lamps.","fbmwHHTwinLamps3_1slavery_00010a35_1"
"","","Slavery",Neutral,50,"I heard that you killed Hides-His-Foot. You do not belong in the Twin Lamps.","I heard that you killed Hides-His-Foot. You do not belong in the Twin Lamps.","fbmwHHTwinLamps3_1slavery_00010a34_1"
"","","Slavery",Neutral,50,"You have saved Hides-His-Foot from slavery. I am grateful to you and I will speak to my father on your behalf.","You have saved Hides-His-Foot from slavery. I am grateful to you and I will speak to my father on your behalf.","fbmwHHTwinLamps3_1slavery_00010a33_1"
"","","Slavery",Neutral,50,"The slaves on the Dren Plantation suffer the worst.","The slaves on the Dren Plantation suffer the worst.","fbmwHHTwinLamps3_1slavery_00010a32_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"One of them knows things about Orvas Dren that are valuable to the Twin Lamps.","One of them knows things about Orvas Dren that are valuable to the Twin Lamps.","fbmwHHTwinLamps3_1slavery_00010a32_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"We can use him to blackmail Orvas Dren. I want you to free Hides-His-Foot from the Dren Plantation.","We can use him to blackmail Orvas Dren. I want you to free Hides-His-Foot from the Dren Plantation.","fbmwHHTwinLamps3_1slavery_00010a32_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Escort him to Sterdecan's Farm. Hides-His-Foot knows the way.","Escort him to Sterdecan's Farm. Hides-His-Foot knows the way.","fbmwHHTwinLamps3_1slavery_00010a32_4"
"","","Slavery",Neutral,50,"I heard that you killed Galyn Arvel. You do not belong in the Twin Lamps.","I heard that you killed Galyn Arvel. You do not belong in the Twin Lamps.","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1slavery_00322ac8_1"
"","","Slavery",Neutral,50,"I heard that you were responsible for the death of that poor Khajiit in Ald Velothi. I should have known better than to trust a foreigner.","I heard that you were responsible for the death of that poor Khajiit in Ald Velothi. I should have known better than to trust a foreigner.","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1slavery_00322ac9_1"
"","","Slavery",Neutral,50,"I heard that you killed Sterdecan. You do not belong in the Twin Lamps.","I heard that you killed Sterdecan. You do not belong in the Twin Lamps.","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1slavery_00322aca_1"
"","","Slavery",Neutral,50,"I heard that you killed Hides-His-Foot. You do not belong in the Twin Lamps.","I heard that you killed Hides-His-Foot. You do not belong in the Twin Lamps.","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1slavery_00322acb_1"
"","","Slavery",Neutral,50,"I heard that you helped the Arvel family. When you have time, speak with me again, for there is still much work to done.","I heard that you helped the Arvel family. When you have time, speak with me again, for there is still much work to done.","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1slavery_000100dc_1"
"","","Slavery",Neutral,50,"As I asked, go to Ald Velothi and speak with Galyn Arvel.","As I asked, go to Ald Velothi and speak with Galyn Arvel.","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1slavery_000100db_1"
"","","Slavery",Neutral,50,"Oh, have you seen the Twin Lamps?","Oh, have you seen the Twin Lamps?","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1slavery_000100da_1"
"","","Slavery",Neutral,50,"Oh, have you seen the Twin Lamps?","Oh, have you seen the Twin Lamps?","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1slavery_00322ad4_1"
"","","The ring is for you.",Neutral,50,"This is for me? What are you suggesting?","This is for me? What are you suggesting?","fbmwTGssGreedySlaver_1BrallionAsSRing3_0032321c_1"
"","","Never mind.",Neutral,50,"Keep it. I wouldn't wear that gaudy thing anyway.","Keep it. I wouldn't wear that gaudy thing anyway.","fbmwTGssGreedySlaver_1BrallionAsSRing4_00f8ab95_1"
"","","Yes, take it",Neutral,50,"Thank you, outlander. I am in your debt.","Thank you, outlander. I am in your debt.","fbmwILMaidenToken_1mySglove1_003235be_1"
"","","No",Neutral,50,"What do you want, outlander? I will not pay you or influence my father over this matter.","What do you want, outlander? I will not pay you or influence my father over this matter.","fbmwILMaidenToken_1mySglove2_003235bf_1"
"","","Yes",Neutral,50,"I am sorry. I thought we might have a common interest.","I am sorry. I thought we might have a common interest.","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1slavery1_00323609_1"
"","","No",Neutral,50,"I am sorry. I thought we might have a common interest.","I am sorry. I thought we might have a common interest.","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1slavery2_0032360a_1"
"","","Never heard of 'em.",Neutral,50,"I am sorry. I thought we might have a common interest.","I am sorry. I thought we might have a common interest.","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1slavery3_0032360b_1"
"","","They light the way to freedom.",Neutral,50,"I am always glad to meet another member!","I am always glad to meet another member!","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1slavery4_0032360c_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"There is a family in Ald Velothi, the Arvels, who need our help.","There is a family in Ald Velothi, the Arvels, who need our help.","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1slavery4_0032360c_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Go to Ald Velothi and speak with Galyn Arvel.","Go to Ald Velothi and speak with Galyn Arvel.","fbmwHHTwinLamps1_1slavery4_0032360c_3"
"","","I stole it for you.",Neutral,50,"How could I wear a ring like that when there is so much suffering in Tamriel? If you want my appreciation, there are better ways to earn it than fancy gifts.","How could I wear a ring like that when there is so much suffering in Tamriel? If you want my appreciation, there are better ways to earn it than fancy gifts.","fbmwTGssGreedySlaver_fbmwtgssstole_00f8a964_1"
"","","The Bal Molagmer return this to you.",Neutral,50,"The Bal Molagmer? I remember tales of them told to me when I was a child, and I have heard whisperings recently that they were returning. I accept this ring as a symbol of good faith.","The Bal Molagmer? I remember tales of them told to me when I was a child, and I have heard whisperings recently that they were returning. I accept this ring as a symbol of good faith.","fbmwTGssGreedySlaver_fbmwtgssbal_00f8a966_1"
"","","The Bal Molagmer return this to you.",Neutral,50,"The Bal Molagmer? What do you know of this, thief? I have heard of these noble bandits, but you show no sign of being one. Still, anything taken from a slaver is a good thing.","The Bal Molagmer? What do you know of this, thief? I have heard of these noble bandits, but you show no sign of being one. Still, anything taken from a slaver is a good thing.","fbmwTGssGreedySlaver_fbmwtgssbal_00f8a967_1"
