Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Ah, you have spoken with Ettiene. Good. Now, speak with my sister Fallaise. When she has given you an errand, speak with me again, and I will do the same.","Ah, you have spoken with Ettiene. Good. Now, speak with my sister Fallaise. When she has given you an errand, speak with me again, and I will do the same.","fbmwBMWolfGiver_GREETING_000b865d_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"The Rite of the Wolf Giver requires one bunch of ripened belladonna berries.  Unripened berries won't do, I'm afraid.  You can find ripened belladonna berries on belladonna plants that grow near Solstheim's burial barrows, for they thrive on death.","The Rite of the Wolf Giver requires one bunch of ripened belladonna berries.  Unripened berries won't do, I'm afraid.  You can find ripened belladonna berries on belladonna plants that grow near Solstheim's burial barrows, for they thrive on death.","fbmwBMWolfGiver_GREETING_000b9f45_1"
"","","",Neutral,50," The Spriggan creatures have also been known to possess them, on occassion.  When you have one bunch of ripened belladonna berries, return it to me.","The Spriggan creatures have also been known to possess them, on occassion.  When you have one bunch of ripened belladonna berries, return it to me.","fbmwBMWolfGiver_GREETING_000b9f45_2"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"You have brought me a bunch of ripened belladonna berries.  Well done.  The berries will be added to our cauldron, and sweeten the brew with the flavor of death.  I see you have also completed my sister Fallaise's task as well.  Excellent.","You have brought me a bunch of ripened belladonna berries.  Well done.  The berries will be added to our cauldron, and sweeten the brew with the flavor of death.  I see you have also completed my sister Fallaise's task as well.  Excellent.","fbmwBMWolfGiver_GREETING_000b9f48_1"
"","","",Neutral,50," Speak now with Ettiene to learn what you must do next.","Speak now with Ettiene to learn what you must do next.","fbmwBMWolfGiver_GREETING_000b9f48_2"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"You have already brought me the ripened belladonna berries.  I must add them to the brew, yes.  Did you know that belladonna is also referred to as deadly nightshade?","You have already brought me the ripened belladonna berries.  I must add them to the brew, yes.  Did you know that belladonna is also referred to as deadly nightshade?","fbmwBMWolfGiver_GREETING_000b9f49_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"When properly prepared, it is one of the deadliest posions in existence!  He he he he he he he he he he he he he he!","When properly prepared, it is one of the deadliest posions in existence!  He he he he he he he he he he he he he he!","fbmwBMWolfGiver_GREETING_000b9f49_2"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"You have brought me a bunch of ripened belladonna berries. Well done. The berries will be added to our cauldron, and sweeten the brew with the flavor of death.  Remember, you must also complete my sister Fallaise's task as well before talking to Ettiene.","You have brought me a bunch of ripened belladonna berries. Well done. The berries will be added to our cauldron, and sweeten the brew with the flavor of death.  Remember, you must also complete my sister Fallaise's task as well before talking to Ettiene.","fbmwBMWolfGiver_GREETING_000b9f47_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Return to me when you have obtained a single bunch of ripened belladonna berries.","Return to me when you have obtained a single bunch of ripened belladonna berries.","fbmwBMWolfGiver_GREETING_000b9f46_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Speak first with our sister Etienne.  She is the point of the dagger.  The piercing of body and mind begins with her.","Speak first with our sister Etienne.  She is the point of the dagger.  The piercing of body and mind begins with her.","fbmwBMWolfGiver_GREETING_000b865c_1"
