Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"How good to see you again. Continuing to serve the Imperial cult in your own inimitable fashion, I assume? I have no more tasks for you. Is there anything else I can do for you?","How good to see you again. Continuing to serve the Imperial cult in your own inimitable fashion, I assume? I have no more tasks for you. Is there anything else I can do for you?","fbmwICMossanon_GREETING_00f8991e_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Have you spoken to Canctunian Ponius? Have you brought the generous pledge he promised to support a mission to the Ashlanders? Or have you come to report your failure?","Have you spoken to Canctunian Ponius? Have you brought the generous pledge he promised to support a mission to the Ashlanders? Or have you come to report your failure?","fbmwICMossanon_GREETING_00f8991a_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Canctunian Ponius of the East Empire Company has promised to sponsor a mission to the Ashlanders. Such a long-term mission will be quite expensive -- 1000 drakes is a bare minimum.","Canctunian Ponius of the East Empire Company has promised to sponsor a mission to the Ashlanders. Such a long-term mission will be quite expensive -- 1000 drakes is a bare minimum.","fbmwICRich_GREETING_00f89915_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"We're concerned that we haven't received the money he pledged, and that he does not reply to our correspondence. We wish you to go to him in the East Empire Company Hall in Ebonheart and persuade him to provide us with the generous pledge as he promised.","We're concerned that we haven't received the money he pledged, and that he does not reply to our correspondence. We wish you to go to him in the East Empire Company Hall in Ebonheart and persuade him to provide us with the generous pledge as he promised.","fbmwICRich_GREETING_00f89915_2"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Have you brought me Cunius Pelelius's 500-drake donation to the Widows and Orphans Fund? Or have you come to report your failure?","Have you brought me Cunius Pelelius's 500-drake donation to the Widows and Orphans Fund? Or have you come to report your failure?","fbmwICRich_GREETING_00f89919_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Cunius Pelelius of the Caldera Mining Company is a member in good standing, and a prominent citizen, but unfortunately he has not been forthcoming with donations to help us in our good works.","Cunius Pelelius of the Caldera Mining Company is a member in good standing, and a prominent citizen, but unfortunately he has not been forthcoming with donations to help us in our good works.","fbmwICDinner_GREETING_00f89914_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Please speak with him, and see if you can persuade him to donate 500 drakes to our Widows and Orphans Fund. You'll find him in Caldera at the Governor's Hall.","Please speak with him, and see if you can persuade him to donate 500 drakes to our Widows and Orphans Fund. You'll find him in Caldera at the Governor's Hall.","fbmwICDinner_GREETING_00f89914_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"When you've obtained the donation, deliver it to me.","When you've obtained the donation, deliver it to me.","fbmwICDinner_GREETING_00f89914_3"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Have you brought me the five bottles of Cyrodilic brandy? Or have you come to report your failure?","Have you brought me the five bottles of Cyrodilic brandy? Or have you come to report your failure?","fbmwICDinner_GREETING_00f89911_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"The Balmora shrine is planning a fundraising dinner at Fort Moonmoth. We will need food and refreshments. We've had generous offers of food, but we've had trouble getting donation of strong spirits.","The Balmora shrine is planning a fundraising dinner at Fort Moonmoth. We will need food and refreshments. We've had generous offers of food, but we've had trouble getting donation of strong spirits.","fbmwICShirt_GREETING_00f89910_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"We've determined that we need 5 bottles of Cyrodilic brandy. Please make the rounds of the tradehouses and cornerclubs in Balmora and ask if the publicans will donate Cyrodiliic brandy.","We've determined that we need 5 bottles of Cyrodilic brandy. Please make the rounds of the tradehouses and cornerclubs in Balmora and ask if the publicans will donate Cyrodiliic brandy.","fbmwICShirt_GREETING_00f89910_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"When you have the brandy, please deliver it to me.","When you have the brandy, please deliver it to me.","fbmwICShirt_GREETING_00f89910_3"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Have you brought me the red shirt and black vest? Or have you come to report your failure?","Have you brought me the red shirt and black vest? Or have you come to report your failure?","fbmwICShirt_GREETING_00f8990c_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"For our coming Harvest's End pageant, we need a red shirt with a black vest. Please visit clothiers and ask if they would donate such a shirt and vest to the cult.","For our coming Harvest's End pageant, we need a red shirt with a black vest. Please visit clothiers and ask if they would donate such a shirt and vest to the cult.","fbmwICBuckmothAlms_GREETING_00f89907_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The combination of shirt and vest is what they call a 'common shirt.' When you have the red shirt with a black vest, return and deliver them to me.","The combination of shirt and vest is what they call a 'common shirt.' When you have the red shirt with a black vest, return and deliver them to me.","fbmwICBuckmothAlms_GREETING_00f89907_2"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Have you reached our goal of 100 gold in donations for the Buckmoth fund? Or have you come to report your failure?","Have you reached our goal of 100 gold in donations for the Buckmoth fund? Or have you come to report your failure?","fbmwICBuckmothAlms_GREETING_00f89905_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"The shrine at Buckmoth Legion Fort has experienced an unfortunate shortfall in alms for the poor, and funds are urgently needed to purchase food and blankets for orphans and indigents.","The shrine at Buckmoth Legion Fort has experienced an unfortunate shortfall in alms for the poor, and funds are urgently needed to purchase food and blankets for orphans and indigents.","fbmwICArgonianAlms_GREETING_00f898ff_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Please go to Ald'ruhn and see if you can raise the money for the Buckmoth Fund.","Please go to Ald'ruhn and see if you can raise the money for the Buckmoth Fund.","fbmwICArgonianAlms_GREETING_00f898ff_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The fund needs at least 100 drakes immediately. It may be difficult to raise funds, since Ald'ruhn is a Redoran town, and most residents are Dunmer, ","The fund needs at least 100 drakes immediately. It may be difficult to raise funds, since Ald'ruhn is a Redoran town, and most residents are Dunmer,","fbmwICArgonianAlms_GREETING_00f898ff_3"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Have you reached our goal of 100 gold in donations from the Argonian mission? Or have you come to report your failure?","Have you reached our goal of 100 gold in donations from the Argonian mission? Or have you come to report your failure?","fbmwICArgonianAlms_GREETING_00f89900_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Go ask the Argonian Mission in Ebonheart for alms for the poor. Their province is not so rich as Skyrim, but they are a generous and civic-minded people.","Go ask the Argonian Mission in Ebonheart for alms for the poor. Their province is not so rich as Skyrim, but they are a generous and civic-minded people.","fbmwICNordAlms_GREETING_00f898fe_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Our fund raising goal for the Argonian mission is 100 gold. When you have reached our goal, return and deliver the gold to me.","Our fund raising goal for the Argonian mission is 100 gold. When you have reached our goal, return and deliver the gold to me.","fbmwICNordAlms_GREETING_00f898fe_2"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Have you reached our goal of 100 gold in donations from the Skyrim mission? Or have you come to report your failure?","Have you reached our goal of 100 gold in donations from the Skyrim mission? Or have you come to report your failure?","fbmwICNordAlms_GREETING_00f898f5_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Hello. I am Iulus Truptor. I manage the volunteer almoners for our cult. If you are ready to accept a fund raising project as an almoner, let me know.","Hello. I am Iulus Truptor. I manage the volunteer almoners for our cult. If you are ready to accept a fund raising project as an almoner, let me know.","fbmwICAdvancement_GREETING_00f898f0_1"
"","","Donate Cyrodilic Brandy",Neutral,50,"I'm afraid only Cyrodilic brandy will do for the Fort Moonmoth fund-raising dinner. The sort of person who has money to give to charity turns the nose up at the local comberry brandy they call greef.","I'm afraid only Cyrodilic brandy will do for the Fort Moonmoth fund-raising dinner. The sort of person who has money to give to charity turns the nose up at the local comberry brandy they call greef.","fbmwICDinner_1donateSCyrodilicSbrandy_00f8aa2d_1"
"","","East Empire Company",Neutral,50,"The East Empire Company Hall is just northwest of Ebonheart's dragon statue. You must have seen the dragon statue.","The East Empire Company Hall is just northwest of Ebonheart's dragon statue. You must have seen the dragon statue.","MorroDefaultQuest_1EastSEmpireSCompany_003208ad_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"It's in the plaza all the way to the east, just before you step down to the docks.","It's in the plaza all the way to the east, just before you step down to the docks.","MorroDefaultQuest_1EastSEmpireSCompany_003208ad_2"
"","","Imperial cult ranks",Neutral,50,"The ten ranks of status in the Imperial cult are, from lowest rank to highest rank: Rank One, Layman; Rank Two, Novice; Rank Three, Initiate;","The ten ranks of status in the Imperial cult are, from lowest rank to highest rank: Rank One, Layman; Rank Two, Novice; Rank Three, Initiate;","MorroDefaultQuest_1ImperialScultSranks_0032091b_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Rank Four, Acolyte; Rank Five, Adept; Rank Six, Disciple; Rank Seven, Oracle; Rank Eight, Invoker; Rank Nine, Theurgist; and Rank Ten, Primate.","Rank Four, Acolyte; Rank Five, Adept; Rank Six, Disciple; Rank Seven, Oracle; Rank Eight, Invoker; Rank Nine, Theurgist; and Rank Ten, Primate.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ImperialScultSranks_0032091b_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You are currently at that rank outlander.","You are currently at that rank outlander.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ImperialScultSranks_0032091b_3"
"","","Alms for the poor",Neutral,50,"The Imperial cult asks for donations from members and friends of the faith to support our good works.","The Imperial cult asks for donations from members and friends of the faith to support our good works.","MorroDefaultQuest_1almsSforStheSpoor_00320c11_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"As a custom, we ask for alms for the poor, because most of the gifts go to feed, cloth, cure, and heal the less fortunate, but in fact the donations go to support various worthy causes and special projects.","As a custom, we ask for alms for the poor, because most of the gifts go to feed, cloth, cure, and heal the less fortunate, but in fact the donations go to support various worthy causes and special projects.","MorroDefaultQuest_1almsSforStheSpoor_00320c11_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Collecting alms is just one of the many tasks our more faithful members perform in the service of the Nine.","Collecting alms is just one of the many tasks our more faithful members perform in the service of the Nine.","MorroDefaultQuest_1almsSforStheSpoor_00320c11_3"
"","","Donate 500 Drakes",Neutral,50,"That is a large sum, but the Widows and Orphans Fund needs it badly.","That is a large sum, but the Widows and Orphans Fund needs it badly.","fbmwICRich_1donateS500Sdrakes_00f8a399_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And Cunius Pelelius is a part of the trust who received the exclusive Imperial charter to exploit the rich ebony deposits of Caldera Mine, so he must be a very wealthy man, and more than able to spare 500 drakes for such a worth cause.","And Cunius Pelelius is a part of the trust who received the exclusive Imperial charter to exploit the rich ebony deposits of Caldera Mine, so he must be a very wealthy man, and more than able to spare 500 drakes for such a worth cause.","fbmwICRich_1donateS500Sdrakes_00f8a399_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Unfortunately, every time we ask Cunius Pelelius for the donation, he says he is very busy at the moment, but he will be happy to discuss the donation at a later date.","Unfortunately, every time we ask Cunius Pelelius for the donation, he says he is very busy at the moment, but he will be happy to discuss the donation at a later date.","fbmwICRich_1donateS500Sdrakes_00f8a399_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I suppose he plans to keep deferring the obligation indefinitely until we abandon hope. We must have that money for the Widows and Orphans Fund.","I suppose he plans to keep deferring the obligation indefinitely until we abandon hope. We must have that money for the Widows and Orphans Fund.","fbmwICRich_1donateS500Sdrakes_00f8a399_4"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You'll just have to find some way to impress upon him the urgency of our cause. We have the greatest faith in you. We know you'll succeed.","You'll just have to find some way to impress upon him the urgency of our cause. We have the greatest faith in you. We know you'll succeed.","fbmwICRich_1donateS500Sdrakes_00f8a399_5"
"","","1000-drake pledge",Neutral,50,"When I spoke with him some time ago, Canctunian Ponius promised us a donation of 1000 drakes for a mission to the Ashlanders.","When I spoke with him some time ago, Canctunian Ponius promised us a donation of 1000 drakes for a mission to the Ashlanders.","fbmwICMossanon_11000TdrakeSpledge_00aa0e79_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Canctunian Ponius is an important and prominent member of our community, and his word is widely respected.","Canctunian Ponius is an important and prominent member of our community, and his word is widely respected.","fbmwICMossanon_11000TdrakeSpledge_00aa0e79_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"That is why it is strange that he has not been forthcoming with his pledge.","That is why it is strange that he has not been forthcoming with his pledge.","fbmwICMossanon_11000TdrakeSpledge_00aa0e79_3"
"","","Argonian Mission",Neutral,50,"The Argonian Mission is Black Marsh's diplomatic embassy to Vvardenfell District.","The Argonian Mission is Black Marsh's diplomatic embassy to Vvardenfell District.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ArgonianSMission_00320e20_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Leave the Imperial Chapels, pass through the Grand Council Chambers, cross the bridge, then down the stairs.","Leave the Imperial Chapels, pass through the Grand Council Chambers, cross the bridge, then down the stairs.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ArgonianSMission_00320e20_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"As you face out the gate, the Argonian Mission is to the south, on the southern side of the well.","As you face out the gate, the Argonian Mission is to the south, on the southern side of the well.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ArgonianSMission_00320e20_3"
"","","Cunius Pelelius",Neutral,50,"He's dead? How unfortunate... I mean... how sad for his family and friends. But it would also be unfortunate if we were to lose his donation....","He's dead? How unfortunate... I mean... how sad for his family and friends. But it would also be unfortunate if we were to lose his donation....","fbmwICRich_1CuniusSPelelius_00f8a458_1"
"","","Cunius Pelelius",Neutral,50,"Cunius Pelelius owns part of the Caldera Mine. He's a man of wealth and influence. You'll find him in Caldera at the Governor's Hall.","Cunius Pelelius owns part of the Caldera Mine. He's a man of wealth and influence. You'll find him in Caldera at the Governor's Hall.","fbmwICRich_1CuniusSPelelius_00f8a459_1"
"","","Generous Pledge",Neutral,50,"When I spoke with him some time ago, Canctunian Ponius promised us a donation of 1000 drakes for a mission to the Ashlanders. Canctunian Ponius is an important and prominent member of our community, and his word is widely respected.","When I spoke with him some time ago, Canctunian Ponius promised us a donation of 1000 drakes for a mission to the Ashlanders. Canctunian Ponius is an important and prominent member of our community, and his word is widely respected.","fbmwICMossanon_1generousSpledge_00f8aac7_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"That is why it is strange that he has not been forthcoming with his generous pledge.","That is why it is strange that he has not been forthcoming with his generous pledge.","fbmwICMossanon_1generousSpledge_00f8aac7_2"
"","","Darl Elf Savant",Neutral,50,"The only Dark Elf savant that comes to mind is Llaalam Dredil. Fortunately, he's close by, in the Ebonheart Grand Council Chambers.","The only Dark Elf savant that comes to mind is Llaalam Dredil. Fortunately, he's close by, in the Ebonheart Grand Council Chambers.","MorroDefaultQuest_1DarlSElfSsavant_00321082_1"
"","","Shirt and Vest",Neutral,50,"Thank you. Just what we were looking for.","Thank you. Just what we were looking for.","fbmwICShirt_1shirtSandSvest_00f8a509_1"
"","","Shirt and Vest",Neutral,50,"I'm told that a shirt and vest together is what they call here a 'common shirt.' There are many styles of common shirt, but we must have a red shirt with a black vest to symbolize the drake's fire that warms us in long, cold winter nights.","I'm told that a shirt and vest together is what they call here a 'common shirt.' There are many styles of common shirt, but we must have a red shirt with a black vest to symbolize the drake's fire that warms us in long, cold winter nights.","fbmwICShirt_1shirtSandSvest_0032146e_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Since the red shirt and black vest are a Western style, Dunmer clothiers may not have them.","Since the red shirt and black vest are a Western style, Dunmer clothiers may not have them.","fbmwICShirt_1shirtSandSvest_0032146e_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You may have better luck in Vivec's Foreign Quarter, or Balmora, Caldera, or Pelagiad.","You may have better luck in Vivec's Foreign Quarter, or Balmora, Caldera, or Pelagiad.","fbmwICShirt_1shirtSandSvest_0032146e_3"
"","","Skyrim Mission",Neutral,50,"The Skyrim Mission is Skyrim's diplomatic embassy to Vvardenfell District.","The Skyrim Mission is Skyrim's diplomatic embassy to Vvardenfell District.","MorroDefaultQuest_1SkyrimSMission_00321477_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Leave the Imperial Chapels, pass through the Grand Council Chambers, cross the bridge, then down the stairs, out through the gate.","Leave the Imperial Chapels, pass through the Grand Council Chambers, cross the bridge, then down the stairs, out through the gate.","MorroDefaultQuest_1SkyrimSMission_00321477_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"As you look south from the gate, the Skyrim Mission is to the right, west of the well.","As you look south from the gate, the Skyrim Mission is to the right, west of the well.","MorroDefaultQuest_1SkyrimSMission_00321477_3"
"","","Advancement",Neutral,50,"You have already risen to the highest rank available to a lay servant of the Imperial cult.","You have already risen to the highest rank available to a lay servant of the Imperial cult.","fbmwICAdvancement_1Advancement_00322068_1"
"","","Advancement",Neutral,50,"You cannot receive advancement unless you join the Imperial Cult.","You cannot receive advancement unless you join the Imperial Cult.","fbmwICAdvancement_1Advancement_00322069_1"
"","","Advancement",Neutral,50,"You have been expelled from the Imperial cult. I am disappointed, and ashamed for you.","You have been expelled from the Imperial cult. I am disappointed, and ashamed for you.","fbmwICAdvancement_1Advancement_0032206a_1"
"","","Advancement",Neutral,50,"If you want to advance in the service of the Nine, you must dedicate more of your time and resources to serving the cult, and you must strive for personal improvement in your attributes and skills.","If you want to advance in the service of the Nine, you must dedicate more of your time and resources to serving the cult, and you must strive for personal improvement in your attributes and skills.","fbmwICAdvancement_1Advancement_0032206b_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Only the most distinguished are worthy of advancement to the higher ranks in the Imperial cult.","Only the most distinguished are worthy of advancement to the higher ranks in the Imperial cult.","fbmwICAdvancement_1Advancement_0032206b_2"
"","","Advancement",Neutral,50,"You have the attributes and skills we expect in our higher ranks, but you have not yet dedicated enough time and service to the Nine to warrant advancement.","You have the attributes and skills we expect in our higher ranks, but you have not yet dedicated enough time and service to the Nine to warrant advancement.","fbmwICAdvancement_1Advancement_0032206c_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I can tell you more about the Imperial cult ranks and their requirements, if you like.","I can tell you more about the Imperial cult ranks and their requirements, if you like.","fbmwICAdvancement_1Advancement_0032206c_2"
"","","Advancement",Neutral,50,"You have served the Nine well, but I'm afraid you do not yet measure up to our high standards for personal attributes and skills.","You have served the Nine well, but I'm afraid you do not yet measure up to our high standards for personal attributes and skills.","fbmwICAdvancement_1Advancement_0032206d_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I can tell you more about the Imperial cult ranks and their requirements, if you like.","I can tell you more about the Imperial cult ranks and their requirements, if you like.","fbmwICAdvancement_1Advancement_0032206d_2"
"","","Advancement",Neutral,50,"Congratulations, outlander. You have been promoted.","Congratulations, outlander. You have been promoted.","fbmwICAdvancement_1Advancement_0032206e_1"
"","","Ald'ruhn",Neutral,50,"Ald'ruhn is the district seat of House Redoran, and a large settlement. Travel by guild guide is the best method.","Ald'ruhn is the district seat of House Redoran, and a large settlement. Travel by guild guide is the best method.","MorroDefaultQuest_1AldAruhn_0032281e_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Head north from Ebonheart by road, take the bridge into Vivec's Hlaalu Compound, pass through Redoran Compound, find the Guild of Mages on the upper level of the Foreign Quarter.","Head north from Ebonheart by road, take the bridge into Vivec's Hlaalu Compound, pass through Redoran Compound, find the Guild of Mages on the upper level of the Foreign Quarter.","MorroDefaultQuest_1AldAruhn_0032281e_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Pay a guild guide at the Guild of Mages for transport to Ald'ruhn.","Pay a guild guide at the Guild of Mages for transport to Ald'ruhn.","MorroDefaultQuest_1AldAruhn_0032281e_3"
"","","Almoners",Neutral,50,"Almoners gather alms from members and friends of the faith. We depend on donations to fund most of our good works.","Almoners gather alms from members and friends of the faith. We depend on donations to fund most of our good works.","MorroDefaultQuest_1almoners_003228c5_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Almoners who are successful at bringing in generous donations may rise in the ranks of Imperial cult service.","Almoners who are successful at bringing in generous donations may rise in the ranks of Imperial cult service.","MorroDefaultQuest_1almoners_003228c5_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If you are interested, speak to Iulus Truptor at the Imperial Chapels in Ebonheart.","If you are interested, speak to Iulus Truptor at the Imperial Chapels in Ebonheart.","MorroDefaultQuest_1almoners_003228c5_3"
"","","Balmora",Neutral,50,"Balmora is the district seat of House Hlaalu, and the largest settlement on Vvardenfell after Vivec City. Travel by guild guide is the best method.","Balmora is the district seat of House Hlaalu, and the largest settlement on Vvardenfell after Vivec City. Travel by guild guide is the best method.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Balmora_00322aa0_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Head north from Ebonheart by road, take the bridge into Vivec's Hlaalu Compound, pass through Redoran Compound, find the Guild of Mages on the upper level of the Foreign Quarter.","Head north from Ebonheart by road, take the bridge into Vivec's Hlaalu Compound, pass through Redoran Compound, find the Guild of Mages on the upper level of the Foreign Quarter.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Balmora_00322aa0_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Pay a guild guide at the Guild of Mages for transport to Balmora.","Pay a guild guide at the Guild of Mages for transport to Balmora.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Balmora_00322aa0_3"
"","","Temple",Neutral,50,"The Tribunal Temple is the native religion of civilized Morrowind.","The Tribunal Temple is the native religion of civilized Morrowind.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Temple_00322c84_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"They worship three God-Kings, Almalexia, Sotha Sil, and Vivec, who are known together as the Tribunal. We usually just call it 'The Temple.'","They worship three God-Kings, Almalexia, Sotha Sil, and Vivec, who are known together as the Tribunal. We usually just call it 'The Temple.'","MorroDefaultQuest_1Temple_00322c84_2"
"","","Dunmer",Neutral,50,"The Buckmoth fund, based in Fort Buckmoth, serves the citizens of nearby Ald'ruhn.","The Buckmoth fund, based in Fort Buckmoth, serves the citizens of nearby Ald'ruhn.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Dunmer_00f8a842_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But most Ald'ruhn residents are Dunmer belonging to House Redoran, and therefore members of the Tribunal Temple, so it may be hard to collect alms for the poor in Ald'ruhn on behalf of the Imperial cult.","But most Ald'ruhn residents are Dunmer belonging to House Redoran, and therefore members of the Tribunal Temple, so it may be hard to collect alms for the poor in Ald'ruhn on behalf of the Imperial cult.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Dunmer_00f8a842_2"
"","","I have something else to ask about.",Neutral,50,"Then what can I do for you?","Then what can I do for you?","fbmwICAdvancement_fbmwiciulusworkno_00f8a9c1_1"
"","","I'm ready for an almoner project.",Neutral,50,"Thank Zenithar! We have so many projects, and so little gold. Go ask the Skyrim Mission in Ebonheart for alms for the poor. They should give generously to support the Imperial cult. Our fund raising goal for the Skyrim mission is 100 gold.","Thank Zenithar! We have so many projects, and so little gold. Go ask the Skyrim Mission in Ebonheart for alms for the poor. They should give generously to support the Imperial cult. Our fund raising goal for the Skyrim mission is 100 gold.","fbmwICAdvancement_fbmwiciulusworkyes_00f8a9c3_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"When you have reached our goal, return and deliver the gold to me.","When you have reached our goal, return and deliver the gold to me.","fbmwICAdvancement_fbmwiciulusworkyes_00f8a9c3_2"
"","","I have DOUBLED our goal!",Neutral,50,"Excellent! Once again, you've exceeded our expectations. Take these gifts as tokens of our gratitude for your faithful and diligent service to the Imperial cult.","Excellent! Once again, you've exceeded our expectations. Take these gifts as tokens of our gratitude for your faithful and diligent service to the Imperial cult.","fbmwICBuckmothAlms_fbmwicnorddouble_00f8a9c5_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And when you're ready for your next almoner mission, speak to me again.","And when you're ready for your next almoner mission, speak to me again.","fbmwICBuckmothAlms_fbmwicnorddouble_00f8a9c5_2"
"","","I have DOUBLED our goal!",Neutral,50,"Excellent! Once again, you've exceeded our expectations. You are blessed with Zenithar's gift of fine words and generous sentiments. Take this, and wear it with pride.","Excellent! Once again, you've exceeded our expectations. You are blessed with Zenithar's gift of fine words and generous sentiments. Take this, and wear it with pride.","fbmwICArgonianAlms_fbmwicnorddouble_00f8a9c6_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And when you're ready for your next almoner mission, speak to me again.","And when you're ready for your next almoner mission, speak to me again.","fbmwICArgonianAlms_fbmwicnorddouble_00f8a9c6_2"
"","","I have DOUBLED our goal!",Neutral,50,"Excellent! You've far exceeded our expectations. Surely you have a touch of Zenithar in your soul. Please accept this small token of our gratitude and encouragement.","Excellent! You've far exceeded our expectations. Surely you have a touch of Zenithar in your soul. Please accept this small token of our gratitude and encouragement.","fbmwICNordAlms_fbmwicnorddouble_00f8a9c7_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And when you're ready for your next almoner mission, speak to me again.","And when you're ready for your next almoner mission, speak to me again.","fbmwICNordAlms_fbmwicnorddouble_00f8a9c7_2"
"","","Yes, I've reached our goal.",Neutral,50,"Very good. Congratulations. And perhaps you'll find this useful in your work. When you're ready for your next almoner mission, speak to me again.","Very good. Congratulations. And perhaps you'll find this useful in your work. When you're ready for your next almoner mission, speak to me again.","fbmwICBuckmothAlms_fbmwicnordreach_00f8a9c9_1"
"","","Yes, I've reached our goal.",Neutral,50,"Very good. Congratulations. And perhaps you'll find this useful in your work. When you're ready for your next almoner mission, speak to me again.","Very good. Congratulations. And perhaps you'll find this useful in your work. When you're ready for your next almoner mission, speak to me again.","fbmwICArgonianAlms_fbmwicnordreach_00f8a9ca_1"
"","","Yes, I've reached our goal.",Neutral,50,"Very good. This gold will help us serve our community of faith. Congratulations. And accept this small blessing as a token of our thanks. Wh","Very good. This gold will help us serve our community of faith. Congratulations. And accept this small blessing as a token of our thanks. Wh","fbmwICNordAlms_fbmwicnordreach_00f8a9cb_1"
"","","No, but I'm working on it.",Neutral,50,"Very well. Carry on.","Very well. Carry on.","fbmwICArgonianAlms_fbmwicworking_00f8a9cd_1"
"","","No, but I'm working on it.",Neutral,50,"Very well. Carry on.","Very well. Carry on.","fbmwICNordAlms_fbmwicworking_00f8a9ce_1"
"","","I'm sorry, but I can't do it.",Neutral,50,"You're not trying hard enough. We are disappointed. We all need to do our part for Imperial cult. But it's your decision.","You're not trying hard enough. We are disappointed. We all need to do our part for Imperial cult. But it's your decision.","fbmwICArgonianAlms_fbmwicnordgiveup_00f8a9d1_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Perhaps you should take some time off and decide whether your talents and temperaments are suited for fund raising. When you approach us again for another almoner's mission, be sure you want to give us your full commitment.","Perhaps you should take some time off and decide whether your talents and temperaments are suited for fund raising. When you approach us again for another almoner's mission, be sure you want to give us your full commitment.","fbmwICArgonianAlms_fbmwicnordgiveup_00f8a9d1_2"
"","","I'm sorry, but I can't do it.",Neutral,50,"You're not trying hard enough. We are disappointed. We all need to do our part for Imperial cult. But it's your decision. Perhaps you should take some time off and decide whether your talents and temperaments are suited for fund raising.","You're not trying hard enough. We are disappointed. We all need to do our part for Imperial cult. But it's your decision. Perhaps you should take some time off and decide whether your talents and temperaments are suited for fund raising.","fbmwICNordAlms_fbmwicnordgiveup_00f8a9d2_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"When you approach us again for an almoner's mission, be sure you want to give us your full commitment.","When you approach us again for an almoner's mission, be sure you want to give us your full commitment.","fbmwICNordAlms_fbmwicnordgiveup_00f8a9d2_2"
"","","No, but I'm working on it.",Neutral,50,"Very well. Carry on.","Very well. Carry on.","fbmwICMossanon_fbmwicnordworking_00f8a9d4_1"
"","","No, but I'm working on it.",Neutral,50,"Very well. Carry on.","Very well. Carry on.","fbmwICRich_fbmwicnordworking_00f8a9d5_1"
"","","No, but I'm working on it.",Neutral,50,"Fine then. Carry on.","Fine then. Carry on.","fbmwICDinner_fbmwicnordworking_00f8a9d6_1"
"","","No, but I'm working on it.",Neutral,50,"Very well. Carry on.","Very well. Carry on.","fbmwICShirt_fbmwicnordworking_00f8a9d7_1"
"","","No, but I'm working on it.",Neutral,50,"Very well. Carry on.","Very well. Carry on.","fbmwICBuckmothAlms_fbmwicnordworking_00f8a9d8_1"
"","","Yes, I have the shirt and vest here.",Neutral,50,"Very good. Congratulations. When you're ready for your next almoner mission, speak to me again. But before you do, you might take a look at this book.","Very good. Congratulations. When you're ready for your next almoner mission, speak to me again. But before you do, you might take a look at this book.","fbmwICShirt_fbmwicfindshirt_00f8a9da_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I've found it helpful. Go ahead. Keep it. I've learned all I can from it.","I've found it helpful. Go ahead. Keep it. I've learned all I can from it.","fbmwICShirt_fbmwicfindshirt_00f8a9da_2"
"","","Yes, I have the Cyrodiliic brandy.",Neutral,50,"Very good. Congratulations. This was no easy task, I'm sure. I'd like to acknowledge your faithful service with this token of Zenithar's special blessing.","Very good. Congratulations. This was no easy task, I'm sure. I'd like to acknowledge your faithful service with this token of Zenithar's special blessing.","fbmwICDinner_fbmwicdinnerhave_00f8a9dc_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Accept them with my thanks, and with the thanks of the Imperial cult. When you're ready for your next almoner mission, speak to me again.","Accept them with my thanks, and with the thanks of the Imperial cult. When you're ready for your next almoner mission, speak to me again.","fbmwICDinner_fbmwicdinnerhave_00f8a9dc_2"
"","","Yes, I have the 500-drake donation.",Neutral,50,"You have succeeded where other have failed. Congratulations. This money will greatly benefit the widows and orphans of Vvardenfell.","You have succeeded where other have failed. Congratulations. This money will greatly benefit the widows and orphans of Vvardenfell.","fbmwICRich_fbmwicrichyes_00f8a9de_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I'm beginning to run out of gifts suitable to reward your diligence. Perhaps you may find this assortment of scrolls useful. We received them from an anonymous donor, but there may be some good in them. Now.","I'm beginning to run out of gifts suitable to reward your diligence. Perhaps you may find this assortment of scrolls useful. We received them from an anonymous donor, but there may be some good in them. Now.","fbmwICRich_fbmwicrichyes_00f8a9de_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"When you're ready for your next almoner mission, speak to me again.","When you're ready for your next almoner mission, speak to me again.","fbmwICRich_fbmwicrichyes_00f8a9de_3"
"","","Yes, I have the generous pledge.",Neutral,50,"Thank you. You have exceeded our greatest expectations. I'm afraid we have no more tasks to challenge your remarkable abilities. I suspect you already outstip your teachers.","Thank you. You have exceeded our greatest expectations. I'm afraid we have no more tasks to challenge your remarkable abilities. I suspect you already outstip your teachers.","fbmwICMossanon_fbmwicmossanonyes_00f8a9e0_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Perhaps you will consider becoming one of our lay healers or shrine sergeants, if you have not already sampled these duties. I have also passed your name to our Oracle here, Lalatia Varian.","Perhaps you will consider becoming one of our lay healers or shrine sergeants, if you have not already sampled these duties. I have also passed your name to our Oracle here, Lalatia Varian.","fbmwICMossanon_fbmwicmossanonyes_00f8a9e0_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"She may have tasks suited to your talents. But before you go, I have one last gift for you to remember us by. Goodbye, and good luck.","She may have tasks suited to your talents. But before you go, I have one last gift for you to remember us by. Goodbye, and good luck.","fbmwICMossanon_fbmwicmossanonyes_00f8a9e0_3"
