Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"You have dealt with my captors. I will find my own way back to the Erabinimsun and continue to teach them of the Empire and its ways.","You have dealt with my captors. I will find my own way back to the Erabinimsun and continue to teach them of the Empire and its ways.","fbmwILRescueHermit_GREETING_00f88705_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"You have dealt with my captors. I will find my own way back to the Erabinimsun and continue to teach them of the Empire and its ways.","You have dealt with my captors. I will find my own way back to the Erabinimsun and continue to teach them of the Empire and its ways.","fbmwILRescueHermit_GREETING_00f88706_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I dare not leave until these outcast Erabinimsun have been dealt with.","I dare not leave until these outcast Erabinimsun have been dealt with.","fbmwILRescueHermit_GREETING_00f88707_1"
