Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"Dremora","","GREETING",Disgust,50,"Have you not given me a silver longsword? Just read the shrine and leave. I tire of your mortal presence.","Have you not given me a silver longsword? Just read the shrine and leave. I tire of your mortal presence.","fbmwTTSevenGraces_GREETING_000033c8_1"
"Dremora","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Are you here on the pilgrimage? I take it that silver longsword is for me.","Are you here on the pilgrimage? I take it that silver longsword is for me.","fbmwTTSevenGraces_GREETING_000033cb_1"
"Dremora","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Are you here on the pilgrimage? Read the shrine.","Are you here on the pilgrimage? Read the shrine.","fbmwTTSevenGraces_GREETING_000033cc_1"
"Dremora","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Are you here on the pilgrimage? Do you have a silver longsword for me?","Are you here on the pilgrimage? Do you have a silver longsword for me?","fbmwTTSevenGraces_GREETING_000033cd_1"
"Dremora","","Silver Longsword",Neutral,50,"I remember you. You have already given me a silver longsword.","I remember you. You have already given me a silver longsword.","fbmwTTSevenGraces_1silverSlongsword_00f8aaa8_1"
"Dremora","","Silver Longsword",Neutral,50,"As you see. I am unarmed. But you are brave and gallant. <sigh> Will you give me your longsword so that I may stand a chance against your might?","As you see. I am unarmed. But you are brave and gallant. <sigh> Will you give me your longsword so that I may stand a chance against your might?","fbmwTTSevenGraces_1silverSlongsword_00f8aaa9_1"
"Dremora","","Silver Longsword",Neutral,50,"I can only accept plain silver longswords. I didn't make the rules.","I can only accept plain silver longswords. I didn't make the rules.","fbmwTTSevenGraces_1silverSlongsword_00f8aaaa_1"
"Dremora","","Yes, take it.",Neutral,50,"Yes, I accept this sword. Thank you. You have the grace of courtesy. You should read the inscription on the shrine to complete your pilgrimage.","Yes, I accept this sword. Thank you. You have the grace of courtesy. You should read the inscription on the shrine to complete your pilgrimage.","fbmwTTSevenGraces_fbmwttpuzzlegive_00f8a9bd_1"
"Dremora","","Yes, take it.",Neutral,50,"Yes, I accept this sword. Thank you. You have the grace of courtesy. You should read the inscription on the shrine to complete your pilgrimage.","Yes, I accept this sword. Thank you. You have the grace of courtesy. You should read the inscription on the shrine to complete your pilgrimage.","fbmwTTSevenGraces_fbmwttpuzzlegive_00f8e984_1"
"Dremora","","Nevermind.",Neutral,50,"Perhaps you should read the shrine again.","Perhaps you should read the shrine again.","fbmwTTSevenGraces_fbmwttpuzzlekeep_00f8a9bf_1"
