Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Ho there, good friend!","Ho there, good friend!","fbmwFGNchurdamz_GREETING_0001010f_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"What's that? Do you require aid?","What's that? Do you require aid?","fbmwFGNchurdamz_GREETING_000100f8_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Ho there! Your one of Hrundi's band, aren't you? I can spot you a mile off.","Ho there! Your one of Hrundi's band, aren't you? I can spot you a mile off.","fbmwFGNchurdamz_GREETING_000100f7_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I've been waiting for some time now for assistance, but I suppose you will have to do.","I've been waiting for some time now for assistance, but I suppose you will have to do.","fbmwFGNchurdamz_GREETING_000100f7_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I'm on a quest to root out a "great beast" dwelling within these ruins. You and I will explore together.","I'm on a quest to root out a "great beast" dwelling within these ruins. You and I will explore together.","fbmwFGNchurdamz_GREETING_000100f7_3"
"","","Explore Together",Neutral,50,"Ah -- I knew you would return. The call of battle is strong, is it not?","Ah -- I knew you would return. The call of battle is strong, is it not?","fbmwFGNchurdamz_1exploreStogether_00f8aa90_1"
"","","Explore Together",Neutral,50,"I have scoured the world over hunting a specific Daedroth with whom I have had issues in the past. When last we battled, I struck her a blow so grievous that she fled via spell to her dark sanctuary.","I have scoured the world over hunting a specific Daedroth with whom I have had issues in the past. When last we battled, I struck her a blow so grievous that she fled via spell to her dark sanctuary.","fbmwFGNchurdamz_1exploreStogether_00f8aa91_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"This is that place. The beast's name is Hrelvesuu. She is weak, and likely recuperating from the damage I caused her. This place is well defended and I need someone to watch my back.","This is that place. The beast's name is Hrelvesuu. She is weak, and likely recuperating from the damage I caused her. This place is well defended and I need someone to watch my back.","fbmwFGNchurdamz_1exploreStogether_00f8aa91_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You can have whatever "treasure" you can find in there. I seek only vengeance. What say you?","You can have whatever "treasure" you can find in there. I seek only vengeance. What say you?","fbmwFGNchurdamz_1exploreStogether_00f8aa91_3"
"","","Require Aid",Neutral,50,"Ah. I see. Alright, hold still.","Ah. I see. Alright, hold still.","fbmwFGNchurdamz_1requireSaid_00f8bd37_1"
"","","Require Aid",Neutral,50,"Understand that this does deplete my strength. However, I trust your judgement.","Understand that this does deplete my strength. However, I trust your judgement.","fbmwFGNchurdamz_1requireSaid_00001be4_1"
"","","I'm ready.",Neutral,50,"All right then. Let's go. Remember, let me know if you require aid -- you watch my back and I'll watch yours. Take point and root out the threats. The treasure is yours--and Hrelvesuu is mine.","All right then. Let's go. Remember, let me know if you require aid -- you watch my back and I'll watch yours. Take point and root out the threats. The treasure is yours--and Hrelvesuu is mine.","fbmwFGNchurdamz_fbmwfgnchyes_00f8a98b_1"
"","","You are insane.",Neutral,50,"Fine. When you work up the gumption, lemme know. Otherwise, I'm sure someone else will come along and share the riches with me soon.","Fine. When you work up the gumption, lemme know. Otherwise, I'm sure someone else will come along and share the riches with me soon.","fbmwFGNchurdamz_fbmwfgnchno_00f8a98d_1"
