Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I'm just glad it's over.","I'm just glad it's over.","fbmwMGApprentice_GREETING_00f852b2_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Is the Scamp really gone? Thank you, whoever you are. This is all my fault.","Is the Scamp really gone? Thank you, whoever you are. This is all my fault.","fbmwMGApprentice_GREETING_00f852ae_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Please, whoever you are, kill the Scamp before it causes any more trouble.","Please, whoever you are, kill the Scamp before it causes any more trouble.","fbmwMGApprentice_GREETING_00f852af_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Oh, thank Julianos you're here! It's all my fault!","Oh, thank Julianos you're here! It's all my fault!","fbmwMGApprentice_GREETING_00f852b0_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I'm so sorry. It was all my fault.","I'm so sorry. It was all my fault.","fbmwMGApprentice_GREETING_00f852b1_1"
"","","GREETING",Fear,50,"Is the Scamp really gone? Thank you, whoever you are. This is all my fault.","Is the Scamp really gone? Thank you, whoever you are. This is all my fault.","fbmwMSGreetings_GREETING_00006791_1"
"","","GREETING",Fear,100,"Please, whoever you are, kill the Scamp before it causes any more trouble.","Please, whoever you are, kill the Scamp before it causes any more trouble.","fbmwMSGreetings_GREETING_00006794_1"
"","","Huleen's hut",Neutral,50,"It's outside the town walls to the southeast, near the shrine.","It's outside the town walls to the southeast, near the shrine.","fbmwMGApprentice_1HuleenAsShut_00321b71_1"
"","","All my fault",Neutral,50,"I wanted to be a real Sorcerer, not just Huleen's apprentice for the rest of my life. I wanted to prove I could summon a scamp...","I wanted to be a real Sorcerer, not just Huleen's apprentice for the rest of my life. I wanted to prove I could summon a scamp...","fbmwMGApprentice_1allSmySfault_00321b76_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Then Huleen would have to take me seriously. I'm just glad it's all over now. Thanks for killing the scamp,&sUActnQuick1;.","Then Huleen would have to take me seriously. I'm just glad it's all over now. Thanks for killing the scamp,&sUActnQuick1;.","fbmwMGApprentice_1allSmySfault_00321b76_2"
"","","All my fault",Neutral,50,"Please, kill the scamp! I didn't know I couldn't control it!","Please, kill the scamp! I didn't know I couldn't control it!","fbmwMGApprentice_1allSmySfault_00321b73_1"
"","","Scamp",Neutral,50,"At first he did everything I told him, but he tricked me! He wasn't really under my control.","At first he did everything I told him, but he tricked me! He wasn't really under my control.","fbmwMGApprentice_1Scamp_00322db9_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Then he started tearing the place up, and he took all my clothes, and I locked myself in this closet, and it's been just horrible.","Then he started tearing the place up, and he took all my clothes, and I locked myself in this closet, and it's been just horrible.","fbmwMGApprentice_1Scamp_00322db9_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I don't want to be a Sorcerer anymore. I won't ever summon another Daedra as long as I live.","I don't want to be a Sorcerer anymore. I won't ever summon another Daedra as long as I live.","fbmwMGApprentice_1Scamp_00322db9_3"
"","","Scamp",Neutral,50,"Kill it! Kill the scamp before it causes any more trouble!","Kill it! Kill the scamp before it causes any more trouble!","fbmwMGApprentice_1Scamp_00322dba_1"
