Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Join us",Neutral,50,"Yes, I am a member now. Just leave me to my research.","Yes, I am a member now. Just leave me to my research.","fbmwMGJoinUS_1joinSus_00f8a766_1"
"","","Join us",Neutral,50,"What is it now? I already said I would join the Mages Guild next time I'm in Balmora.","What is it now? I already said I would join the Mages Guild next time I'm in Balmora.","fbmwMGJoinUS_1joinSus_00f8a767_1"
"","","Join us",Neutral,50,"If I agree to join, will you leave me to my research? Fine, then. I will join the Mages Guild next time I'm in Balmora.","If I agree to join, will you leave me to my research? Fine, then. I will join the Mages Guild next time I'm in Balmora.","fbmwMGJoinUS_1joinSus_00f8a768_1"
"","","Join us",Neutral,50,"Do I look like a fool? Collect your dues from someone else. Or at least give me a reason to listen to your drivel.","Do I look like a fool? Collect your dues from someone else. Or at least give me a reason to listen to your drivel.","fbmwMGJoinUS_1joinSus_00f8a769_1"
