Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Latest Rumors",Neutral,50,"Ranis Athrys in the Balmora Mages Guild has something against wizards who aren't in the guild.","Ranis Athrys in the Balmora Mages Guild has something against wizards who aren't in the guild.","MorroDefaultQuest_1latestSrumors_00321631_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I think it has something to do with her parents, who were murdered by the old Telvanni Archmagister, the one before Gothren.","I think it has something to do with her parents, who were murdered by the old Telvanni Archmagister, the one before Gothren.","MorroDefaultQuest_1latestSrumors_00321631_2"
