Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Arethan Mandas",Neutral,50,"My granddaughter is dead, and you are to blame.","My granddaughter is dead, and you are to blame.","fbmwHRMadMilk_1ArethanSMandas_003214fe_1"
"","","Arethan Mandas",Neutral,50,"I can't prove anything, but I believe you are responsible for my son's death. I have nothing to say to you.","I can't prove anything, but I believe you are responsible for my son's death. I have nothing to say to you.","fbmwHRMadMilk_1ArethanSMandas_003214ff_1"
"","","Arethan Mandas",Neutral,50,"Thank you for bringing my son back to his senses.","Thank you for bringing my son back to his senses.","fbmwHRMadMilk_1ArethanSMandas_0001ce56_1"
"","","Arethan Mandas",Neutral,50,"Yes, I heard my son had gone mad. I fear his madness was caused when his daughter, Delyna Mandas, was captured.","Yes, I heard my son had gone mad. I fear his madness was caused when his daughter, Delyna Mandas, was captured.","fbmwHRMadMilk_1ArethanSMandas_0001ce55_1"
"","","Delyna Mandas",Neutral,50,"I heard that Delyna was dead. I don't know if you did it or if that bastard in Tel Fyr did it. Either way, you'll get no help from me.","I heard that Delyna was dead. I don't know if you did it or if that bastard in Tel Fyr did it. Either way, you'll get no help from me.","fbmwHRMadMilk_1DelynaSMandas_0032181e_1"
"","","Delyna Mandas",Neutral,50,"My granddaughter is safe for now, but I fear she will be in trouble again.","My granddaughter is safe for now, but I fear she will be in trouble again.","fbmwHRMadMilk_1DelynaSMandas_00003840_1"
"","","Delyna Mandas",Neutral,50,"You have rescued my granddaughter, and I am grateful. Please take this helm from all the Mandas family.","You have rescued my granddaughter, and I am grateful. Please take this helm from all the Mandas family.","fbmwHRMadMilk_1DelynaSMandas_00003841_1"
"","","Delyna Mandas",Neutral,50,"She is being held captive in Tel Fyr. I do not want to lose another grandchild to the Telvanni. Please bring her back to me.","She is being held captive in Tel Fyr. I do not want to lose another grandchild to the Telvanni. Please bring her back to me.","fbmwHRMadMilk_1DelynaSMandas_0032181f_1"
"","","Tel Fyr",Neutral,50,"Tel Fyr is Divayth Fyr's tower. The only way to get there is to swim straight southwest from Sadrith Mora.","Tel Fyr is Divayth Fyr's tower. The only way to get there is to swim straight southwest from Sadrith Mora.","MorroDefaultQuest_1TelSFyr_00322af5_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Let me mark it on your map in case you get lost.","Let me mark it on your map in case you get lost.","MorroDefaultQuest_1TelSFyr_00322af5_2"
