Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Marksman Weapons",Neutral,50,"Short bows and long bows use arrows. Crossbows use bolts. Bow and crossbows are more cumbersome, two-handed weapons, but more effective.","Short bows and long bows use arrows. Crossbows use bolts. Bow and crossbows are more cumbersome, two-handed weapons, but more effective.","MorroDefaultQuest_1marksmanSweapons_00320cab_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Throwing stars and throwing knives are fast, light, one-handed attacks, but less damaging than bows and crossbows.","Throwing stars and throwing knives are fast, light, one-handed attacks, but less damaging than bows and crossbows.","MorroDefaultQuest_1marksmanSweapons_00320cab_2"
"","","Little Advice",Neutral,50,"Llevana Salaren at the Temple in Molag Mar is the most knowledgeable acrobat I know. I didn't say BEST acrobat.","Llevana Salaren at the Temple in Molag Mar is the most knowledgeable acrobat I know. I didn't say BEST acrobat.","MorroDefaultQuest_1littleSadvice_00321936_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"There's others who can leap higher and jump farther, but she can TALK acrobat talk better than any other acrobat I've ever met.","There's others who can leap higher and jump farther, but she can TALK acrobat talk better than any other acrobat I've ever met.","MorroDefaultQuest_1littleSadvice_00321936_2"
"","","Martial Arts",Neutral,50,"Admirers of the unarmed, unarmored martial arts traditions of the Marshmerrow, Salt Rice, and Golden Reed societies have adapted them for use in the Mages Guild, in the criminal subcultures, and among opponents of Imperial occupation of Morrowind.","Admirers of the unarmed, unarmored martial arts traditions of the Marshmerrow, Salt Rice, and Golden Reed societies have adapted them for use in the Mages Guild, in the criminal subcultures, and among opponents of Imperial occupation of Morrowind.","MorroDefaultQuest_1martialSarts_00321c1c_1"
