Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","The Cleansing",Neutral,50,"It is a ritual suicide, outlander. My brother was no fool, but he was a trusting person, always looking for someone or something to believe in.","It is a ritual suicide, outlander. My brother was no fool, but he was a trusting person, always looking for someone or something to believe in.","fbmwTRShowPower_1theSCleansing_0032177f_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"He thought he had found that in the End of Times.","He thought he had found that in the End of Times.","fbmwTRShowPower_1theSCleansing_0032177f_2"
"","","Meralyn Othan",Neutral,50,"I am she.","I am she.","fbmwTRShowPower_1MeralynSOthan_0032178d_1"
"","","End of Times",Neutral,50,"They are a suicide cult, plain and simple. Their beliefs are destructive, heretical, and frightening to me.","They are a suicide cult, plain and simple. Their beliefs are destructive, heretical, and frightening to me.","fbmwTRShowPower_1EndSofSTimes_00321b23_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I don't know how my brother ever got involved with them!","I don't know how my brother ever got involved with them!","fbmwTRShowPower_1EndSofSTimes_00321b23_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I'm beginning to see them all over the city, but you'll most often find them in Godsreach, outside the Winged Guar.","I'm beginning to see them all over the city, but you'll most often find them in Godsreach, outside the Winged Guar.","fbmwTRShowPower_1EndSofSTimes_00321b23_3"
"","","Eno Romari",Neutral,50,"A lunatic, outlander. You'll often find him outside the Winged Guar, spouting his nonsense to passersby, and to the drunks stumbling out of the tavern.","A lunatic, outlander. You'll often find him outside the Winged Guar, spouting his nonsense to passersby, and to the drunks stumbling out of the tavern.","fbmwTRShowPower_1EnoSRomari_003223fb_1"
"","","Found dead",Neutral,50,"Yes, my brother was found dead not long ago. I think it was poison, probably given to him by Eno Romari and those sick End of Times lunatics.","Yes, my brother was found dead not long ago. I think it was poison, probably given to him by Eno Romari and those sick End of Times lunatics.","fbmwTRShowPower_1foundSdead_003220fe_1"
"","","Beliefs",Neutral,50,"They preach that the Tribunal have lost their powers, and that this is a signal that the apocalypse is near. ","They preach that the Tribunal have lost their powers, and that this is a signal that the apocalypse is near.","fbmwTRShowPower_1beliefs_00f8e5a7_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Eno Romari teaches his followers that our time in Tamriel is at an end, and the gates of Oblivion will soon open and the daedra will walk the land.","Eno Romari teaches his followers that our time in Tamriel is at an end, and the gates of Oblivion will soon open and the daedra will walk the land.","fbmwTRShowPower_1beliefs_00f8e5a7_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Only the ancestors who have already left this world will remain once the daedric scourge covers the earth.","Only the ancestors who have already left this world will remain once the daedric scourge covers the earth.","fbmwTRShowPower_1beliefs_00f8e5a7_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And so he promotes what he calls "the Cleansing."","And so he promotes what he calls "the Cleansing."","fbmwTRShowPower_1beliefs_00f8e5a7_4"
"","","Beliefs",Neutral,50,"They preach that the Tribunal have lost their powers, and that this is a signal that the apocalypse is near.","They preach that the Tribunal have lost their powers, and that this is a signal that the apocalypse is near.","MorroDefaultQuest_1beliefs_00322948_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Eno Romari teaches his followers that our time in Tamriel is at an end, and the gates of Oblivion will soon open and the daedra will walk the land.","Eno Romari teaches his followers that our time in Tamriel is at an end, and the gates of Oblivion will soon open and the daedra will walk the land.","MorroDefaultQuest_1beliefs_00322948_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Only the ancestors who have already left this world will remain once the daedric scourge covers the earth.","Only the ancestors who have already left this world will remain once the daedric scourge covers the earth.","MorroDefaultQuest_1beliefs_00322948_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And so he promotes what he calls "the Cleansing."","And so he promotes what he calls "the Cleansing."","MorroDefaultQuest_1beliefs_00322948_4"
"","","Sevil",Neutral,50,"You've heard about my brother? It's hard to imagine he's gone.","You've heard about my brother? It's hard to imagine he's gone.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Sevil_00322e01_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"All would be well if he hadn't fallen in with Eno Romari and those End of Times lunatics. Sevil was a lonely man, a bit lost, but he was hardly stupid.","All would be well if he hadn't fallen in with Eno Romari and those End of Times lunatics. Sevil was a lonely man, a bit lost, but he was hardly stupid.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Sevil_00322e01_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"It was that cult that caused his death!","It was that cult that caused his death!","MorroDefaultQuest_1Sevil_00322e01_3"
