Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Odirniran",Neutral,50,"It is so much happier here now that the meddling Hlaalu are gone.","It is so much happier here now that the meddling Hlaalu are gone.","fbmwHTOdirniran_1Odirniran_000041d6_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Now, go away, I have work to do.","Now, go away, I have work to do.","fbmwHTOdirniran_1Odirniran_000041d6_2"
"","","Odirniran",Neutral,50,"Remasa Othril and her meddling Hlaalu are gone, yes, but you also let her sister, Vedelea Othril, get away!","Remasa Othril and her meddling Hlaalu are gone, yes, but you also let her sister, Vedelea Othril, get away!","fbmwHTOdirniran_1Odirniran_000054fd_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I was... saving her for an experiment of mine and now you've ruined it.","I was... saving her for an experiment of mine and now you've ruined it.","fbmwHTOdirniran_1Odirniran_000054fd_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Report back to Aryon that I am well. And don't come here every again.","Report back to Aryon that I am well. And don't come here every again.","fbmwHTOdirniran_1Odirniran_000054fd_3"
"","","Odirniran",Neutral,50,"Is Remasa Othril is dead, yes, but you also killed her sister, Vedelea Othril.","Is Remasa Othril is dead, yes, but you also killed her sister, Vedelea Othril.","fbmwHTOdirniran_1Odirniran_003224cc_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I was... saving her for an experiment of mine and now you've ruined it.","I was... saving her for an experiment of mine and now you've ruined it.","fbmwHTOdirniran_1Odirniran_003224cc_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Report back to Aryon that I am well. And don't come here every again.","Report back to Aryon that I am well. And don't come here every again.","fbmwHTOdirniran_1Odirniran_003224cc_3"
"","","Odirniran",Neutral,50,"Is Remasa Othril dead? She is? Excellent. I can get on with my experiments.","Is Remasa Othril dead? She is? Excellent. I can get on with my experiments.","fbmwHTOdirniran_1Odirniran_003224cd_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Since you helped me with these meddling Hlaalu, I might be persuaded to share the results of my research.","Since you helped me with these meddling Hlaalu, I might be persuaded to share the results of my research.","fbmwHTOdirniran_1Odirniran_003224cd_2"
"","","Odirniran",Neutral,50,"Yes, Odirniran is my home. If you wish to help me, please get rid of Remasa Othril, the leader of these Hlaalu who pester me.","Yes, Odirniran is my home. If you wish to help me, please get rid of Remasa Othril, the leader of these Hlaalu who pester me.","fbmwHTOdirniran_1Odirniran_003224ce_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Feel free to kill my servants. I can usually raise them again. ","Feel free to kill my servants. I can usually raise them again.","fbmwHTOdirniran_1Odirniran_003224ce_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Also, please leave Vedelea Othril to me. I do not want her damaged or altered in any way... At least not by you.","Also, please leave Vedelea Othril to me. I do not want her damaged or altered in any way... At least not by you.","fbmwHTOdirniran_1Odirniran_003224ce_3"
"","","Odirniran",Neutral,50,"Odirniran is mine. You shall not take it from me.","Odirniran is mine. You shall not take it from me.","fbmwHTOdirniran_1Odirniran_003224cf_1"
"","","Keep listening",Neutral,50,"Yes, quite. Why not take a sample of these new scrolls and examine them yourself? Now, if you will excuse me, I really must get back to work now.","Yes, quite. Why not take a sample of these new scrolls and examine them yourself? Now, if you will excuse me, I really must get back to work now.","fbmwHTOdirniran_1Odirniran1_00323577_1"
"","","Listen to what he has to say.",Neutral,50,"Scrolls of summoning are, without exception, based on the Law of Similarity as you must know.","Scrolls of summoning are, without exception, based on the Law of Similarity as you must know.","fbmwHTOdirniran_1Odirniran2_00323578_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"While others use parts of the creature, such as Daedra skin for summoning Daedra, I have developed a new methods, based on a recovered Dwemer machine.","While others use parts of the creature, such as Daedra skin for summoning Daedra, I have developed a new methods, based on a recovered Dwemer machine.","fbmwHTOdirniran_1Odirniran2_00323578_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"My scrolls only have an image of the Daedra, which works almost as well as a Daedra skin or heart... And at a fraction of the cost.","My scrolls only have an image of the Daedra, which works almost as well as a Daedra skin or heart... And at a fraction of the cost.","fbmwHTOdirniran_1Odirniran2_00323578_3"
"","","Not interested.",Neutral,50,"You are not interested in my research? Fine, then. I have important work to do.","You are not interested in my research? Fine, then. I have important work to do.","fbmwHTOdirniran_1Odirniran3_00323579_1"
