Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"You did well, outlander. Thank you.","You did well, outlander. Thank you.","fbmwMSTreraynaBounty_GREETING_0000ce6a_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"You did well, outlander. Thank you.","You did well, outlander. Thank you.","fbmwMSTreraynaBounty_GREETING_00f8869f_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Well done, outlander. I can report to my mistress that Trerayna Dalen is no longer a problem. I'll mention your name... for what it's worth. Here's your gold. And my thanks.","Well done, outlander. I can report to my mistress that Trerayna Dalen is no longer a problem. I'll mention your name... for what it's worth. Here's your gold. And my thanks.","fbmwMSTreraynaBounty_GREETING_00f8869e_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"What's the delay? You want your gold, don't you? Kill Trerayna Dalen, and I'll pay you 1000 gold.","What's the delay? You want your gold, don't you? Kill Trerayna Dalen, and I'll pay you 1000 gold.","fbmwMSTreraynaBounty_GREETING_00f8869d_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Outlander. Would you like to earn some gold? Take care of Trerayna Dalen for me.","Outlander. Would you like to earn some gold? Take care of Trerayna Dalen for me.","fbmwMSGreetings_GREETING_0000ce6d_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"She's a petty annoyance, but Mistress Therana won't let me leave the tower to take care of her. Don't be fooled by her thugs.","She's a petty annoyance, but Mistress Therana won't let me leave the tower to take care of her. Don't be fooled by her thugs.","fbmwMSGreetings_GREETING_0000ce6d_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The armor is impressive, but there's not much inside it. Kill Trerayna Dalen, and I'll pay you 1000 gold.","The armor is impressive, but there's not much inside it. Kill Trerayna Dalen, and I'll pay you 1000 gold.","fbmwMSGreetings_GREETING_0000ce6d_3"
"","","Someone in Particular",Neutral,50,"In the village, Llorayna Sethan runs Sethan's Tradehouse. Galen Berer is a smith and armorer. Fadase Selvayn is a trader.","In the village, Llorayna Sethan runs Sethan's Tradehouse. Galen Berer is a smith and armorer. Fadase Selvayn is a trader.","MorroDefaultQuest_1someoneSinSparticular_003206a3_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"In the tower, Mistress Therana is our lady sorceress. Darvasa Vedas is her second-in-command, and the Altmer Mollimo of Cloudrest is her guard captain.","In the tower, Mistress Therana is our lady sorceress. Darvasa Vedas is her second-in-command, and the Altmer Mollimo of Cloudrest is her guard captain.","MorroDefaultQuest_1someoneSinSparticular_003206a3_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And Trerayna Dalen, Mistress Therana's Telvanni challenger, has a camp just outside the village.","And Trerayna Dalen, Mistress Therana's Telvanni challenger, has a camp just outside the village.","MorroDefaultQuest_1someoneSinSparticular_003206a3_3"
"","","Little Advice",Neutral,50,"I bet old Mollimo and his hirelings could make short work of Trerayna Dalen. But they way I hear it, Mistress Therana has got Mollimo on a short leash.","I bet old Mollimo and his hirelings could make short work of Trerayna Dalen. But they way I hear it, Mistress Therana has got Mollimo on a short leash.","MorroDefaultQuest_1littleSadvice_003218c1_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Won't let him out of the tower, wants to keep him and the guard real close so everything safe.","Won't let him out of the tower, wants to keep him and the guard real close so everything safe.","MorroDefaultQuest_1littleSadvice_003218c1_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Granted, it's probably the safest, and most economical tactic, but it's dull and tiresome, and I think it's getting on Mollimo's nerves.","Granted, it's probably the safest, and most economical tactic, but it's dull and tiresome, and I think it's getting on Mollimo's nerves.","MorroDefaultQuest_1littleSadvice_003218c1_3"
"","","Little Advice",Neutral,50,"Security is pretty tight at the tower, what with Trerayna Dalen's siege and all. Better not ruffle any feathers if you have any business in the tower.","Security is pretty tight at the tower, what with Trerayna Dalen's siege and all. Better not ruffle any feathers if you have any business in the tower.","MorroDefaultQuest_1littleSadvice_003218c2_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If Mollimo thinks you've got something cooked up with Dalen, he might kill you first and let the old necromancer ask questions later. Heh-heh.","If Mollimo thinks you've got something cooked up with Dalen, he might kill you first and let the old necromancer ask questions later. Heh-heh.","MorroDefaultQuest_1littleSadvice_003218c2_2"
"","","Little Advice",Neutral,50,"Trerayna Dalen has challenged Mistress Therana for Tel Branora.","Trerayna Dalen has challenged Mistress Therana for Tel Branora.","MorroDefaultQuest_1littleSadvice_003218c3_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Dalen and her mercenaries have been camped out here for months, but they haven't got much to show for it. I think she may have run out of steam.","Dalen and her mercenaries have been camped out here for months, but they haven't got much to show for it. I think she may have run out of steam.","MorroDefaultQuest_1littleSadvice_003218c3_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Or maybe the mercenaries are getting restless. Might be Therana's captain, Mollimo, would welcome some help.","Or maybe the mercenaries are getting restless. Might be Therana's captain, Mollimo, would welcome some help.","MorroDefaultQuest_1littleSadvice_003218c3_3"
