Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Vassir Didanat Mine",Neutral,50,"Yes, I promise you will have great riches. These things take time to arrange.","Yes, I promise you will have great riches. These things take time to arrange.","MorroDefaultQuest_1VassirSDidanatSMine_00f8a297_1"
"","","Vassir Didanat Mine",Neutral,50,"You should have spoken with me instead. I would have promised you more than just a weapon.","You should have spoken with me instead. I would have promised you more than just a weapon.","MorroDefaultQuest_1VassirSDidanatSMine_00f8a298_1"
"","","Vassir Didanat Mine",Neutral,50,"You should have spoken with me instead. I would have promised much more than Velanda Omani.","You should have spoken with me instead. I would have promised much more than Velanda Omani.","MorroDefaultQuest_1VassirSDidanatSMine_00f8a299_1"
"","","Vassir Didanat Mine",Neutral,50,"Are you hinting that you know the location of Vassir-Didanat? I promise that you will have great riches if you tell me the location of this mine...","Are you hinting that you know the location of Vassir-Didanat? I promise that you will have great riches if you tell me the location of this mine...","MorroDefaultQuest_1VassirSDidanatSMine_00f8a29a_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Whatever you do, don't speak a word to Dram Bero or Velanda Omani.","Whatever you do, don't speak a word to Dram Bero or Velanda Omani.","MorroDefaultQuest_1VassirSDidanatSMine_00f8a29a_2"
"","","Hlaalu Hortator",Neutral,50,"You have killed one of the councilors. I will make sure that your request to be Hortator of House Hlaalu is postponed. Indefinitely.","You have killed one of the councilors. I will make sure that your request to be Hortator of House Hlaalu is postponed. Indefinitely.","fbmwMQHlaaluUles_1HlaaluSHortator_00025ac4_1"
"","","Hlaalu Hortator",Neutral,50,"Since everyone agrees, you are the Hortator now, right? Hortator of House Hlaalu? I think you should talk with Crassius Curio again. Something about a belt confirming your title?","Since everyone agrees, you are the Hortator now, right? Hortator of House Hlaalu? I think you should talk with Crassius Curio again. Something about a belt confirming your title?","fbmwMQHlaaluUles_1HlaaluSHortator_00025ac3_1"
"","","Hlaalu Hortator",Neutral,50,"I have given you my vote. There's no need to keep asking me about it. Go talk to the other councilors and get their votes.","I have given you my vote. There's no need to keep asking me about it. Go talk to the other councilors and get their votes.","fbmwMQHlaaluUles_1HlaaluSHortator_00025ac2_1"
"","","Hlaalu Hortator",Neutral,50,"Oh. Yes. You want to be Hortator. Sure. I think that's a very good idea. You'll be a very special Hortator. Is that okay?","Oh. Yes. You want to be Hortator. Sure. I think that's a very good idea. You'll be a very special Hortator. Is that okay?","fbmwMQHlaaluUles_1HlaaluSHortator_00320f19_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Do I need to say anything official? Here. How about... 'In the name of House Hlaalu, I hereby say you are a Hortator. Of this house...","Do I need to say anything official? Here. How about... 'In the name of House Hlaalu, I hereby say you are a Hortator. Of this house...","fbmwMQHlaaluUles_1HlaaluSHortator_00320f19_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"House Hlaalu.' I hope that's right. Once all the councilors agree, make sure you see Crassius Curio.","House Hlaalu.' I hope that's right. Once all the councilors agree, make sure you see Crassius Curio.","fbmwMQHlaaluUles_1HlaaluSHortator_00320f19_3"
"","","Hlaalu Hortator",Neutral,50,"I think that's some kind of war leader. Why are you interested?","I think that's some kind of war leader. Why are you interested?","fbmwMQHlaaluUles_1HlaaluSHortator_00025abf_1"
"","","Tell the location of Vassir-Didanat.",Neutral,50,"Yes, I will have someone investigate. I promise that you will be richly rewarded.","Yes, I will have someone investigate. I promise that you will be richly rewarded.","MorroDefaultQuest_1VassirSDidanatSMine1_00323036_1"
"","","Nevermind.",Neutral,50,"I am disappointed. I thought you knew where Vassir-Didanat was.","I am disappointed. I thought you knew where Vassir-Didanat was.","MorroDefaultQuest_1VassirSDidanatSMine2_00323039_1"
"","","Tell your story and ask to be confirmed as Hortator.",Neutral,50,"I don't know. Don't we already have a Hortator? If we don't, maybe we can find one somewhere.","I don't know. Don't we already have a Hortator? If we don't, maybe we can find one somewhere.","fbmwMQHlaaluUles_1HlaaluSHortator1_003231ea_1"
"","","Tell your story and ask to be confirmed as Hortator.",Neutral,50,"Oh. Oh. Yes. Yes, Ser. The Hortator thing, right? They said, if I knew what was good for me, I would do as you asked. So.","Oh. Oh. Yes. Yes, Ser. The Hortator thing, right? They said, if I knew what was good for me, I would do as you asked. So.","fbmwMQHlaaluUles_1HlaaluSHortator1_00025ac0_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You want to be a Hortator? I make you a Hortator. I vote for you. That's all I have to do, right? Once all the councilors agree, make sure you see Crassius Curio.","You want to be a Hortator? I make you a Hortator. I vote for you. That's all I have to do, right? Once all the councilors agree, make sure you see Crassius Curio.","fbmwMQHlaaluUles_1HlaaluSHortator1_00025ac0_2"
"","","Tell your story and ask to be confirmed as Hortator.",Neutral,50,"Oh. Oh. Yes. Yes, Sera. The Hortator thing, right? They said, if I knew what was good for me, I would do as you asked. So.","Oh. Oh. Yes. Yes, Sera. The Hortator thing, right? They said, if I knew what was good for me, I would do as you asked. So.","fbmwMQHlaaluUles_1HlaaluSHortator1_00025ac1_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You want to be a Hortator? I make you a Hortator. I vote for you. That's all I have to do, right? Once all the councilors agree, make sure you see Crassius Curio.","You want to be a Hortator? I make you a Hortator. I vote for you. That's all I have to do, right? Once all the councilors agree, make sure you see Crassius Curio.","fbmwMQHlaaluUles_1HlaaluSHortator1_00025ac1_2"
"","","Tell your story and ask to be confirmed as Hortator.",Neutral,50,"That's a very strange story, with all the stars and prophecies. I'm not sure I understand what you're asking.","That's a very strange story, with all the stars and prophecies. I'm not sure I understand what you're asking.","fbmwMQHlaaluUles_1HlaaluSHortator1_003231ff_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Maybe you should speak with one of my advisors, Orvas Dren. He owns a plantation in the Ascadian Isles.","Maybe you should speak with one of my advisors, Orvas Dren. He owns a plantation in the Ascadian Isles.","fbmwMQHlaaluUles_1HlaaluSHortator1_003231ff_2"
"","","Tell your story and ask to be confirmed as Hortator.",Neutral,50,"That's a very strange story, with all the stars and prophecies. I'm not sure I understand what you're asking.","That's a very strange story, with all the stars and prophecies. I'm not sure I understand what you're asking.","fbmwMQHlaaluUles_1HlaaluSHortator1_00323200_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Maybe you should speak with one of my advisors, Orvas Dren. He owns a plantation in the Ascadian Isles.","Maybe you should speak with one of my advisors, Orvas Dren. He owns a plantation in the Ascadian Isles.","fbmwMQHlaaluUles_1HlaaluSHortator1_00323200_2"
"","","Tell your story and ask to be confirmed as Hortator.",Neutral,50,"I don't understand at all. What is this about stars and a prophesy? No, don't tell me again. I don't know why you want to be a Hortator.","I don't understand at all. What is this about stars and a prophesy? No, don't tell me again. I don't know why you want to be a Hortator.","fbmwMQHlaaluUles_1HlaaluSHortator1_00323201_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"It's all very confusing. Maybe I should talk to the other counselors. And my advisors.","It's all very confusing. Maybe I should talk to the other counselors. And my advisors.","fbmwMQHlaaluUles_1HlaaluSHortator1_00323201_2"
"","","To Defeat Dagoth Ur.",Neutral,50,"That's a very strange story, with all the stars and prophecies. I'm not sure I understand what you're asking.","That's a very strange story, with all the stars and prophecies. I'm not sure I understand what you're asking.","fbmwMQHlaaluUles_1HlaaluSHortator2_003231ef_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Maybe you should speak with one of my advisors, Orvas Dren. He owns a plantation in the Ascadian Isles.","Maybe you should speak with one of my advisors, Orvas Dren. He owns a plantation in the Ascadian Isles.","fbmwMQHlaaluUles_1HlaaluSHortator2_003231ef_2"
"","","To Defeat Dagoth Ur.",Neutral,50,"That's a very strange story, with all the stars and prophecies. I'm not sure I understand what you're asking.","That's a very strange story, with all the stars and prophecies. I'm not sure I understand what you're asking.","fbmwMQHlaaluUles_1HlaaluSHortator2_003231f0_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Maybe you should speak with one of my advisors, Orvas Dren. He owns a plantation in the Ascadian Isles.","Maybe you should speak with one of my advisors, Orvas Dren. He owns a plantation in the Ascadian Isles.","fbmwMQHlaaluUles_1HlaaluSHortator2_003231f0_2"
"","","To Defeat Dagoth Ur.",Neutral,50,"I don't understand at all. What is this about stars and a prophesy? No, don't tell me again. I don't know why you want to be a Hortator.","I don't understand at all. What is this about stars and a prophesy? No, don't tell me again. I don't know why you want to be a Hortator.","fbmwMQHlaaluUles_1HlaaluSHortator2_003231f1_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"It's all very confusing. Maybe I should talk to the other counselors. And my advisors.","It's all very confusing. Maybe I should talk to the other counselors. And my advisors.","fbmwMQHlaaluUles_1HlaaluSHortator2_003231f1_2"
"","","Ask how a Hortator is chosen.",Neutral,50,"I don't know. Don't we already have a Hortator? If we don't, maybe we can find one somewhere.","I don't know. Don't we already have a Hortator? If we don't, maybe we can find one somewhere.","fbmwMQHlaaluUles_1HlaaluSHortator6_003231fa_1"
