Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Murderer's Description",Neutral,50,"See? Now you know I am innocent.","See? Now you know I am innocent.","fbmwHHRetaliation_1murdererAsSdescription_00005e7f_1"
"","","Blades Trainers",Neutral,50,"The basics we can teach you, won't cost much. Advanced training, though... that's expensive. If you're already skilled, you're much harder to teach.","The basics we can teach you, won't cost much. Advanced training, though... that's expensive. If you're already skilled, you're much harder to teach.","fbmwBladesTrainers_1BladesSTrainers_0032109a_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Maybe I can help you out. Here's a little moon sugar, on the house.","Maybe I can help you out. Here's a little moon sugar, on the house.","fbmwBladesTrainers_1BladesSTrainers_0032109a_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You do know that trade in moon sugar and skooma is against the law, and most alchemists and apothecaries won't buy it. But Khajiit generally will.","You do know that trade in moon sugar and skooma is against the law, and most alchemists and apothecaries won't buy it. But Khajiit generally will.","fbmwBladesTrainers_1BladesSTrainers_0032109a_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Try Ajira at the Balmora Mages Guild, or Ra'Virr, the trader in Balmora. Sell the sugar, and start saving for training.","Try Ajira at the Balmora Mages Guild, or Ra'Virr, the trader in Balmora. Sell the sugar, and start saving for training.","fbmwBladesTrainers_1BladesSTrainers_0032109a_4"
"","","Latest Rumors",Neutral,50,"I'm trying to update our maps of the Bitter Coast. There are no goods maps of this area. Period. Islands, mountains, swamps, lakes, rivers.","I'm trying to update our maps of the Bitter Coast. There are no goods maps of this area. Period. Islands, mountains, swamps, lakes, rivers.","MorroDefaultQuest_1latestSrumors_003215fd_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"It's impossible. I'm getting to know the swamps and waterways here, maybe as well as the natives.","It's impossible. I'm getting to know the swamps and waterways here, maybe as well as the natives.","MorroDefaultQuest_1latestSrumors_003215fd_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But I can't blend with the natives, and I'm useless in the West Gash or the Ashlands. And I don't see why the maps are so important. Smuggling, maybe.","But I can't blend with the natives, and I'm useless in the West Gash or the Ashlands. And I don't see why the maps are so important. Smuggling, maybe.","MorroDefaultQuest_1latestSrumors_003215fd_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But I'm wondering if they're thinking about landing and moving the Legions through here. In case of trouble.","But I'm wondering if they're thinking about landing and moving the Legions through here. In case of trouble.","MorroDefaultQuest_1latestSrumors_003215fd_4"
"","","Ralen Hlaalo",Neutral,50,"I heard you found the real murderer. It is good to trust each other among these slavers, outlander.","I heard you found the real murderer. It is good to trust each other among these slavers, outlander.","fbmwHHRetaliation_1RalenSHlaalo_00005e89_1"
"","","Ralen Hlaalo",Neutral,50,"I heard you found the real murderer. I am grateful to you, soft-skin.","I heard you found the real murderer. I am grateful to you, soft-skin.","fbmwHHRetaliation_1RalenSHlaalo_00005e8a_1"
"","","Ralen Hlaalo",Neutral,50,"I have heard the rumors, but I am not a murderer. I believe someone is spreading these rumors because I am a foreigner and an Argonian.","I have heard the rumors, but I am not a murderer. I believe someone is spreading these rumors because I am a foreigner and an Argonian.","fbmwHHRetaliation_1RalenSHlaalo_00321bc7_1"
"","","Nine-Toes",Neutral,50,"Yes, I am Nine-Toes.","Yes, I am Nine-Toes.","MorroDefaultQuest_1NineTToes_00322453_1"
"","","Blades",Neutral,50,"I'm a Blade, too, and I report to Caius, like you. You're welcome to use my bed to rest, but leave my other stuff alone, please.","I'm a Blade, too, and I report to Caius, like you. You're welcome to use my bed to rest, but leave my other stuff alone, please.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Blades_00322b46_1"
