Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Ahhh...one of the dark ones. You are an interesting lot. Mistress Dratha has a task for you. She would like the Altmer named Rimintil eliminated.","Ahhh...one of the dark ones. You are an interesting lot. Mistress Dratha has a task for you. She would like the Altmer named Rimintil eliminated.","fbmwMSGreetings_GREETING_0000a99d_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Did you find the Black Jinx?","Did you find the Black Jinx?","fbmwHTAdvancement_GREETING_0000828e_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Do you have the muck?","Do you have the muck?","fbmwHTAdvancement_GREETING_0000828f_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I am Raven Omayn, Mouth of Mistress Dratha.","I am Raven Omayn, Mouth of Mistress Dratha.","fbmwHTAdvancement_GREETING_00008290_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Have you taken care of Rimintil, vampire?","Have you taken care of Rimintil, vampire?","fbmwVARimintil_GREETING_0000a99c_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Have you retrieved the Quarra Blood Potion yet?","Have you retrieved the Quarra Blood Potion yet?","fbmwVAVampBlood2_GREETING_0000a99b_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Mistress Dratha has no more words for you.","Mistress Dratha has no more words for you.","MorroDefaultQuest_GREETING_0000a99a_1"
"","","Yes, here it is.",Neutral,50,"Yes, this is it. Mistress Dratha will appreciate this. The ring can instill fear in others.","Yes, this is it. Mistress Dratha will appreciate this. The ring can instill fear in others.","fbmwHTBlackJinx_1BlackSJinx5_00323554_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I know a spell or two that are not as powerful as this ring, but I will teach them to you if you wish to learn.","I know a spell or two that are not as powerful as this ring, but I will teach them to you if you wish to learn.","fbmwHTBlackJinx_1BlackSJinx5_00323554_2"
"","","Yes, here it is.",Anger,50,"Why should I believe you if you won't show me the ring? Bring the ring to me or stop wasting my time.","Why should I believe you if you won't show me the ring? Bring the ring to me or stop wasting my time.","fbmwHTBlackJinx_1BlackSJinx5_00323555_1"
"","","No, not yet.",Neutral,50,"Then keep trying. Surely someone here in Sadrith Mora has heard of it.","Then keep trying. Surely someone here in Sadrith Mora has heard of it.","fbmwHTBlackJinx_1BlackSJinx6_00323557_1"
"","","Quarra Blood Potion",Neutral,50,"Mistress Dratha will be pleased to be able to study the Blood.","Mistress Dratha will be pleased to be able to study the Blood.","fbmwVAVampBlood2_1QuarraSBloodSPotion_00f8ad4b_1"
"","","Quarra Blood Potion",Neutral,50,"You have the Blood. Well done, vampire. Perhaps your kind can be trained after all.","You have the Blood. Well done, vampire. Perhaps your kind can be trained after all.","fbmwVAVampBlood2_1QuarraSBloodSPotion_00f8ad4d_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"As a reward for your effort, I have something your kind might be able to use.","As a reward for your effort, I have something your kind might be able to use.","fbmwVAVampBlood2_1QuarraSBloodSPotion_00f8ad4d_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"During an enchanting experiment, I created this Jinksword. It is strong and sharp, but the enchantment did not go as planned.","During an enchanting experiment, I created this Jinksword. It is strong and sharp, but the enchantment did not go as planned.","fbmwVAVampBlood2_1QuarraSBloodSPotion_00f8ad4d_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I believe one of your ilk might find it valuable, though, as you seem to have a natural resistance to the spell in question.","I believe one of your ilk might find it valuable, though, as you seem to have a natural resistance to the spell in question.","fbmwVAVampBlood2_1QuarraSBloodSPotion_00f8ad4d_4"
"","","Quarra Blood Potion",Neutral,50,"You already have the Blood, vampire? An interesting coincidence.","You already have the Blood, vampire? An interesting coincidence.","fbmwVAVampBlood2_1QuarraSBloodSPotion_00f8ad4c_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Mistress Dratha will be pleased to have it in her possession.","Mistress Dratha will be pleased to have it in her possession.","fbmwVAVampBlood2_1QuarraSBloodSPotion_00f8ad4c_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"As a reward for your effort, I have something your kind might be able to use.","As a reward for your effort, I have something your kind might be able to use.","fbmwVAVampBlood2_1QuarraSBloodSPotion_00f8ad4c_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"During an enchanting experiment, I created this Jinksword.","During an enchanting experiment, I created this Jinksword.","fbmwVAVampBlood2_1QuarraSBloodSPotion_00f8ad4c_4"
"","","",Neutral,50,"It is strong and sharp, but the enchantment did not go as planned.","It is strong and sharp, but the enchantment did not go as planned.","fbmwVAVampBlood2_1QuarraSBloodSPotion_00f8ad4c_5"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I believe one of your ilk might find it valuable, though, as you seem to have a natural resistance to the spell in question.","I believe one of your ilk might find it valuable, though, as you seem to have a natural resistance to the spell in question.","fbmwVAVampBlood2_1QuarraSBloodSPotion_00f8ad4c_6"
"","","Quarra Blood Potion",Neutral,50,"Mistress Dratha believes that the study of the Blood of the Quarra Ancients could lead to a greater understanding of the abilities your kind possesses. It is important for her to obtain it.","Mistress Dratha believes that the study of the Blood of the Quarra Ancients could lead to a greater understanding of the abilities your kind possesses. It is important for her to obtain it.","fbmwVAVampBlood2_1QuarraSBloodSPotion_00f8ad4f_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If her information is correct, the potion will be found close to Volrina Quarra, in her clan's lair in Druscashti.","If her information is correct, the potion will be found close to Volrina Quarra, in her clan's lair in Druscashti.","fbmwVAVampBlood2_1QuarraSBloodSPotion_00f8ad4f_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If it is not, only your kind might know where it resides now. Return it to me, vampire.","If it is not, only your kind might know where it resides now. Return it to me, vampire.","fbmwVAVampBlood2_1QuarraSBloodSPotion_00f8ad4f_4"
"","","Quarra Blood Potion",Neutral,50,"Mistress Dratha believes that the study of the Blood of the Quarra Ancients could lead to a greater understanding of the abilities your kind possesses. It is important for her to obtain it.","Mistress Dratha believes that the study of the Blood of the Quarra Ancients could lead to a greater understanding of the abilities your kind possesses. It is important for her to obtain it.","fbmwVAVampBlood2_1QuarraSBloodSPotion_00f8ad4e_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If her information is correct, the potion will be found close to Volrina Quarra, in her clan's lair in Druscashti.","If her information is correct, the potion will be found close to Volrina Quarra, in her clan's lair in Druscashti.","fbmwVAVampBlood2_1QuarraSBloodSPotion_00f8ad4e_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If it is not, only your kind might know where it resides now. Return it to me, vampire.","If it is not, only your kind might know where it resides now. Return it to me, vampire.","fbmwVAVampBlood2_1QuarraSBloodSPotion_00f8ad4e_4"
"","","Telvanni Hortator",Neutral,50,"That's a title given to a special champion and war leader among the Great Houses. Why?","That's a title given to a special champion and war leader among the Great Houses. Why?","fbmwMQ10_1TelvanniSHortator_00025aed_1"
"","","Mistress Dratha",Neutral,50,"She is my patron, and I am her Mouth on the council. If you have personal business with her, you may find her in Tel Mora.","She is my patron, and I am her Mouth on the council. If you have personal business with her, you may find her in Tel Mora.","MorroDefaultQuest_1MistressSDratha_00321093_1"
"","","Black Jinx",Neutral,50,"You have already given me the Black Jinx.","You have already given me the Black Jinx.","fbmwHTBlackJinx_1BlackSJinx_00008299_1"
"","","Black Jinx",Neutral,50,"Have you found the Ring of the Black Jinx?","Have you found the Ring of the Black Jinx?","fbmwHTBlackJinx_1BlackSJinx_0000829a_1"
"","","Black Jinx",Neutral,50,"Mistress Dratha has always had an interest in this ring.","Mistress Dratha has always had an interest in this ring.","fbmwHTBlackJinx_1BlackSJinx_0000829b_1"
"","","Rimintil",Neutral,50,"I understand you've taken care of the troublesome Rimintil. Your kind does have its uses. There are many of us who would like to learn more about your...inner workings, but that is unimportant now.","I understand you've taken care of the troublesome Rimintil. Your kind does have its uses. There are many of us who would like to learn more about your...inner workings, but that is unimportant now.","fbmwVARimintil_1Rimintil_00f8ad8a_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You have done well. Take this for your own use. I think your kind will find it valuable.","You have done well. Take this for your own use. I think your kind will find it valuable.","fbmwVARimintil_1Rimintil_00f8ad8a_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"There is one thing further Mistress Dratha requires from you: the Quarra Blood Potion.","There is one thing further Mistress Dratha requires from you: the Quarra Blood Potion.","fbmwVARimintil_1Rimintil_00f8ad8a_4"
"","","Rimintil",Neutral,50,"You have already killed him. That is good. Your kind has its uses.","You have already killed him. That is good. Your kind has its uses.","fbmwVARimintil_1Rimintil_00f8ec51_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"There are many of us who would like to learn more about your...inner workings, but that is unimportant now.","There are many of us who would like to learn more about your...inner workings, but that is unimportant now.","fbmwVARimintil_1Rimintil_00f8ec51_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You have done well. Take this for your own use. I think your kind will find it valuable.","You have done well. Take this for your own use. I think your kind will find it valuable.","fbmwVARimintil_1Rimintil_00f8ec51_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"There is one thing further Mistress Dratha requires from you: the Quarra Blood Potion.","There is one thing further Mistress Dratha requires from you: the Quarra Blood Potion.","fbmwVARimintil_1Rimintil_00f8ec51_4"
"","","Rimintil",Neutral,50,"Yes, he poses a problem for Mistress Dratha. That is not your concern.","Yes, he poses a problem for Mistress Dratha. That is not your concern.","fbmwVARimintil_1Rimintil_00f8ad89_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Your people reek of death; it is only fitting we use your penchant for bringing it upon others to our own ends.","Your people reek of death; it is only fitting we use your penchant for bringing it upon others to our own ends.","fbmwVARimintil_1Rimintil_00f8ad89_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You will find him in the Central Tower of Tel Vos. Dispose of him and return to me.","You will find him in the Central Tower of Tel Vos. Dispose of him and return to me.","fbmwVARimintil_1Rimintil_00f8ad89_3"
"","","Chores",Neutral,50,"I have no other chores for you. Check with the other Mouths.","I have no other chores for you. Check with the other Mouths.","fbmwHTAdvancement_1chores_00008297_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You may also speak with my patron, Mistress Dratha, but be warned that she does not like men.","You may also speak with my patron, Mistress Dratha, but be warned that she does not like men.","fbmwHTAdvancement_1chores_00008297_2"
"","","Chores",Neutral,50,"I have no other chores for you. Check with my patron, Mistress Dratha, or with the other Mouths.","I have no other chores for you. Check with my patron, Mistress Dratha, or with the other Mouths.","fbmwHTAdvancement_1chores_00008296_1"
"","","Chores",Neutral,50,"Mistress Dratha wants a ring known as the Black Jinx.","Mistress Dratha wants a ring known as the Black Jinx.","fbmwHTAdvancement_1chores_00008295_1"
"","","Chores",Neutral,50,"Daynali Dren, Mistress Dratha's Alchemist, needs five portions of muck.","Daynali Dren, Mistress Dratha's Alchemist, needs five portions of muck.","fbmwHTAdvancement_1chores_00322c02_1"
"","","Muck",Neutral,50,"You already brought me five portions of muck.","You already brought me five portions of muck.","fbmwHTMuck_1muck_00008291_1"
"","","Muck",Neutral,50,"Do you have the five portions of muck?","Do you have the five portions of muck?","fbmwHTMuck_1muck_00008294_1"
"","","Muck",Neutral,50,"Yes, I am looking for five portions of muck. Many alchemists sell it and you can gather it yourself from muckspunge.","Yes, I am looking for five portions of muck. Many alchemists sell it and you can gather it yourself from muckspunge.","fbmwHTMuck_1muck_00322ed9_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Once you have five portions of muck, bring them to me.","Once you have five portions of muck, bring them to me.","fbmwHTMuck_1muck_00322ed9_2"
"","","How is a Hortator chosen?",Neutral,50,"All the Telvanni councilors must vote to choose a Hortator, and the vote must be unanimous. It's an old tradition, rarely used -- never in my lifetime.","All the Telvanni councilors must vote to choose a Hortator, and the vote must be unanimous. It's an old tradition, rarely used -- never in my lifetime.","fbmwMQ10_1TelvanniSHortator1_003230dc_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"A Hortator's duty is to lead a Great House in war, and we haven't had a war in a very long time.","A Hortator's duty is to lead a Great House in war, and we haven't had a war in a very long time.","fbmwMQ10_1TelvanniSHortator1_003230dc_2"
"","","Tell your story and ask to be confirmed as Hortator.",Neutral,50,"Good grief. We've heard talk about a reborn Nerevar for years, and thought it was just Ashlander superstition.","Good grief. We've heard talk about a reborn Nerevar for years, and thought it was just Ashlander superstition.","fbmwMQTelvanniDratha_1TelvanniSHortator2_003230fa_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You'll have to speak directly to Mistress Dratha about this. She lives at Tel Mora, a tower north along the coast.","You'll have to speak directly to Mistress Dratha about this. She lives at Tel Mora, a tower north along the coast.","fbmwMQTelvanniDratha_1TelvanniSHortator2_003230fa_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You should be able to find a ship at the docks to take you there for a pittance. And I must warn you. Mistress Dratha doesn't like men. Of any race.","You should be able to find a ship at the docks to take you there for a pittance. And I must warn you. Mistress Dratha doesn't like men. Of any race.","fbmwMQTelvanniDratha_1TelvanniSHortator2_003230fa_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I suggest you do everything possible to improve her disposition before talking to her.","I suggest you do everything possible to improve her disposition before talking to her.","fbmwMQTelvanniDratha_1TelvanniSHortator2_003230fa_4"
"","","Tell your story and ask to be confirmed as Hortator.",Neutral,50,"Good grief. We've heard talk about a reborn Nerevar for years, and thought it was just Ashlander superstition.","Good grief. We've heard talk about a reborn Nerevar for years, and thought it was just Ashlander superstition.","fbmwMQTelvanniDratha_1TelvanniSHortator2_003230fb_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And it sounds like a crisis is coming with Dagoth Ur and the Sixth House. You'll have to speak directly to Mistress Dratha about this.","And it sounds like a crisis is coming with Dagoth Ur and the Sixth House. You'll have to speak directly to Mistress Dratha about this.","fbmwMQTelvanniDratha_1TelvanniSHortator2_003230fb_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"She lives in Tel Mora, a tower north along the coast. You should be able to find a ship at the docks to take you there for a pittance.","She lives in Tel Mora, a tower north along the coast. You should be able to find a ship at the docks to take you there for a pittance.","fbmwMQTelvanniDratha_1TelvanniSHortator2_003230fb_3"
"","","Yes, teach me the spells.",Neutral,50,"Very well. [Raven teaches you how to demoralize your opponents.] If you want more chores, speak with the other Mouths.","Very well. [Raven teaches you how to demoralize your opponents.] If you want more chores, speak with the other Mouths.","fbmwHTBlackJinx_1BlackSJinx3_00323558_1"
"","","No thank you.",Neutral,50,"If you want more chores, speak with the others Mouths.","If you want more chores, speak with the others Mouths.","fbmwHTBlackJinx_1BlackSJinx4_00323559_1"
"","","Yes, here they are.",Neutral,50,"Good. Here, take these hundred drakes for your trouble.","Good. Here, take these hundred drakes for your trouble.","fbmwHTMuck_1muck1_00008292_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I already have enough gravedust and green lichen to finish these potions of cure disease.","I already have enough gravedust and green lichen to finish these potions of cure disease.","fbmwHTMuck_1muck1_00008292_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"It would be so much easier if everyone could cure themselves...","It would be so much easier if everyone could cure themselves...","fbmwHTMuck_1muck1_00008292_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You CAN do that, can't you?","You CAN do that, can't you?","fbmwHTMuck_1muck1_00008292_4"
"","","Yes, here they are.",Neutral,50,"Do not try my patience with lies and stories, outlander! Bring me five portions of muck.","Do not try my patience with lies and stories, outlander! Bring me five portions of muck.","fbmwHTMuck_1muck1_00008293_1"
"","","No, not yet.",Neutral,50,"Then go get them.","Then go get them.","fbmwHTMuck_1muck2_003236ab_1"
"","","Yes, of course.",Neutral,50,"Good. Perhaps you are not totally hopeless. If you do not want any more chores, go about your business.","Good. Perhaps you are not totally hopeless. If you do not want any more chores, go about your business.","fbmwHTMuck_1muck3_003236ac_1"
"","","No. Could you teach me?",Neutral,50,"Oh, very well. [Raven instructs you in the spell.] There. Now if you do not wish for more chores, go about your business.","Oh, very well. [Raven instructs you in the spell.] There. Now if you do not wish for more chores, go about your business.","fbmwHTMuck_1muck4_003236ad_1"
