Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Greetings and welcome, sera! Are you in the market for trained scribs and rats?","Greetings and welcome, sera! Are you in the market for trained scribs and rats?","fbmwMSGreetings_GREETING_00009ebe_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I think you'll find my prices quite reasonable, and my rats and scribs are fine as pets or beasts of burden -- or as tasty little morsels.","I think you'll find my prices quite reasonable, and my rats and scribs are fine as pets or beasts of burden -- or as tasty little morsels.","fbmwMSGreetings_GREETING_00009ebe_2"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I'm not selling you any more of my trained beasts. You don't take good enough care of them.","I'm not selling you any more of my trained beasts. You don't take good enough care of them.","fbmwMSBadPets_GREETING_00009ebf_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Greetings and welcome, sera! Are you in the market for trained scribs and rats?","Greetings and welcome, sera! Are you in the market for trained scribs and rats?","fbmwMSBadPets_GREETING_0000b804_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I think you'll find my prices quite reasonable, and my rats and scribs are fine as pets or beasts of burden -- or as tasty little morsels.","I think you'll find my prices quite reasonable, and my rats and scribs are fine as pets or beasts of burden -- or as tasty little morsels.","fbmwMSBadPets_GREETING_0000b804_2"
"","","Latest Rumors",Neutral,50,"If you're thinking of going down the sewers to explore Old Mournhold, watch out for the Black Dart Gang. ","If you're thinking of going down the sewers to explore Old Mournhold, watch out for the Black Dart Gang.","MorroDefaultQuest_1latestSrumors_00016524_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"They look like helpless paupers, but they are deadly. They prey on adventurers coming out of the ruins loaded with treasure.","They look like helpless paupers, but they are deadly. They prey on adventurers coming out of the ruins loaded with treasure.","MorroDefaultQuest_1latestSrumors_00016524_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"They call them the Black Dart Gang on account of the poisoned black darts they use -- deadly poison -- one is enough to kill you.","They call them the Black Dart Gang on account of the poisoned black darts they use -- deadly poison -- one is enough to kill you.","MorroDefaultQuest_1latestSrumors_00016524_3"
"","","Latest Rumors",Neutral,50,"Packrats. Really. You think I'm kidding. But Rerlas Mon is selling them in the Great Bazaar.","Packrats. Really. You think I'm kidding. But Rerlas Mon is selling them in the Great Bazaar.","MorroDefaultQuest_1latestSrumors_00016531_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You'd be surprised how well-trained they are, and how much they can carry. Cheap, too. And in a tight spot, they're pretty good for stew.","You'd be surprised how well-trained they are, and how much they can carry. Cheap, too. And in a tight spot, they're pretty good for stew.","MorroDefaultQuest_1latestSrumors_00016531_2"
"","","Trained Scribs and Rats",Neutral,50,"Yes, when I was a lad, I dreamed of being the greatest scrib and rat trainer in the world.","Yes, when I was a lad, I dreamed of being the greatest scrib and rat trainer in the world.","fbmwMSBadPets_1trainedSscribsSandSrats_00320502_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And, given the limited capacities of scribs and rats, I flatter myself that I've achieved my goal. These creatures are priceless...","And, given the limited capacities of scribs and rats, I flatter myself that I've achieved my goal. These creatures are priceless...","fbmwMSBadPets_1trainedSscribsSandSrats_00320502_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"but since I find myself unexpectedly short of cash, I'm reduced to selling off my superbly trained scribs and rats as pets.","but since I find myself unexpectedly short of cash, I'm reduced to selling off my superbly trained scribs and rats as pets.","fbmwMSBadPets_1trainedSscribsSandSrats_00320502_3"
"","","Selling off",Neutral,50,"That's right, you can have a scrib for the low, low price of 20 gold, or a rat for 25.","That's right, you can have a scrib for the low, low price of 20 gold, or a rat for 25.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff_00321d8c_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"They are trained to follow you and attack anyone who attacks you. OR you can buy my exclusive pack rat for 100 gold.","They are trained to follow you and attack anyone who attacks you. OR you can buy my exclusive pack rat for 100 gold.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff_00321d8c_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"They not only follow and fight, but also carry small burdens. And, in a pinch, you've got fresh meat on the hoof, whenever you need it.","They not only follow and fight, but also carry small burdens. And, in a pinch, you've got fresh meat on the hoof, whenever you need it.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff_00321d8c_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"What do you say?  Would you like one?","What do you say?  Would you like one?","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff_00321d8c_4"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy your exclusive pack rat.",Neutral,50,"Good grief, outlander. Six of the best packrats ever to come out of my stable... dead! And you want me to sell you more? No, sera! I just can't stand it!","Good grief, outlander. Six of the best packrats ever to come out of my stable... dead! And you want me to sell you more? No, sera! I just can't stand it!","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff3_00323456_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"All that work I put into training them, and you treating them like grocery items? No! It just won't do!","All that work I put into training them, and you treating them like grocery items? No! It just won't do!","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff3_00323456_2"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy your exclusive pack rat.",Neutral,50,"Sorry, outlander. I don't have any packrats in my stable, and I don't think I'll have any more in the foreseeable future.","Sorry, outlander. I don't have any packrats in my stable, and I don't think I'll have any more in the foreseeable future.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff3_00f8e8bb_1"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy your exclusive pack rat.",Neutral,50,"Here is one of my finest pack rats.  He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go. AND he'll carry small burdens for you.","Here is one of my finest pack rats.  He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go. AND he'll carry small burdens for you.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff3_00f8e8bc_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But take good care of him. Seems a shame to eat the poor little fellows, after all the trouble I have in capturing them and training them.","But take good care of him. Seems a shame to eat the poor little fellows, after all the trouble I have in capturing them and training them.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff3_00f8e8bc_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But.. the customer is always right, and they're yours to do with as you wish.","But.. the customer is always right, and they're yours to do with as you wish.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff3_00f8e8bc_3"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy your exclusive pack rat.",Neutral,50,"Here is one of my finest pack rats.  He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go. AND he'll carry small burdens for you.","Here is one of my finest pack rats.  He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go. AND he'll carry small burdens for you.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff3_00009efe_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But take good care of him. Seems a shame to eat the poor little fellows, after all the trouble I have in capturing them and training them.","But take good care of him. Seems a shame to eat the poor little fellows, after all the trouble I have in capturing them and training them.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff3_00009efe_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But.. the customer is always right, and they're yours to do with as you wish.","But.. the customer is always right, and they're yours to do with as you wish.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff3_00009efe_3"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy your exclusive pack rat.",Neutral,50,"Here is one of my finest pack rats.  He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go. AND he'll carry small burdens for you.","Here is one of my finest pack rats.  He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go. AND he'll carry small burdens for you.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff3_00009eff_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But take good care of him. Seems a shame to eat the poor little fellows, after all the trouble I have in capturing them and training them.","But take good care of him. Seems a shame to eat the poor little fellows, after all the trouble I have in capturing them and training them.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff3_00009eff_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But.. the customer is always right, and they're yours to do with as you wish.","But.. the customer is always right, and they're yours to do with as you wish.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff3_00009eff_3"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy your exclusive pack rat.",Neutral,50,"Sorry, outlander. I don't have any more in my stable, and it takes a while to train them. Tell you what.","Sorry, outlander. I don't have any more in my stable, and it takes a while to train them. Tell you what.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff3_00323459_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Check by with me later, and I'll see what can be done.","Check by with me later, and I'll see what can be done.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff3_00323459_2"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy your exclusive pack rat.",Neutral,50,"Sorry, outlander. I don't have any more in my stable, and it takes a while to train them. Tell you what.","Sorry, outlander. I don't have any more in my stable, and it takes a while to train them. Tell you what.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff3_0000b803_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Check by with me later, and I'll see what can be done.","Check by with me later, and I'll see what can be done.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff3_0000b803_2"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy your exclusive pack rat.",Neutral,50,"Thanks, outlander. Here is your very own pack rat. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go. AND he'll carry small burdens for you.","Thanks, outlander. Here is your very own pack rat. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go. AND he'll carry small burdens for you.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff3_00f8e8bd_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But take good care of him. They don't grow on trees, you know.","But take good care of him. They don't grow on trees, you know.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff3_00f8e8bd_2"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy your exclusive pack rat.",Neutral,50,"Thanks, outlander. Here is your very own pack rat. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go. AND he'll carry small burdens for you.","Thanks, outlander. Here is your very own pack rat. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go. AND he'll carry small burdens for you.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff3_00009f00_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But take good care of him. They don't grow on trees, you know.","But take good care of him. They don't grow on trees, you know.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff3_00009f00_2"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy your exclusive pack rat.",Neutral,50,"Thanks, outlander. Here is your very own pack rat. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go. AND he'll carry small burdens for you.","Thanks, outlander. Here is your very own pack rat. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go. AND he'll carry small burdens for you.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff3_00009f01_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But take good care of him. They don't grow on trees, you know.","But take good care of him. They don't grow on trees, you know.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff3_00009f01_2"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy your exclusive pack rat.",Neutral,50,"I'd love to sell you one, outlander, but it doesn't look like you can afford it. ","I'd love to sell you one, outlander, but it doesn't look like you can afford it.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff3_00009efd_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Come back when you have the money and I'll have the creature packaged up and ready to go.","Come back when you have the money and I'll have the creature packaged up and ready to go.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff3_00009efd_2"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy a rat.",Neutral,50,"Good grief, outlander. Six of the best rats ever to come out of my stable... dead! And you want me to sell you more? No, sera!","Good grief, outlander. Six of the best rats ever to come out of my stable... dead! And you want me to sell you more? No, sera!","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff2_00009f04_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I just can't stand it! All that work I put into training them, and you treating them like grocery items? No! It just won't do!","I just can't stand it! All that work I put into training them, and you treating them like grocery items? No! It just won't do!","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff2_00009f04_2"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy a rat.",Neutral,50,"Sorry, outlander. I don't have any more in my stable, and it takes a while to train them. Tell you what.","Sorry, outlander. I don't have any more in my stable, and it takes a while to train them. Tell you what.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff2_0032345f_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Check by with me later, and I'll see what can be done.","Check by with me later, and I'll see what can be done.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff2_0032345f_2"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy a rat.",Neutral,50,"Here is one of my finest pet rats. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go. But take good care of him.","Here is one of my finest pet rats. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go. But take good care of him.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff2_0032345e_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"They're hard to train, you know. Seems a shame to eat the poor little fellows, after all the trouble I have in capturing them and training them. But..","They're hard to train, you know. Seems a shame to eat the poor little fellows, after all the trouble I have in capturing them and training them. But..","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff2_0032345e_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"the customer is always right, and they're yours to do with as you wish.","the customer is always right, and they're yours to do with as you wish.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff2_0032345e_3"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy a rat.",Neutral,50,"Here is one of my finest pet rats. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go. But take good care of him.","Here is one of my finest pet rats. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go. But take good care of him.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff2_00f8e8be_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"They're hard to train, you know. Seems a shame to eat the poor little fellows, after all the trouble I have in capturing them and training them. But..","They're hard to train, you know. Seems a shame to eat the poor little fellows, after all the trouble I have in capturing them and training them. But..","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff2_00f8e8be_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"the customer is always right, and they're yours to do with as you wish.","the customer is always right, and they're yours to do with as you wish.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff2_00f8e8be_3"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy a rat.",Neutral,50,"Here is one of my finest pet rats. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go. But take good care of him.","Here is one of my finest pet rats. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go. But take good care of him.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff2_00f8e8bf_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"They're hard to train, you know. Seems a shame to eat the poor little fellows, after all the trouble I have in capturing them and training them. But..","They're hard to train, you know. Seems a shame to eat the poor little fellows, after all the trouble I have in capturing them and training them. But..","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff2_00f8e8bf_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"the customer is always right, and they're yours to do with as you wish.","the customer is always right, and they're yours to do with as you wish.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff2_00f8e8bf_3"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy a rat.",Neutral,50,"Sorry, outlander. I don't have any pet rats in my stable, and I don't think I'll have any more in the foreseeable future.","Sorry, outlander. I don't have any pet rats in my stable, and I don't think I'll have any more in the foreseeable future.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff2_0032345d_1"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy a rat.",Neutral,50,"Sorry, outlander. I don't have any pet rats in my stable, and I don't think I'll have any more in the foreseeable future.","Sorry, outlander. I don't have any pet rats in my stable, and I don't think I'll have any more in the foreseeable future.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff2_0000b801_1"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy a rat.",Neutral,50,"Thanks, outlander. Here is your very own rat. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go.","Thanks, outlander. Here is your very own rat. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff2_00323460_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Come back anytime if you need another or want a replacement!","Come back anytime if you need another or want a replacement!","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff2_00323460_2"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy a rat.",Neutral,50,"Thanks, outlander. Here is your very own rat. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go.","Thanks, outlander. Here is your very own rat. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff2_00009f02_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Come back anytime if you need another or want a replacement!","Come back anytime if you need another or want a replacement!","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff2_00009f02_2"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy a rat.",Neutral,50,"Thanks, outlander. Here is your very own rat. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go.","Thanks, outlander. Here is your very own rat. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff2_00009f03_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Come back anytime if you need another or want a replacement!","Come back anytime if you need another or want a replacement!","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff2_00009f03_2"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy a rat.",Neutral,50,"I'd love to sell you one, outlander, but it doesn't look like you can afford it.","I'd love to sell you one, outlander, but it doesn't look like you can afford it.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff2_00323461_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Come back when you have the money and I'll have the creature packaged up and ready to go.","Come back when you have the money and I'll have the creature packaged up and ready to go.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff2_00323461_2"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy a scrib.",Neutral,50,"Good grief, outlander. Six of the best scribs ever to come out of my stable... dead! And you want me to sell you more?","Good grief, outlander. Six of the best scribs ever to come out of my stable... dead! And you want me to sell you more?","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff1_00009f05_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"No, sera! I just can't stand it! All that work I put into training them, and you treating them like grocery items? No! It just won't do!","No, sera! I just can't stand it! All that work I put into training them, and you treating them like grocery items? No! It just won't do!","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff1_00009f05_2"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy a scrib.",Neutral,50,"Sorry, outlander. I don't have any pet scribs in my stable, and I don't think I'll have any more in the foreseeable future.","Sorry, outlander. I don't have any pet scribs in my stable, and I don't think I'll have any more in the foreseeable future.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff1_00323463_1"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy a scrib.",Neutral,50,"Here is one of my finest pet scribs. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go. But take good care of him.","Here is one of my finest pet scribs. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go. But take good care of him.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff1_00323464_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"They're hard to train, you know. Seems a shame to eat the poor little fellows, after all the trouble I have in capturing them and training them. But..","They're hard to train, you know. Seems a shame to eat the poor little fellows, after all the trouble I have in capturing them and training them. But..","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff1_00323464_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"the customer is always right, and they're yours to do with as you wish.","the customer is always right, and they're yours to do with as you wish.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff1_00323464_3"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy a scrib.",Neutral,50,"Here is one of my finest pet scribs. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go. But take good care of him.","Here is one of my finest pet scribs. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go. But take good care of him.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff1_00009ef0_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"They're hard to train, you know. Seems a shame to eat the poor little fellows, after all the trouble I have in capturing them and training them. But..","They're hard to train, you know. Seems a shame to eat the poor little fellows, after all the trouble I have in capturing them and training them. But..","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff1_00009ef0_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"the customer is always right, and they're yours to do with as you wish.","the customer is always right, and they're yours to do with as you wish.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff1_00009ef0_3"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy a scrib.",Neutral,50,"Here is one of my finest pet scribs. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go. But take good care of him.","Here is one of my finest pet scribs. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go. But take good care of him.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff1_00f8e8c0_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"They're hard to train, you know. Seems a shame to eat the poor little fellows, after all the trouble I have in capturing them and training them. But..","They're hard to train, you know. Seems a shame to eat the poor little fellows, after all the trouble I have in capturing them and training them. But..","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff1_00f8e8c0_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"the customer is always right, and they're yours to do with as you wish.","the customer is always right, and they're yours to do with as you wish.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff1_00f8e8c0_3"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy a scrib.",Neutral,50,"Sorry, outlander. I don't have any more in my stable, and it takes a while to train them. Tell you what.","Sorry, outlander. I don't have any more in my stable, and it takes a while to train them. Tell you what.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff1_00323465_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Check by with me later, and I'll see what can be done.","Check by with me later, and I'll see what can be done.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff1_00323465_2"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy a scrib.",Neutral,50,"Sorry, outlander. I don't have any more in my stable, and it takes a while to train them. Tell you what.","Sorry, outlander. I don't have any more in my stable, and it takes a while to train them. Tell you what.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff1_00009f06_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Check by with me later, and I'll see what can be done.","Check by with me later, and I'll see what can be done.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff1_00009f06_2"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy a scrib.",Neutral,50,"Thanks, outlander. Here is your very own scrib. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go.","Thanks, outlander. Here is your very own scrib. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff1_00323466_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Come back anytime if you need another or want a replacement!","Come back anytime if you need another or want a replacement!","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff1_00323466_2"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy a scrib.",Neutral,50,"Thanks, outlander. Here is your very own scrib. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go.","Thanks, outlander. Here is your very own scrib. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff1_00009f07_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Come back anytime if you need another or want a replacement!","Come back anytime if you need another or want a replacement!","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff1_00009f07_2"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy a scrib.",Neutral,50,"Thanks, outlander. Here is your very own scrib. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go.","Thanks, outlander. Here is your very own scrib. He'll follow you around, right behind you, wherever you go.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff1_00009f08_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Come back anytime if you need another or want a replacement!","Come back anytime if you need another or want a replacement!","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff1_00009f08_2"
"","","Yes, I'd like to buy a scrib.",Neutral,50,"I'd love to sell you one, outlander, but it doesn't look like you can afford it.","I'd love to sell you one, outlander, but it doesn't look like you can afford it.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff1_00323467_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Come back when you have the money and I'll have the creature packaged up and ready to go.","Come back when you have the money and I'll have the creature packaged up and ready to go.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff1_00323467_2"
"","","No, thank you.",Neutral,50,"Well, come back anytime you think you need one. I sure could use the business.","Well, come back anytime you think you need one. I sure could use the business.","fbmwMSBadPets_1sellingSoff4_00323468_1"
