Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Services",Neutral,50,"You're standing the midst of the services Raven Rock has to offer. If you need anything else, you're better off checking at Fort Frostmoth.","You're standing the midst of the services Raven Rock has to offer. If you need anything else, you're better off checking at Fort Frostmoth.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Services_00322891_1"
