Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"There has been no word from the Captain. I fear the worst.","There has been no word from the Captain. I fear the worst.","fbmwBMWildHunt_GREETING_00f8afd6_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Captain Carius has returned. He's said very little about his ordeal, but we are all just glad he is back where he belongs. Fort Frostmoth will be stronger than ever.","Captain Carius has returned. He's said very little about his ordeal, but we are all just glad he is back where he belongs. Fort Frostmoth will be stronger than ever.","fbmwBMWildHunt_GREETING_00f8afd7_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"As I said, someone must find the Captain!","As I said, someone must find the Captain!","fbmwBMSmugglers_GREETING_00f8afa6_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"As I said, someone must find the Captain!","As I said, someone must find the Captain!","fbmwBMSmugglers_GREETING_00f8afa7_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Thank the gods you've returned! I see that Artoria has not returned with you. This day is filled with horrible news. There was a terrible battle. And Captain Carius...someone must find the Captain!","Thank the gods you've returned! I see that Artoria has not returned with you. This day is filled with horrible news. There was a terrible battle. And Captain Carius...someone must find the Captain!","fbmwBMSmugglers_GREETING_00f8afa9_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Thank the gods you've returned! There was a terrible battle. And Captain Carius...someone must find the Captain!","Thank the gods you've returned! There was a terrible battle. And Captain Carius...someone must find the Captain!","fbmwBMSmugglers_GREETING_00f8afaa_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Wait! Something here is amiss. The fort has been attacked while we were gone. We must find Captain Carius immediately!","Wait! Something here is amiss. The fort has been attacked while we were gone. We must find Captain Carius immediately!","fbmwBMSmugglers_GREETING_00f8afab_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"He wants to make a deal with you, does he?","He wants to make a deal with you, does he?","fbmwBMSmugglers_GREETING_00f8afac_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Yes? Would you like to continue to travel together? I imagine it would be best with the task at hand. Captain Carius wishes for us to work together.","Yes? Would you like to continue to travel together? I imagine it would be best with the task at hand. Captain Carius wishes for us to work together.","fbmwBMSmugglers_GREETING_00f8afad_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I understand you have chosen to work with my compatriot, Gaea Artoria. There is no finer warrior in Fort Frostmoth, save perhaps Captain Carius. I wish you both the best of luck.","I understand you have chosen to work with my compatriot, Gaea Artoria. There is no finer warrior in Fort Frostmoth, save perhaps Captain Carius. I wish you both the best of luck.","fbmwBMSmugglers_GREETING_00f8afae_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Captain Carius mentioned that you might come to speak with me. How may I assist you?","Captain Carius mentioned that you might come to speak with me. How may I assist you?","fbmwBMSmugglers_GREETING_00f8afaf_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"As I said, someone must find the Captain!","As I said, someone must find the Captain!","fbmwBMCariusGone_GREETING_00f8afd2_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"From what Artoria has told us, the course is clear. You must travel to the Nord village and see what they know about the attack.","From what Artoria has told us, the course is clear. You must travel to the Nord village and see what they know about the attack.","fbmwBMCariusGone_GREETING_00f8afd3_1"
"","","Travel Together",Neutral,50,"It is best if I remain here.","It is best if I remain here.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1travelStogether_00030584_1"
"","","Travel Together",Neutral,50,"We should continue to travel together, should we not?","We should continue to travel together, should we not?","fbmwBMSmugglers_1travelStogether_00030583_1"
"","","Weapons being smuggled",Neutral,50,"That task is complete. We have other matters at hand.","That task is complete. We have other matters at hand.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1weaponsSbeingSsmuggled_00f8aff3_1"
"","","Weapons being smuggled",Neutral,50,"The smugglers are dead, so the smuggling ring is effectively broken. Not the way I would have done it, perhaps, but effective nonetheless. Let us return to the fort.","The smugglers are dead, so the smuggling ring is effectively broken. Not the way I would have done it, perhaps, but effective nonetheless. Let us return to the fort.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1weaponsSbeingSsmuggled_00f8aff4_1"
"","","Weapons being smuggled",Neutral,50,"You have made your decision. I will let you report these findings to Carius. I hope you have made the correct decision.","You have made your decision. I will let you report these findings to Carius. I hope you have made the correct decision.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1weaponsSbeingSsmuggled_00f8aff5_1"
"","","Weapons being smuggled",Neutral,50,"I believe we have enough information to break up this ring. Let us finish.","I believe we have enough information to break up this ring. Let us finish.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1weaponsSbeingSsmuggled_00f8aff6_1"
"","","Weapons being smuggled",Neutral,50,"You've chosen to work with Gaea Artoria, have you not? She'll be a more than able companion for you. You should speak with her about this matter.","You've chosen to work with Gaea Artoria, have you not? She'll be a more than able companion for you. You should speak with her about this matter.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1weaponsSbeingSsmuggled_00f8aff7_1"
"","","Weapons being smuggled",Neutral,50,"I suggest we speak with some of the soldiers here at the fort. A motley bunch, to be sure, but some of them are fair soldiers. I've developed quite a rapport with a few, in fact. Why don't we begin by speaking with Zeno Faustus. He's an interesting character.","I suggest we speak with some of the soldiers here at the fort. A motley bunch, to be sure, but some of them are fair soldiers. I've developed quite a rapport with a few, in fact. Why don't we begin by speaking with Zeno Faustus. He's an interesting character.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1weaponsSbeingSsmuggled_00f8aff8_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"We'll find him in the Armory.","We'll find him in the Armory.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1weaponsSbeingSsmuggled_00f8aff8_2"
"","","Weapons being smuggled",Neutral,50,"Well, if you choose to work with me, I'm certain I can be of some assistance in this matter.","Well, if you choose to work with me, I'm certain I can be of some assistance in this matter.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1weaponsSbeingSsmuggled_00f8aff9_1"
"","","Find the Captain",Neutral,50,"There is still no word from the Captain. He is now presumed dead. This is a great loss to all of us at Fort Frostmoth, and a loss to the Legion as a whole.","There is still no word from the Captain. He is now presumed dead. This is a great loss to all of us at Fort Frostmoth, and a loss to the Legion as a whole.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1findStheSCaptain_00f8b02d_1"
"","","Find the Captain",Neutral,50,"Thank the gods that he has returned.","Thank the gods that he has returned.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1findStheSCaptain_00f8b02e_1"
"","","Find the Captain",Neutral,50,"He must be found, and it is possible that these Skaal know something of the disappearance, though they claim they do not. Learn what you can from them. They do not seem to be threatening, but I believe they know more than they let on.","He must be found, and it is possible that these Skaal know something of the disappearance, though they claim they do not. Learn what you can from them. They do not seem to be threatening, but I believe they know more than they let on.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1findStheSCaptain_00f8b02f_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Stay with them until you have learned more. I will take care of the soldiers here at the fort. I am counting on you. Good luck.","Stay with them until you have learned more. I will take care of the soldiers here at the fort. I am counting on you. Good luck.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1findStheSCaptain_00f8b02f_2"
"","","Find the Captain",Neutral,50,"The Skaal say they know nothing of the attack? Interesting. I have no doubt that they were not the instigators of this horror, but I do believe they know more than they have let on to you. For now, return to them.","The Skaal say they know nothing of the attack? Interesting. I have no doubt that they were not the instigators of this horror, but I do believe they know more than they have let on to you. For now, return to them.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1findStheSCaptain_00f8b030_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Live among them for a time, and see what you might learn. Take care with them. They live by a strict code, and you will be expected to follow it while you are with them.","Live among them for a time, and see what you might learn. Take care with them. They live by a strict code, and you will be expected to follow it while you are with them.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1findStheSCaptain_00f8b030_2"
"","","Find the Captain",Neutral,50,"You must find Carius. And the Nord village would be a good place to begin looking.","You must find Carius. And the Nord village would be a good place to begin looking.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1findStheSCaptain_00f8b031_1"
"","","Find the Captain",Neutral,50,"There was a terrible battle. We were caught completely by surprise. And in the aftermath we realized that Captain Carius was missing. I searched thoroughly, and there was no sign of his body, so I do not believe he is dead. And these wolf creatures...","There was a terrible battle. We were caught completely by surprise. And in the aftermath we realized that Captain Carius was missing. I searched thoroughly, and there was no sign of his body, so I do not believe he is dead. And these wolf creatures...","fbmwBMSmugglers_1findStheSCaptain_00f8b032_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"They were horrible and fierce. You must find him. There is a Nord village on the north end of this island. They may know something about what has occured.","They were horrible and fierce. You must find him. There is a Nord village on the north end of this island. They may know something about what has occured.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1findStheSCaptain_00f8b032_2"
"","","Fort Frostmoth",Neutral,50,"It is a difficult assignment, that is certain. However, some of us make the best of it.","It is a difficult assignment, that is certain. However, some of us make the best of it.","MorroDefaultQuest_1FortSFrostmoth_0032156b_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"It will be better one day, under the leadership of Captain Carius.","It will be better one day, under the leadership of Captain Carius.","MorroDefaultQuest_1FortSFrostmoth_0032156b_2"
"","","Wolf Creatures",Neutral,50,"I don't know exactly what to call them. Of course, I've heard stories about werewolves...men who turn into beasts when the night falls.","I don't know exactly what to call them. Of course, I've heard stories about werewolves...men who turn into beasts when the night falls.","MorroDefaultQuest_1wolfScreatures_00321578_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But I've never heard of them being seen on this island. And I've certainly never heard of so many of them working in concert.","But I've never heard of them being seen on this island. And I've certainly never heard of so many of them working in concert.","MorroDefaultQuest_1wolfScreatures_00321578_2"
"","","Saenus Lusius",Neutral,50,"I am Saenus Lusius. What may I do for you?","I am Saenus Lusius. What may I do for you?","MorroDefaultQuest_1SaenusSLusius_00321a7b_1"
"","","Gaea Artoria",Neutral,50,"She was one of the finest warriors the Legion has ever known. She will be missed.","She was one of the finest warriors the Legion has ever known. She will be missed.","MorroDefaultQuest_1GaeaSArtoria_00321d07_1"
"","","Gaea Artoria",Neutral,50,"A fine warrior, second only to the Captain himself. She'll likely be off on errands for Captain Carius now.","A fine warrior, second only to the Captain himself. She'll likely be off on errands for Captain Carius now.","MorroDefaultQuest_1GaeaSArtoria_00321d08_1"
"","","Gaea Artoria",Neutral,50,"A fine warrior, second only to the Captain himself. She would be an excellent traveling companion.","A fine warrior, second only to the Captain himself. She would be an excellent traveling companion.","MorroDefaultQuest_1GaeaSArtoria_00321d09_1"
"","","Nord village",Neutral,50,"Go there and find out what you can about the Captain's disappearance. It is on the northeastern tip of the island.","Go there and find out what you can about the Captain's disappearance. It is on the northeastern tip of the island.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1NordSvillage_00f8b043_1"
"","","Nord village",Neutral,50,"It is on the northeastern tip of Solstheim. These Skaal are nature-worshippers, and they seem to have a special commune with the creatures of this island. If anyone knows what attacked the fort, it will be these Nords.","It is on the northeastern tip of Solstheim. These Skaal are nature-worshippers, and they seem to have a special commune with the creatures of this island. If anyone knows what attacked the fort, it will be these Nords.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1NordSvillage_00f8b044_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I will mark their location on your map. I would like you to earn their trust and find out what you can. You may have to remain with them for many days, but I believe you are up to the task.","I will mark their location on your map. I would like you to earn their trust and find out what you can. You may have to remain with them for many days, but I believe you are up to the task.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1NordSvillage_00f8b044_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Here, take this--it was found in one of their tombs. Perhaps they will take it as a sign of good faith.","Here, take this--it was found in one of their tombs. Perhaps they will take it as a sign of good faith.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1NordSvillage_00f8b044_3"
"","","Make a deal",Neutral,50,"Interesting. Well, I suppose you could let him go. I know Spurius, and while he wasn't the best soldier, he wasn't the worst, either.","Interesting. Well, I suppose you could let him go. I know Spurius, and while he wasn't the best soldier, he wasn't the worst, either.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1makeSaSdeal_00f8b04c_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And I know he has a family to feed back home. Still, he has stolen from the Legion, and his crimes are punishable by death. I'm afraid the decision is yours, my friend.","And I know he has a family to feed back home. Still, he has stolen from the Legion, and his crimes are punishable by death. I'm afraid the decision is yours, my friend.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1makeSaSdeal_00f8b04c_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Whatever you decide, I will support it.","Whatever you decide, I will support it.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1makeSaSdeal_00f8b04c_3"
"","","Assist You",Neutral,50,"Ah yes, this smuggling ring. Captain Carius mentioned something about that. I would be glad to help. Though I'm admittedly not the most handy with my blade, I believe I can help guide you through this conundrum.","Ah yes, this smuggling ring. Captain Carius mentioned something about that. I would be glad to help. Though I'm admittedly not the most handy with my blade, I believe I can help guide you through this conundrum.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1assistSyou_00aa3cdf_1"
"","","Skaal",Neutral,50,"They are a mysterious bunch, but to be truthful, I know very little about them.","They are a mysterious bunch, but to be truthful, I know very little about them.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Skaal_00322e23_1"
"","","Wait here.",Neutral,50,"If you insist.","If you insist.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1travelStogether2_0032326b_1"
"","","Wait here.",Neutral,50,"If you insist.","If you insist.","MorroDefaultQuest_1travelStogether2_0032325b_1"
"","","Follow me.",Neutral,50,"Excellent.","Excellent.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1travelStogether1_00323283_1"
"","","I am not sure with whom I will work.",Neutral,50,"As you wish. If you change your mind, please let me know.","As you wish. If you change your mind, please let me know.","fbmwBMSmugglers_1assistSyou2_0032355e_1"
"","","I would like you to work with me.",Neutral,50,"Excellent. Gaea Artoria will have to perform the other tasks that Captain Carius had for me today, but no matter. Let us find these scoundrels!","Excellent. Gaea Artoria will have to perform the other tasks that Captain Carius had for me today, but no matter. Let us find these scoundrels!","fbmwBMSmugglers_1assistSyou1_0032356f_1"
