Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Hello, Outlander. Is it snowing again? Feels like it, from the way my joints ache.","Hello, Outlander. Is it snowing again? Feels like it, from the way my joints ache.","fbmwCO7_GREETING_00f8e515_1"
"","","GREETING",Sad,60,"Can't.... can't keep swinging... too tired. Just, just fight me, okay? Come on...","Can't.... can't keep swinging... too tired. Just, just fight me, okay? Come on...","fbmwCO7_GREETING_00f8e516_1"
"","","GREETING",Anger,80,"I suppose they've sent you to deal with me, haven't they? Well, then - let's get this over with! You're not some kind of coward, are you?","I suppose they've sent you to deal with me, haven't they? Well, then - let's get this over with! You're not some kind of coward, are you?","fbmwCO7_GREETING_00f8e517_1"
"","","",Anger,80,"Come on and fight me! If I'm going to die, then I'm going out with a bang!","Come on and fight me! If I'm going to die, then I'm going out with a bang!","fbmwCO7_GREETING_00f8e517_2"
"","","Hire Guards",Neutral,50,"I'm an old man. I'd be of no use to you.","I'm an old man. I'd be of no use to you.","fbmwCO11_1hireSguards_00027775_1"
"","","No, I wont",Neutral,50,"You're right, you're right.... I know you're right. I'm sorry. I'll stop, and I'll try to look on the bright side from now on.","You're right, you're right.... I know you're right. I'm sorry. I'll stop, and I'll try to look on the bright side from now on.","fbmwCO7_1fightSme5_003235cb_1"
"","","No, I wont",Neutral,50,"You won't, eh? Well, maybe I won't give you a choice!","You won't, eh? Well, maybe I won't give you a choice!","fbmwCO7_1fightSme5_003235cc_1"
"","","This isn't your only option.",Neutral,50,"I suppose you're going to try and tell me that my family is more important, right?","I suppose you're going to try and tell me that my family is more important, right?","fbmwCO7_1fightSme4_003235cd_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Look, I don't want things to end like this, but I don't want Dralora to have to see me wasting away in front of her.","Look, I don't want things to end like this, but I don't want Dralora to have to see me wasting away in front of her.","fbmwCO7_1fightSme4_003235cd_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I don't want her to have to take care of me because I can't do it myself. Just kill me, won't you?  Put an end to this!","I don't want her to have to take care of me because I can't do it myself. Just kill me, won't you?  Put an end to this!","fbmwCO7_1fightSme4_003235cd_3"
"","","What about your wife?",Neutral,50,"My wife? She's..... she's dead? Then I really have nothing to live for. Let's end this, outlander, right now!","My wife? She's..... she's dead? Then I really have nothing to live for. Let's end this, outlander, right now!","fbmwCO7_1fightSme3_003235ce_1"
"","","What about your wife?",Neutral,50,"My wife will be better off without me, whether she knows it or not. What, you think you know better?","My wife will be better off without me, whether she knows it or not. What, you think you know better?","fbmwCO7_1fightSme3_003235cf_1"
"","","Why would you want to die?",Neutral,50,"Why? Look at me. I'm an old man. My health is failing, I'm of no use in the mines, and I'm a burden to my family. I don't want to waste away in bed;","Why? Look at me. I'm an old man. My health is failing, I'm of no use in the mines, and I'm a burden to my family. I don't want to waste away in bed;","fbmwCO7_1fightSme2_003235d0_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"don't you see? That's no way for a man to die.","don't you see? That's no way for a man to die.","fbmwCO7_1fightSme2_003235d0_2"
"","","Very well, I'll do as you ask.",Neutral,50,"Good, good. Make it quick, will you? As flashy as I wanted this to be, I wasn't looking for lots of pain.","Good, good. Make it quick, will you? As flashy as I wanted this to be, I wasn't looking for lots of pain.","fbmwCO7_1fightSme1_003235d1_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I'll at least try and put up a fight, to make you look good. You shouldn't be blamed for this.","I'll at least try and put up a fight, to make you look good. You shouldn't be blamed for this.","fbmwCO7_1fightSme1_003235d1_2"
"","","Fight me",Sad,60,"I'm.... I'm too tired. Just can't fight anymore...  Kill me, won't you? Just tell them you had no choice, that you had to defend yourself.","I'm.... I'm too tired. Just can't fight anymore...  Kill me, won't you? Just tell them you had no choice, that you had to defend yourself.","fbmwCO7_1fightSme6_0001013e_1"
"","","",Sad,60,"I just don't want to live like this anymore.","I just don't want to live like this anymore.","fbmwCO7_1fightSme6_0001013e_2"
