Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Greetings. I understand you were sent to help with the trouble we're having with bandits in Suran.","Greetings. I understand you were sent to help with the trouble we're having with bandits in Suran.","fbmwFGSuranBandits_GREETING_0000ce6e_1"
"","","Vassir Didanat Mine",Neutral,50,"If you know where the mine is, speak with Dram Bero. Or if you do not wish to deal with him, speak with Velanda Omani. They are known to keep their word and both would be interested in this mine.","If you know where the mine is, speak with Dram Bero. Or if you do not wish to deal with him, speak with Velanda Omani. They are known to keep their word and both would be interested in this mine.","MorroDefaultQuest_1VassirSDidanatSMine_0032086c_1"
"","","Bandits in Suran",Neutral,50,"You have brought justice to Daldur Sarys and his bandits. House Hlaalu thanks you. Here is the bounty money we agreed on.","You have brought justice to Daldur Sarys and his bandits. House Hlaalu thanks you. Here is the bounty money we agreed on.","fbmwFGSuranBandits_1banditsSinSSuran_00320e51_1"
"","","Bandits in Suran",Neutral,50,"The bandits have been attacking from Saturan which is northeast of here, just over the mountains. Kill Daldur Sarys and the raids will end.","The bandits have been attacking from Saturan which is northeast of here, just over the mountains. Kill Daldur Sarys and the raids will end.","fbmwFGSuranBandits_1banditsSinSSuran_0002d8d5_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"When you have killed him, report directly to me, and I will give you 1,000 gold in bounty.","When you have killed him, report directly to me, and I will give you 1,000 gold in bounty.","fbmwFGSuranBandits_1banditsSinSSuran_0002d8d5_2"
"","","Inanius egg mine",Neutral,50,"I wish you had told me of this sooner. I could have made you a better offer.","I wish you had told me of this sooner. I could have made you a better offer.","fbmwHHEggMine_1InaniusSeggSmine_00004b5b_1"
"","","Inanius egg mine",Neutral,50,"Yes, thank you for reminding me. You killed the kwama queen after you gave me your word. I will make sure the rest of House Hlaalu hears about this.","Yes, thank you for reminding me. You killed the kwama queen after you gave me your word. I will make sure the rest of House Hlaalu hears about this.","fbmwHHEggMine_1InaniusSeggSmine_00004b5c_1"
"","","Inanius egg mine",Neutral,50,"If Nileno Dorvayn makes a better offer, come see me first.","If Nileno Dorvayn makes a better offer, come see me first.","fbmwHHEggMine_1InaniusSeggSmine_00004b5d_1"
"","","Inanius egg mine",Neutral,50,"Yes, that is one of my egg mines. Why do you ask?","Yes, that is one of my egg mines. Why do you ask?","fbmwHHEggMine_1InaniusSeggSmine_00004b5e_1"
"","","Inanius egg mine",Neutral,50,"Ser Avon Oran's egg mine? Just go south around those hills to the east. Then follow the hills back north from the river and you can't miss it.","Ser Avon Oran's egg mine? Just go south around those hills to the east. Then follow the hills back north from the river and you can't miss it.","fbmwHHEggMine_1InaniusSeggSmine_00320e67_1"
"","","I accept your offer.",Neutral,50,"Good. Good. Here are the drakes. Stay out of the egg mine and tell Nileno she lost this time.","Good. Good. Here are the drakes. Stay out of the egg mine and tell Nileno she lost this time.","fbmwHHEggMine_1InaniusSeggSmine1_003231a0_1"
"","","No, I gave my word.",Neutral,50,"Perhaps you misjudged how much the mine is worth to me. 1000 drakes is my final offer.","Perhaps you misjudged how much the mine is worth to me. 1000 drakes is my final offer.","fbmwHHEggMine_1InaniusSeggSmine2_003231a1_1"
"","","Nileno asked me to kill the Queen.",Neutral,50,"So Nileno wants to disrupt my business. Suppose I paid you 1000 drakes to leave the egg mine alone?","So Nileno wants to disrupt my business. Suppose I paid you 1000 drakes to leave the egg mine alone?","fbmwHHEggMine_1InaniusSeggSmine3_003231a2_1"
"","","Nothing, nevermind.",Neutral,50,"Well then, what can I do for you?","Well then, what can I do for you?","fbmwHHEggMine_1InaniusSeggSmine4_003231a3_1"
