Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Yes, we are going together to Ald Daedroth, where we will see if you have made it safe for the Ahemmusa.","Yes, we are going together to Ald Daedroth, where we will see if you have made it safe for the Ahemmusa.","fbmwMQ11a_GREETING_00009347_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I will accompany you until we stand before the great statue, where we will speak further.","I will accompany you until we stand before the great statue, where we will speak further.","fbmwMQ11a_GREETING_00009347_2"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"The Ahemmusa owe you great thanks, Nerevarine, and wish you well.","The Ahemmusa owe you great thanks, Nerevarine, and wish you well.","fbmwMQ11a_GREETING_000104ba_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I said I would accompany you to see if you had made Ald Daedroth safe for the Ahemmusa. You have fulfilled my conditions.","I said I would accompany you to see if you had made Ald Daedroth safe for the Ahemmusa. You have fulfilled my conditions.","fbmwMQ11a_GREETING_000104bb_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Thank you. The Ahemmusa shall be saved. And if you wish, now I shall name you Nerevarine of the Ahemmusa.","Thank you. The Ahemmusa shall be saved. And if you wish, now I shall name you Nerevarine of the Ahemmusa.","fbmwMQ11a_GREETING_000104bb_2"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Yes. Are you ready now for me to accompany you to Ald Daedroth?","Yes. Are you ready now for me to accompany you to Ald Daedroth?","fbmwMQ11a_GREETING_000104bc_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Have you made a safe place for the Ahemmusa? Or is there something else you want?","Have you made a safe place for the Ahemmusa? Or is there something else you want?","fbmwMQ11a_GREETING_000104bd_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Have you given courtesy first to my gulakhans? No? Have you no manners? Go. Do what you should before I will speak with you.","Have you given courtesy first to my gulakhans? No? Have you no manners? Go. Do what you should before I will speak with you.","fbmwMQ11a_GREETING_000104be_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"So you have recovered the Amulet of Ashamanu. Urshamusa Rapli told me of her vision. And now you are come. You have done the tribe a great service.","So you have recovered the Amulet of Ashamanu. Urshamusa Rapli told me of her vision. And now you are come. You have done the tribe a great service.","fbmwMQ11a_GREETING_000104bf_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But perhaps you may do us a greater service yet","But perhaps you may do us a greater service yet","fbmwMQ11a_GREETING_000104bf_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I have heard of an outlander who seeks to fulfill the Nerevarine prophecies, and to be named Nerevarine. Are you that outlander?","I have heard of an outlander who seeks to fulfill the Nerevarine prophecies, and to be named Nerevarine. Are you that outlander?","fbmwMQ11a_GREETING_000104bf_3"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"So you have recovered the Amulet of Ashamanu. Urshamusa Rapli told me of her vision. And now you are come. You have done the tribe a great service.","So you have recovered the Amulet of Ashamanu. Urshamusa Rapli told me of her vision. And now you are come. You have done the tribe a great service.","fbmwMQ11a_GREETING_000104c0_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But perhaps you may do us a greater service yet.","But perhaps you may do us a greater service yet.","fbmwMQ11a_GREETING_000104c0_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I have heard of an outlander who seeks to fulfill the Nerevarine prophecies, and to be named Nerevarine. Are you that outlander?","I have heard of an outlander who seeks to fulfill the Nerevarine prophecies, and to be named Nerevarine. Are you that outlander?","fbmwMQ11a_GREETING_000104c0_3"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I have heard of an outlander who seeks to fulfill the Nerevarine prophecies, and to be named Nerevarine. Are you that outlander?","I have heard of an outlander who seeks to fulfill the Nerevarine prophecies, and to be named Nerevarine. Are you that outlander?","fbmwMQ11a_GREETING_000104c1_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Why do you trouble us, outlander? We have nothing worth taking. Why don't you leave us alone?","Why do you trouble us, outlander? We have nothing worth taking. Why don't you leave us alone?","fbmwMQ11a_GREETING_000104c2_1"
"","","Yes, please accompany me there.",Neutral,50,"Very well. Now I will accompany you to the Daedric shrine on Ald Daedroth.","Very well. Now I will accompany you to the Daedric shrine on Ald Daedroth.","fbmwMQ11a_fbmwMQ11aFollowMeFirst_0001c662_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And when you have brought me to the old sanctuary beneath the ruins, and I may see the great statue of Sheogorath in the inner shrine,","And when you have brought me to the old sanctuary beneath the ruins, and I may see the great statue of Sheogorath in the inner shrine,","fbmwMQ11a_fbmwMQ11aFollowMeFirst_0001c662_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"then I will surely know that you have made Ald Daedroth safe for the Ahemmusa, and I will name you Ahemmusa Nerevarine.","then I will surely know that you have made Ald Daedroth safe for the Ahemmusa, and I will name you Ahemmusa Nerevarine.","fbmwMQ11a_fbmwMQ11aFollowMeFirst_0001c662_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Go ahead, and we will speak further before the great statue.","Go ahead, and we will speak further before the great statue.","fbmwMQ11a_fbmwMQ11aFollowMeFirst_0001c662_4"
"","","Not yet.",Neutral,50,"Very well, then. I will wait here for now. When you are ready, come to me, and I will accompany you to Ald Daedroth to see if it is safe.","Very well, then. I will wait here for now. When you are ready, come to me, and I will accompany you to Ald Daedroth to see if it is safe.","fbmwMQ11a_fbmwMQ11aWaitFirst_0001c664_1"
"","","Yes, please accompany me there.",Neutral,50,"Very well. I will accompany you to Ald Daedroth, and we will speak further when we stand before the great statue.","Very well. I will accompany you to Ald Daedroth, and we will speak further when we stand before the great statue.","fbmwMQ11a_fbmwMQ11aFollowIP_0001c666_1"
"","","Please wait for me here.",Neutral,50,"Very well, then. I will wait here for now.","Very well, then. I will wait here for now.","fbmwMQ11a_fbmwMQ11aWaitIP_0001c668_1"
"","","Who is the Ahemmusa's ashkan?",Neutral,50,"The Ahemmusa have no ashkhan. I am the wise woman of the Ahemmusa, and I speak for the tribe.","The Ahemmusa have no ashkhan. I am the wise woman of the Ahemmusa, and I speak for the tribe.","fbmwMQ11a_fbmwMQ11aaskforashkan_00023c7f_1"
"","","I want you to name me Nerevarine.",Neutral,50,"I will examine your proofs, and you will tell me your story. And if I am satisfied, according to custom, and with reference to the prophecies, I will name you Ahemmusa Nerevarine.","I will examine your proofs, and you will tell me your story. And if I am satisfied, according to custom, and with reference to the prophecies, I will name you Ahemmusa Nerevarine.","fbmwMQ11a_fbmwMQ11awishtobe_00023c7e_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But there will be a price. The Ahemmusa need a safe place, and you will provide that safe place.","But there will be a price. The Ahemmusa need a safe place, and you will provide that safe place.","fbmwMQ11a_fbmwMQ11awishtobe_00023c7e_2"
"","","Name You Nerevarine",Neutral,50,"I have named you Ahemmusa Nerevarine, War Leader of the Ahemmusa, and Protector of the People. You have saved the Ahemmusa. Now we hope that you shall also fufill the other Nerevarine prophecies.","I have named you Ahemmusa Nerevarine, War Leader of the Ahemmusa, and Protector of the People. You have saved the Ahemmusa. Now we hope that you shall also fufill the other Nerevarine prophecies.","fbmwMQ11a_1nameSyouSNerevarine_00022dcc_1"
"","","Name You Nerevarine",Neutral,50,"I have named you Ahemmusa Nerevarine, War Leader of the Ahemmusa, and Protector of the People. You have saved the Ahemmusa. Now we hope that you shall also fufill the other Nerevarine prophecies.","I have named you Ahemmusa Nerevarine, War Leader of the Ahemmusa, and Protector of the People. You have saved the Ahemmusa. Now we hope that you shall also fufill the other Nerevarine prophecies.","fbmwMQ11a_1nameSyouSNerevarine_00022dcb_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I can stay only briefly. Soon I must return to Ahemmusa camp and make preparations to relocate here.","I can stay only briefly. Soon I must return to Ahemmusa camp and make preparations to relocate here.","fbmwMQ11a_1nameSyouSNerevarine_00022dcb_2"
"","","Name You Nerevarine",Neutral,50,"You have made this place safe for the Ahemmusa. And so I name you Ahemmusa Nerevarine, War Leader of the Ahemmusa, and Protector of the People.","You have made this place safe for the Ahemmusa. And so I name you Ahemmusa Nerevarine, War Leader of the Ahemmusa, and Protector of the People.","fbmwMQ11a_1nameSyouSNerevarine_00022dca_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I also give you the Madstone of the Ahemmusa, which shall be a sign to all Dunmer, that you are the Nerevarine, and that the Ahemmusa shall follow you in all thing, even unto death, until the Enemy is defeated, or until you are dead.","I also give you the Madstone of the Ahemmusa, which shall be a sign to all Dunmer, that you are the Nerevarine, and that the Ahemmusa shall follow you in all thing, even unto death, until the Enemy is defeated, or until you are dead.","fbmwMQ11a_1nameSyouSNerevarine_00022dca_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Now, I can stay only briefly. Soon I must return to Ahemmusa camp and make preparations to relocate here.","Now, I can stay only briefly. Soon I must return to Ahemmusa camp and make preparations to relocate here.","fbmwMQ11a_1nameSyouSNerevarine_00022dca_3"
"","","Arrange a meeting",Neutral,50,"No, I have sent my apprentice. That is all I will do for your Argonian.","No, I have sent my apprentice. That is all I will do for your Argonian.","fbmwMGWiseWoman_1arrangeSaSmeeting_00023522_1"
"","","Arrange a meeting",Neutral,50,"I will send my apprentice, Minabibi, to speak with this Argonian.","I will send my apprentice, Minabibi, to speak with this Argonian.","fbmwMGWiseWoman_1arrangeSaSmeeting_00023521_1"
"","","Arrange a meeting",Neutral,50,"I know the spirit of Kanit Ashurnisammis is at rest. Before I send my apprentice to this Skink, I will ask a question.","I know the spirit of Kanit Ashurnisammis is at rest. Before I send my apprentice to this Skink, I will ask a question.","fbmwMGWiseWoman_1arrangeSaSmeeting_00023520_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Did you pacify the spirit, or did Minabibi pacify the spirit?","Did you pacify the spirit, or did Minabibi pacify the spirit?","fbmwMGWiseWoman_1arrangeSaSmeeting_00023520_2"
"","","Arrange a meeting",Neutral,50,"I will not meet with this Argonian. I might send my apprentice, Minabibi, for it is time she saw how you foreigners live and left her childish notions behind her.","I will not meet with this Argonian. I might send my apprentice, Minabibi, for it is time she saw how you foreigners live and left her childish notions behind her.","fbmwMGWiseWoman_1arrangeSaSmeeting_0002351f_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"She is in the Favel Tomb.","She is in the Favel Tomb.","fbmwMGWiseWoman_1arrangeSaSmeeting_0002351f_2"
"","","Childish Notions",Neutral,50,"Minabibi does not respect our ways. She is like a sister to every foreigner who visits our camp. I fear she will not make a good wise woman.","Minabibi does not respect our ways. She is like a sister to every foreigner who visits our camp. I fear she will not make a good wise woman.","fbmwMGWiseWoman_1childishSnotions_00aa3c6c_1"
"","","Hlireni Indavel",Neutral,50,"She is the priestess of Ald Daedroth. But now you have shown that she and her cultists are no threat to us.","She is the priestess of Ald Daedroth. But now you have shown that she and her cultists are no threat to us.","MorroDefaultQuest_1HlireniSIndavel_00aa3c70_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Now the Ahemmusa and the followers of Hlireni Indavel will learn to live in peace.","Now the Ahemmusa and the followers of Hlireni Indavel will learn to live in peace.","MorroDefaultQuest_1HlireniSIndavel_00aa3c70_2"
"","","Hlireni Indavel",Neutral,50,"She is no longer a concern.","She is no longer a concern.","MorroDefaultQuest_1HlireniSIndavel_00aa3c71_1"
"","","Hlireni Indavel",Neutral,50,"All I know is that she is a Dunmer, and she and her followers have defied the Temple's ban against the worship of the Four Corners of the House of Troubles, the four Daedra Lords, Mehrunes Dagon, Molag Bal, Malacath, and Sheogorath..","All I know is that she is a Dunmer, and she and her followers have defied the Temple's ban against the worship of the Four Corners of the House of Troubles, the four Daedra Lords, Mehrunes Dagon, Molag Bal, Malacath, and Sheogorath..","MorroDefaultQuest_1HlireniSIndavel_00aa3c72_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Since so many Ordinators are busy fighting the hosts of Dagoth Ur at Ghostgate, many of the abandoned Daedric sites are once again inhabited.","Since so many Ordinators are busy fighting the hosts of Dagoth Ur at Ghostgate, many of the abandoned Daedric sites are once again inhabited.","MorroDefaultQuest_1HlireniSIndavel_00aa3c72_2"
"","","Cross the Water",Neutral,50,"You know that I can walk on water. You have seen for yourself.","You know that I can walk on water. You have seen for yourself.","fbmwMQ11a_1crossStheSwater_00023c6d_1"
"","","Cross the Water",Neutral,50,"I have not the arts of war, but I am a wise woman, and not without power. I can walk upon the water...","I have not the arts of war, but I am a wise woman, and not without power. I can walk upon the water...","fbmwMQ11a_1crossStheSwater_00320f2e_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"perhaps not so fast as a great witch-warrior, but fast enough.","perhaps not so fast as a great witch-warrior, but fast enough.","fbmwMQ11a_1crossStheSwater_00320f2e_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And while we are on our water journey, if you are hero, you will protect me from slaughterfish and other creatures.","And while we are on our water journey, if you are hero, you will protect me from slaughterfish and other creatures.","fbmwMQ11a_1crossStheSwater_00320f2e_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And if you are not, I shall perish, and you shall not be named Nerevarine.","And if you are not, I shall perish, and you shall not be named Nerevarine.","fbmwMQ11a_1crossStheSwater_00320f2e_4"
"","","Daedric Sites",Neutral,50,"When the Velothi first came to Morrowind, they worshipped our most terrible ancestors, the Daedra Lords.","When the Velothi first came to Morrowind, they worshipped our most terrible ancestors, the Daedra Lords.","MorroDefaultQuest_1DaedricSsites_00aa3c6e_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Legends say the Daedra Lords themselves built these great shrines, because mortals could not build anything grand enough to suit them.","Legends say the Daedra Lords themselves built these great shrines, because mortals could not build anything grand enough to suit them.","MorroDefaultQuest_1DaedricSsites_00aa3c6e_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"When the Tribunal claimed to have tamed the Daedra Lords, they forbid the worship of the Bad Daedra, Malacath, Mehrunes Dagon, Molag Bal, and Sheogorath.","When the Tribunal claimed to have tamed the Daedra Lords, they forbid the worship of the Bad Daedra, Malacath, Mehrunes Dagon, Molag Bal, and Sheogorath.","MorroDefaultQuest_1DaedricSsites_00aa3c6e_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"For thousands of years, the Temple kept these ancient shrines closed, but in recent years, as Dagoth Ur grew stronger and the Temple weaker, there were fewer and fewer priest-soldiers, and they were all sent to Ghostgate.","For thousands of years, the Temple kept these ancient shrines closed, but in recent years, as Dagoth Ur grew stronger and the Temple weaker, there were fewer and fewer priest-soldiers, and they were all sent to Ghostgate.","MorroDefaultQuest_1DaedricSsites_00aa3c6e_4"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Now the Temple can't keep the witches and warlocks of the Daedra cults from bringing the old shrines back to life.","Now the Temple can't keep the witches and warlocks of the Daedra cults from bringing the old shrines back to life.","MorroDefaultQuest_1DaedricSsites_00aa3c6e_5"
"","","Accompany You",Neutral,50,"Yes. I did accompany you to Ald Daedroth, and I did name you Ahemmusa Nerevarine. Now I shall remain here and await the arrival of the tribe.","Yes. I did accompany you to Ald Daedroth, and I did name you Ahemmusa Nerevarine. Now I shall remain here and await the arrival of the tribe.","fbmwMQ11a_1accompanySyou_00aabec6_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"It will take some time to make preparations, and there is much to be done here.","It will take some time to make preparations, and there is much to be done here.","fbmwMQ11a_1accompanySyou_00aabec6_2"
"","","Accompany You",Neutral,50,"I have accompanied you to the place made safe for the Ahemmusa. And so, if you wish, I shall name you Nerevarine.","I have accompanied you to the place made safe for the Ahemmusa. And so, if you wish, I shall name you Nerevarine.","fbmwMQ11a_1accompanySyou_00aabec7_1"
"","","Accompany You",Neutral,50,"Are you ready now for me to accompany you to Ald Daedroth?","Are you ready now for me to accompany you to Ald Daedroth?","fbmwMQ11a_1accompanySyou_00aabec8_1"
"","","Accompany You",Neutral,50,"I am accompanying you to Ald Daedroth, where we will see if you have made it safe for the Ahemmusa.","I am accompanying you to Ald Daedroth, where we will see if you have made it safe for the Ahemmusa.","fbmwMQ11a_1accompanySyou_00aabec9_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I will accompany you until we stand before the great statue in the inner shrine, where we will speak further.","I will accompany you until we stand before the great statue in the inner shrine, where we will speak further.","fbmwMQ11a_1accompanySyou_00aabec9_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Do you wish me to continue accompanying you?","Do you wish me to continue accompanying you?","fbmwMQ11a_1accompanySyou_00aabec9_3"
"","","Accompany You",Neutral,50,"Have you made Ald Daedroth a safe place for the Ahemmusa?","Have you made Ald Daedroth a safe place for the Ahemmusa?","fbmwMQ11a_1accompanySyou_00aabeca_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If I may pass in safety to the old sanctuary and see the great statue in the inner shrine, then the place is safe for my people.","If I may pass in safety to the old sanctuary and see the great statue in the inner shrine, then the place is safe for my people.","fbmwMQ11a_1accompanySyou_00aabeca_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If Ald Daedroth is safe, are you ready for me to accompany you there and test with our lives whether it is indeed safe?","If Ald Daedroth is safe, are you ready for me to accompany you there and test with our lives whether it is indeed safe?","fbmwMQ11a_1accompanySyou_00aabeca_3"
"","","Accompany You",Neutral,50,"When you are sure Ald Daedroth is safe, then you will return here to me. ","When you are sure Ald Daedroth is safe, then you will return here to me.","fbmwMQ11a_1accompanySyou_00aabecb_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Then I will accompany you, and together we will cross the water to Ald Daedroth.","Then I will accompany you, and together we will cross the water to Ald Daedroth.","fbmwMQ11a_1accompanySyou_00aabecb_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If I may pass in safety to the old sanctuary and see the great statue in the inner shrine, then the place is safe for my people.","If I may pass in safety to the old sanctuary and see the great statue in the inner shrine, then the place is safe for my people.","fbmwMQ11a_1accompanySyou_00aabecb_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I have not the arts of war, but I have courage. I wager my life against the safety of my people. But if Ald Daedroth is not safe... ","I have not the arts of war, but I have courage. I wager my life against the safety of my people. But if Ald Daedroth is not safe...","fbmwMQ11a_1accompanySyou_00aabecb_4"
"","","",Neutral,50,"if I die on my journey... remember... if I die, you will not be named Ahemmusa Nerevarine.","if I die on my journey... remember... if I die, you will not be named Ahemmusa Nerevarine.","fbmwMQ11a_1accompanySyou_00aabecb_5"
"","","Ald Daedroth",Neutral,50,"This site is an ancient shrine to Sheogorath, the Mad Lord. But now it will also be a refuge for the Ahemmusa in times of trouble.","This site is an ancient shrine to Sheogorath, the Mad Lord. But now it will also be a refuge for the Ahemmusa in times of trouble.","MorroDefaultQuest_1AldSDaedroth_0001c682_1"
"","","Ald Daedroth",Neutral,50,"The Ald Daedroth Daedric site is a shrine to Sheogorath, the Mad Lord. The surface ruins are on an island a great distance north as the racer flies.","The Ald Daedroth Daedric site is a shrine to Sheogorath, the Mad Lord. The surface ruins are on an island a great distance north as the racer flies.","MorroDefaultQuest_1AldSDaedroth_0001c681_1"
"","","Make it Safe",Neutral,50,"Yes. Ald Daedroth is indeed a safe refuge for the Ahemmusa. Thank you.","Yes. Ald Daedroth is indeed a safe refuge for the Ahemmusa. Thank you.","fbmwMQ11a_1makeSitSsafe_00aa3c74_1"
"","","Make it Safe",Neutral,50,"Have you made Ald Daedroth safe for the Ahemmusa? Have you dealt with the priest Hlireni Indavel? Are there cultists or creatures of Sheogorath to threaten us?","Have you made Ald Daedroth safe for the Ahemmusa? Have you dealt with the priest Hlireni Indavel? Are there cultists or creatures of Sheogorath to threaten us?","fbmwMQ11a_1makeSitSsafe_00aa3c75_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Are there any other dangers that may cause us harm? Remember... to make sure it is safe, I must accompany you to Ald Daedroth, and see for myself.","Are there any other dangers that may cause us harm? Remember... to make sure it is safe, I must accompany you to Ald Daedroth, and see for myself.","fbmwMQ11a_1makeSitSsafe_00aa3c75_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If I die on my journey, it is not safe... and you shall not be named Ahemmusa Nerevarine.","If I die on my journey, it is not safe... and you shall not be named Ahemmusa Nerevarine.","fbmwMQ11a_1makeSitSsafe_00aa3c75_3"
"","","Make it Safe",Neutral,50,"First you will go to Ald Daedroth. You will make it safe for the Ahemmusa. You are the hero. You decide what must be done.","First you will go to Ald Daedroth. You will make it safe for the Ahemmusa. You are the hero. You decide what must be done.","fbmwMQ11a_1makeSitSsafe_00aa3c76_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"We are not traders, to haggle over the meaning of 'safe.' We are not a warlike people. We are not strong with warriors and witch-wizards.","We are not traders, to haggle over the meaning of 'safe.' We are not a warlike people. We are not strong with warriors and witch-wizards.","fbmwMQ11a_1makeSitSsafe_00aa3c76_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Make Ald Daedroth safe for us. Then, when I accompany you to Ald Daedroth, then you and I will judge whether it is safe.","Make Ald Daedroth safe for us. Then, when I accompany you to Ald Daedroth, then you and I will judge whether it is safe.","fbmwMQ11a_1makeSitSsafe_00aa3c76_3"
"","","My Gulakhans",Neutral,50,"The gulakhans of the Ahemmusa are Kausi, Herder and Initiate; Dutadalk, Hunter and Brother; and Yenammu, Scout and Brother.","The gulakhans of the Ahemmusa are Kausi, Herder and Initiate; Dutadalk, Hunter and Brother; and Yenammu, Scout and Brother.","MorroDefaultQuest_1mySgulakhans_00321aa1_1"
"","","Nerevarine",Neutral,50,"You are the Ahemmusa Nerevarine. I have named you, and given you the Madstone, so that you may be known to all Peoples of the Wastes.","You are the Ahemmusa Nerevarine. I have named you, and given you the Madstone, so that you may be known to all Peoples of the Wastes.","fbmwMQ11a_1Nerevarine_00023c78_1"
"","","Nerevarine",Neutral,50,"I know the prophecies. I know an outlander, clanfriend of the Urshilaku, has done great deeds, and claims to fulfill those prophecies.","I know the prophecies. I know an outlander, clanfriend of the Urshilaku, has done great deeds, and claims to fulfill those prophecies.","fbmwMQ11a_1Nerevarine_00023c77_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Are you that outlander? And why are you here?","Are you that outlander? And why are you here?","fbmwMQ11a_1Nerevarine_00023c77_2"
"","","Ordinators",Neutral,50,"The Ordinators, the priest-soldiers of the Temple, have the duty of keeping worshippers from restoring the old Daedric sites scattered throughout the wastelands and along the rocky coasts and islands of Vvardenfell.","The Ordinators, the priest-soldiers of the Temple, have the duty of keeping worshippers from restoring the old Daedric sites scattered throughout the wastelands and along the rocky coasts and islands of Vvardenfell.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Ordinators_00023c79_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Now these Ordinators are busy elsewhere, and the old Daedric sites are coming back to life.","Now these Ordinators are busy elsewhere, and the old Daedric sites are coming back to life.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Ordinators_00023c79_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Some traders reported a ship carrying a few Ordinators has sailed from Molag Maar for Ald Daedroth, but my timid scouts won't dare approach the island.","Some traders reported a ship carrying a few Ordinators has sailed from Molag Maar for Ald Daedroth, but my timid scouts won't dare approach the island.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Ordinators_00023c79_3"
"","","Safe Place",Neutral,50,"You have made Ald Daedroth a safe refuge for the Ahemmusa. Thank you.","You have made Ald Daedroth a safe refuge for the Ahemmusa. Thank you.","fbmwMQ11a_1safeSplace_00aa3c7a_1"
"","","Safe Place",Neutral,50,"In seasons past, when threatened, the Ahemmusa could take shelter in the ruins of Ald Daedroth.","In seasons past, when threatened, the Ahemmusa could take shelter in the ruins of Ald Daedroth.","fbmwMQ11a_1safeSplace_00aa3c7b_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But now the priestess Hlireni Indavel has come and restored the Daedric shrine, and worshippers of Sheogorath dwell there, protected by terrible sorceries and summonings.","But now the priestess Hlireni Indavel has come and restored the Daedric shrine, and worshippers of Sheogorath dwell there, protected by terrible sorceries and summonings.","fbmwMQ11a_1safeSplace_00aa3c7b_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"First, you will go to Ald Daedroth and make it safe for the Ahemmusa.  Then you will return, and I will accompany you there,","First, you will go to Ald Daedroth and make it safe for the Ahemmusa.  Then you will return, and I will accompany you there,","fbmwMQ11a_1safeSplace_00aa3c7b_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If Ald Daedroth is a safe place for my people, then I will name you Nerevarine.","If Ald Daedroth is a safe place for my people, then I will name you Nerevarine.","fbmwMQ11a_1safeSplace_00aa3c7b_4"
"","","Sheogorath",Neutral,50,"For those who serve Sheogorath, the Mad Lord, there is no good or evil, right or wrong, true or false, real or unreal.","For those who serve Sheogorath, the Mad Lord, there is no good or evil, right or wrong, true or false, real or unreal.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Sheogorath_003223bd_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"For them, there is only what they want, and what they see.","For them, there is only what they want, and what they see.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Sheogorath_003223bd_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"With such carelessness, only the very strong and very lucky cultists survive, while the weak provide sport and amusement for the others.","With such carelessness, only the very strong and very lucky cultists survive, while the weak provide sport and amusement for the others.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Sheogorath_003223bd_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And the Spawn of Sheogorath are never twice the same, and each more terrible than the next. It is an evil cult, and dangerous.","And the Spawn of Sheogorath are never twice the same, and each more terrible than the next. It is an evil cult, and dangerous.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Sheogorath_003223bd_4"
"","","Favel Tomb",Neutral,50,"It is west of our camp. Go west along the coast, past the ruins. If you reach the Ashlands, turn back. Outcasts from our tribe live nearby.","It is west of our camp. Go west along the coast, past the ruins. If you reach the Ashlands, turn back. Outcasts from our tribe live nearby.","MorroDefaultQuest_1FavelSTomb_00aa3c6f_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"They are dangerous. Avoid them if you can.","They are dangerous. Avoid them if you can.","MorroDefaultQuest_1FavelSTomb_00aa3c6f_2"
"","","Madstone",Neutral,50,"The Madstone of the Ahemmusa is a protection against the spells of witch-warriors.","The Madstone of the Ahemmusa is a protection against the spells of witch-warriors.","fbmwMQ11a_1Madstone_00aa3c73_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"When you use it, and touch your enemy, it causes the voices of the ancestors to cry out in his head, confusing him, and fuddling his witcheries.","When you use it, and touch your enemy, it causes the voices of the ancestors to cry out in his head, confusing him, and fuddling his witcheries.","fbmwMQ11a_1Madstone_00aa3c73_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I warn you, though; when you use the Madstone, the ancestors also cry out in your ears, so you, too, are made mad by their wailing.","I warn you, though; when you use the Madstone, the ancestors also cry out in your ears, so you, too, are made mad by their wailing.","fbmwMQ11a_1Madstone_00aa3c73_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"It is the Madstone. Perhaps it will not please a wizard, but it may greatly please a warrior.","It is the Madstone. Perhaps it will not please a wizard, but it may greatly please a warrior.","fbmwMQ11a_1Madstone_00aa3c73_4"
"","","I did.",Neutral,50,"I know you speak the truth,&sUActnQuick1;. I do not need such as her for an apprentice. I will send her to talk with this Argonian.","I know you speak the truth,&sUActnQuick1;. I do not need such as her for an apprentice. I will send her to talk with this Argonian.","fbmwMGWiseWoman_1arrangeSaSmeeting1_00323138_1"
"","","Minabibi did.",Neutral,50,"So be it. I will send my apprentice to talk with this Skink, but I do so for the honor of the Ahemmusa.","So be it. I will send my apprentice to talk with this Skink, but I do so for the honor of the Ahemmusa.","fbmwMGWiseWoman_1arrangeSaSmeeting2_00323139_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"She will soon see the error of the foreigners' ways and return to us. She will make a fine Wise Woman when my duties are done.","She will soon see the error of the foreigners' ways and return to us. She will make a fine Wise Woman when my duties are done.","fbmwMGWiseWoman_1arrangeSaSmeeting2_00323139_2"
