Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Our time is almost upon us. What have you done about the Master Thief?","Our time is almost upon us. What have you done about the Master Thief?","fbmwFGBigBosses_GREETING_0000ce5a_1"
"","","GREETING",Anger,50,"Die, thief!","Die, thief!","fbmwFGBigBosses_GREETING_000067a0_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Have you done what I asked? Are the Thieves Guild Bosses taken care of yet?","Have you done what I asked? Are the Thieves Guild Bosses taken care of yet?","fbmwFGKillBosses_GREETING_0000ce5b_1"
"","","Unrest in Cyrodiil City",Neutral,50,"Uriel Septim was never a strong Emperor. And now he's finally dying of age and illness. A coward's death. They say Ocato makes the real decisions.","Uriel Septim was never a strong Emperor. And now he's finally dying of age and illness. A coward's death. They say Ocato makes the real decisions.","MorroDefaultQuest_1UnrestSinSCyrodiilSCity_003204df_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"They say Uriel's heirs are really Daedra or shapeshifters planted by Jagar Tharn.","They say Uriel's heirs are really Daedra or shapeshifters planted by Jagar Tharn.","MorroDefaultQuest_1UnrestSinSCyrodiilSCity_003204df_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"They say the Emperor might pull back the Legions to try and protect himself.","They say the Emperor might pull back the Legions to try and protect himself.","MorroDefaultQuest_1UnrestSinSCyrodiilSCity_003204df_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Some of the generals in the Legions have one eye on Uriel Septim and one eye on the throne.","Some of the generals in the Legions have one eye on Uriel Septim and one eye on the throne.","MorroDefaultQuest_1UnrestSinSCyrodiilSCity_003204df_4"
"","","",Neutral,50,"At a time like this, only the Imperial Guilds with strong allies will survive.","At a time like this, only the Imperial Guilds with strong allies will survive.","MorroDefaultQuest_1UnrestSinSCyrodiilSCity_003204df_5"
"","","Thieves Guild Bosses",Neutral,50,"You've been expelled, outlander. You must make amends before I'll discuss Guild matters with you.","You've been expelled, outlander. You must make amends before I'll discuss Guild matters with you.","fbmwFGKillBosses_1ThievesSGuildSbosses_0032075a_1"
"","","Thieves Guild Bosses",Neutral,50,"What? You already killed the bosses of the Thieves Guild? You deserve the rank of Champion even more than I thought.","What? You already killed the bosses of the Thieves Guild? You deserve the rank of Champion even more than I thought.","fbmwFGKillBosses_1ThievesSGuildSbosses_00f8a27b_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Congratulations, outlander, I'm making you my second in command. Now we need to take care of the Master Thief himself.","Congratulations, outlander, I'm making you my second in command. Now we need to take care of the Master Thief himself.","fbmwFGKillBosses_1ThievesSGuildSbosses_00f8a27b_2"
"","","Thieves Guild Bosses",Neutral,50,"Good work, outlander. I'm making you my second in command. Now our allies want us to take care of the Master Thief himself.","Good work, outlander. I'm making you my second in command. Now our allies want us to take care of the Master Thief himself.","fbmwFGKillBosses_1ThievesSGuildSbosses_00f8a27c_1"
"","","Thieves Guild Bosses",Neutral,50,"In Sadrith Mora, kill Helende at Dirty Muriel's Cornerclub. Feel free to kill any other thieves there.","In Sadrith Mora, kill Helende at Dirty Muriel's Cornerclub. Feel free to kill any other thieves there.","fbmwFGKillBosses_1ThievesSGuildSbosses_0032075b_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"In Balmora, the Thieves Guild there is the South Wall tavern. Kill Habasi the Khajiit. Then go to The Rat in the Pot in Ald'ruhn and kill Aengoth.","In Balmora, the Thieves Guild there is the South Wall tavern. Kill Habasi the Khajiit. Then go to The Rat in the Pot in Ald'ruhn and kill Aengoth.","fbmwFGKillBosses_1ThievesSGuildSbosses_0032075b_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"When the Thieves Guild bosses are dead, talk to me again. Here's some gold to deal with the guards.","When the Thieves Guild bosses are dead, talk to me again. Here's some gold to deal with the guards.","fbmwFGKillBosses_1ThievesSGuildSbosses_0032075b_3"
"","","Fighters Guild",Neutral,50,"You've been expelled, outlander. You must clear your name before I'll discuss Guild matters with you.","You've been expelled, outlander. You must clear your name before I'll discuss Guild matters with you.","MorroDefaultQuest_1FightersSGuild_0032149a_1"
"","","Fighters Guild",Neutral,50,"With our new allies, the Fighters Guild has a bright future. You can share that future with me, outlander.","With our new allies, the Fighters Guild has a bright future. You can share that future with me, outlander.","MorroDefaultQuest_1FightersSGuild_0032149c_1"
"","","Fighters Guild",Neutral,50,"As a member of the Fighters Guild, you'll be around when things start getting dirty here in Vvardenfell. Stick with us, outlander. We're going places.","As a member of the Fighters Guild, you'll be around when things start getting dirty here in Vvardenfell. Stick with us, outlander. We're going places.","MorroDefaultQuest_1FightersSGuild_0032149d_1"
"","","Fighters Guild",Neutral,50,"I'm the head of the Fighters Guild here in Vvardenfell. What do you want?","I'm the head of the Fighters Guild here in Vvardenfell. What do you want?","MorroDefaultQuest_1FightersSGuild_0032149e_1"
"","","Master Thief",Neutral,50,"You've been expelled, outlander. You must make amends before I'll discuss Guild matters with you.","You've been expelled, outlander. You must make amends before I'll discuss Guild matters with you.","fbmwFGBigBosses_1masterSthief_00321b9e_1"
"","","Master Thief",Neutral,50,"What? You're the Master Thief? Well, why didn't you say so from the start?","What? You're the Master Thief? Well, why didn't you say so from the start?","fbmwFGBigBosses_1masterSthief_00321ba3_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Tell you what, outlander, between you and me and Camonna Tong, we've got a good deal here.","Tell you what, outlander, between you and me and Camonna Tong, we've got a good deal here.","fbmwFGBigBosses_1masterSthief_00321ba3_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Let's start by you telling me everything you know about the Thieves Guild operations in Vvardenfell.","Let's start by you telling me everything you know about the Thieves Guild operations in Vvardenfell.","fbmwFGBigBosses_1masterSthief_00321ba3_3"
"","","Master Thief",Neutral,50,"I hear you killed the Master Thief. Great work, outlander. Thanks for taking care of the Thieves Guild for me.","I hear you killed the Master Thief. Great work, outlander. Thanks for taking care of the Thieves Guild for me.","fbmwFGBigBosses_1masterSthief_00321ba4_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Now the only one who can threaten my position...is you. You showed promise, but a bit too much ambition. You will not be missed.","Now the only one who can threaten my position...is you. You showed promise, but a bit too much ambition. You will not be missed.","fbmwFGBigBosses_1masterSthief_00321ba4_2"
"","","Master Thief",Neutral,50,"The Master Thief and his second-in-command are in Simine Fralinie's bookstore. Get rid of Gentleman Jim Stacey, the Redguard. He's in charge.","The Master Thief and his second-in-command are in Simine Fralinie's bookstore. Get rid of Gentleman Jim Stacey, the Redguard. He's in charge.","fbmwFGBigBosses_1masterSthief_00321ba5_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I wouldn't mind if you took out his lackey as well. Once you have crippled the Thieves Guild, I will make you the new Guildmaster and retire.","I wouldn't mind if you took out his lackey as well. Once you have crippled the Thieves Guild, I will make you the new Guildmaster and retire.","fbmwFGBigBosses_1masterSthief_00321ba5_2"
"","","Master Thief",Neutral,50,"First you need to advance to the rank of Champion.","First you need to advance to the rank of Champion.","fbmwFGBigBosses_1masterSthief_00321ba6_1"
"","","Advancement",Neutral,50,"You wish to advance further, outlander? There really isn't much farther for you to advance, save for taking my position!","You wish to advance further, outlander? There really isn't much farther for you to advance, save for taking my position!","fbmwFGAdvancement_1Advancement_003220a8_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"We can discuss that later, though. First, I have some orders for you.","We can discuss that later, though. First, I have some orders for you.","fbmwFGAdvancement_1Advancement_003220a8_2"
"","","Advancement",Neutral,50,"I can't advance you anymore, outlander. For further advancement, you'll have to talk to Sjoring Hard-Heart himself in Vivec.","I can't advance you anymore, outlander. For further advancement, you'll have to talk to Sjoring Hard-Heart himself in Vivec.","fbmwFGAdvancement_1Advancement_003220a9_1"
"","","Orvas Dren",Neutral,50,"Since Orvas Dren died, I've been thinking I might want to look somewhere else for allies.","Since Orvas Dren died, I've been thinking I might want to look somewhere else for allies.","MorroDefaultQuest_1OrvasSDren_0032236f_1"
"","","Orvas Dren",Neutral,50,"He's strong, but tough and fair. With his help, I'm sure the Fighters Guild here in Vvardenfell will survive.","He's strong, but tough and fair. With his help, I'm sure the Fighters Guild here in Vvardenfell will survive.","MorroDefaultQuest_1OrvasSDren_00322370_1"
"","","Smuggling",Neutral,50,"It's dangerous, but the money is good. Our new allies can take care of it. I'd advise staying out of the way.","It's dangerous, but the money is good. Our new allies can take care of it. I'd advise staying out of the way.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Smuggling_00322495_1"
"","","Orders",Neutral,50,"You did quite a job on the local heads of the Thieves Guild. Now it's time to take care of the Master Thief in Vivec.","You did quite a job on the local heads of the Thieves Guild. Now it's time to take care of the Master Thief in Vivec.","fbmwFGAdvancement_1Orders_00012c61_1"
"","","Orders",Neutral,50,"Just kill the Thieves Guild bosses like I told you. Then we can talk about the future of the Fighters Guild.","Just kill the Thieves Guild bosses like I told you. Then we can talk about the future of the Fighters Guild.","fbmwFGAdvancement_1Orders_00012c60_1"
"","","Orders",Neutral,50,"I've watched your progress in the Fighters Guild, outlander. You'll make a fine Guildmaster someday.","I've watched your progress in the Fighters Guild, outlander. You'll make a fine Guildmaster someday.","fbmwFGAdvancement_1Orders_00322b9d_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But with all the unrest in Cyrodiil city, we need allies to make sure there's still a Fighter's Guild here for you.","But with all the unrest in Cyrodiil city, we need allies to make sure there's still a Fighter's Guild here for you.","fbmwFGAdvancement_1Orders_00322b9d_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I need you to kill the Thieves Guild bosses.","I need you to kill the Thieves Guild bosses.","fbmwFGAdvancement_1Orders_00322b9d_3"
"","","Orders",Neutral,50,"Until you earn a better rank, you'll take your orders from my Champion, Lorbumol gro-Aglakh.","Until you earn a better rank, you'll take your orders from my Champion, Lorbumol gro-Aglakh.","fbmwFGAdvancement_1Orders_00322b9e_1"
"","","Allies",Neutral,50,"You've been expelled,&sUActnQuick1. You must make amends before I'll discuss Guild matters with you.","You've been expelled,&sUActnQuick1. You must make amends before I'll discuss Guild matters with you.","fbmwFGKillBosses_1allies_00322bf5_1"
"","","Allies",Neutral,50,"Like I said our allies are the Camonna Tong.","Like I said our allies are the Camonna Tong.","fbmwFGKillBosses_1allies_00008bf0_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If we get rid of the Thieves Guild by killing the Master Thief, they'll be free to help the Fighters Guild here in Vvardenfell survive the hard times","If we get rid of the Thieves Guild by killing the Master Thief, they'll be free to help the Fighters Guild here in Vvardenfell survive the hard times","fbmwFGKillBosses_1allies_00008bf0_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"ahead.","ahead.","fbmwFGKillBosses_1allies_00008bf0_3"
"","","Allies",Neutral,50,"I trust you,&sUActnQuick1;, so I'll tell you that I've made an alliance with the Camonna Tong. These local boys have the wit and the juice.","I trust you,&sUActnQuick1;, so I'll tell you that I've made an alliance with the Camonna Tong. These local boys have the wit and the juice.","fbmwFGKillBosses_1allies_00322bf6_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The Thieves Guild hasn't got a chance, but they're bad for business. It's time for change in Vvardenfell, and you can bring about that change.","The Thieves Guild hasn't got a chance, but they're bad for business. It's time for change in Vvardenfell, and you can bring about that change.","fbmwFGKillBosses_1allies_00322bf6_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I'd like you to kill the Thieves Guild bosses.","I'd like you to kill the Thieves Guild bosses.","fbmwFGKillBosses_1allies_00322bf6_3"
"","","Tell All",Neutral,50,"That information will help a great deal when I take over the Thieves Guild and the Camonna Tong myself. Now who's the "Master Thief," outlander?","That information will help a great deal when I take over the Thieves Guild and the Camonna Tong myself. Now who's the "Master Thief," outlander?","fbmwFGBigBosses_1masterSthief1_0032341c_1"
"","","Refuse",Neutral,50,"That's too bad, outlander. We could have worked together. Instead, you'll die alone.","That's too bad, outlander. We could have worked together. Instead, you'll die alone.","fbmwFGBigBosses_1masterSthief2_0032341d_1"
