Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Hail, friend! I hope you find our mead hall to your liking. If you're tired, grab a bedroll and go to sleep. We don't stand on ceremony here at Thirsk. We live like family, as it should be!","Hail, friend! I hope you find our mead hall to your liking. If you're tired, grab a bedroll and go to sleep. We don't stand on ceremony here at Thirsk. We live like family, as it should be!","fbmwMSGreetings_GREETING_0002f6e0_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Hail, good friend! Skjoldr Wolf-Runner is my name. I am the chieftain of Thirsk, and welcome you to our home.","Hail, good friend! Skjoldr Wolf-Runner is my name. I am the chieftain of Thirsk, and welcome you to our home.","fbmwMSGreetings_GREETING_0002f6e1_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You'll not find a better mead hall anywhere, not even in Skyrim. For one hundred years Thirsk has withstood all manner of attack, from the snow and hail to those infernal Rieklings. But the mead hall still stands, and its hospitality is unmatched.","You'll not find a better mead hall anywhere, not even in Skyrim. For one hundred years Thirsk has withstood all manner of attack, from the snow and hail to those infernal Rieklings. But the mead hall still stands, and its hospitality is unmatched.","fbmwMSGreetings_GREETING_0002f6e1_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Please, stay and relax. Enjoy our fine drink, and seek shelter from the cold.  Here, my friend -- taste the nectar of Shor!","Please, stay and relax. Enjoy our fine drink, and seek shelter from the cold.  Here, my friend -- taste the nectar of Shor!","fbmwMSGreetings_GREETING_0002f6e1_3"
"","","Mirisa never returned",Neutral,50,"Aye, the missionary came here several weeks ago. She started talking about her Shrine, and then began preaching about the evils of mead.","Aye, the missionary came here several weeks ago. She started talking about her Shrine, and then began preaching about the evils of mead.","MorroDefaultQuest_1MirisaSneverSreturned_00320730_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Nice lass, but a little high-strung. Erich, he...he didn't really like what she had to say. Thought he'd teach her a lesson.","Nice lass, but a little high-strung. Erich, he...he didn't really like what she had to say. Thought he'd teach her a lesson.","MorroDefaultQuest_1MirisaSneverSreturned_00320730_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I'm...I'm not really sure where she is now.","I'm...I'm not really sure where she is now.","MorroDefaultQuest_1MirisaSneverSreturned_00320730_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"[Skjoldr gives you a knowing look, and then gestures with his head to the staircase leading to the second floor.]","[Skjoldr gives you a knowing look, and then gestures with his head to the staircase leading to the second floor.]","MorroDefaultQuest_1MirisaSneverSreturned_00320730_4"
"","","Mirisa never returned",Neutral,50,"Well, it would seem Erich has finally met his destiny, so there's no harm in letting you know the truth.","Well, it would seem Erich has finally met his destiny, so there's no harm in letting you know the truth.","MorroDefaultQuest_1MirisaSneverSreturned_00320731_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The missionary is upstairs, locked in Erich's room. She's been there for quite a while, too, poor thing.","The missionary is upstairs, locked in Erich's room. She's been there for quite a while, too, poor thing.","MorroDefaultQuest_1MirisaSneverSreturned_00320731_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If you intend to let her go, no one here will stop you.","If you intend to let her go, no one here will stop you.","MorroDefaultQuest_1MirisaSneverSreturned_00320731_3"
"","","Erich the Unworthy",Neutral,50,"Erich is a loyal member of the clan, and has defended Thirsk time and time again.","Erich is a loyal member of the clan, and has defended Thirsk time and time again.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ErichStheSUnworthy_00320afd_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But he's hot headed and loose lipped, and has made more enemies around here than he should have.","But he's hot headed and loose lipped, and has made more enemies around here than he should have.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ErichStheSUnworthy_00320afd_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"We can not harm a clan brother, but there are some days....","We can not harm a clan brother, but there are some days....","MorroDefaultQuest_1ErichStheSUnworthy_00320afd_3"
"","","Erich the Unworthy",Neutral,50,"We'll miss the strength of a good warrior, but not the man. Erich was too arrogant for his own good and his days were numbered anyway.","We'll miss the strength of a good warrior, but not the man. Erich was too arrogant for his own good and his days were numbered anyway.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ErichStheSUnworthy_00320afe_1"
