Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Other Mysticism Spells",Neutral,50,"Other mysticism spells work directly upon the subtle magical forces of the unseen world.","Other mysticism spells work directly upon the subtle magical forces of the unseen world.","MorroDefaultQuest_1otherSmysticismSspells_00320563_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The most common of these mysticism spells are: purge magicka, touch dispel, Almalexia's grace, soul trap, telekinesis, detect creature, detect enchantment, detect key, spell absorption, and reflect.","The most common of these mysticism spells are: purge magicka, touch dispel, Almalexia's grace, soul trap, telekinesis, detect creature, detect enchantment, detect key, spell absorption, and reflect.","MorroDefaultQuest_1otherSmysticismSspells_00320563_2"
"","","Fundamental Attributes",Neutral,50,"The eleven fundamental attributes of natural and supernatural beings are agility, endurance, fatigue, health, intelligence, luck, personality, speed, strength, willpower, magicka.","The eleven fundamental attributes of natural and supernatural beings are agility, endurance, fatigue, health, intelligence, luck, personality, speed, strength, willpower, magicka.","MorroDefaultQuest_1fundamentalSattributes_0032056a_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Scholars and sages of the six magic colleges are familiar with these fundamental attributes from the works of the earliest Aldmeri philosophers, and the concepts have been adopted by all the other scholarly disciplines of Imperial culture.","Scholars and sages of the six magic colleges are familiar with these fundamental attributes from the works of the earliest Aldmeri philosophers, and the concepts have been adopted by all the other scholarly disciplines of Imperial culture.","MorroDefaultQuest_1fundamentalSattributes_0032056a_2"
"","","Bound Weapons Spells",Neutral,50,"Bound weapon spells summon lesser daedra constrained within the form of magical weapons for the duration of the magical effect.","Bound weapon spells summon lesser daedra constrained within the form of magical weapons for the duration of the magical effect.","MorroDefaultQuest_1boundSweaponsSspells_003207a0_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The weapons are impossibly light, superbly formed, and profoundly bloodthirsty.","The weapons are impossibly light, superbly formed, and profoundly bloodthirsty.","MorroDefaultQuest_1boundSweaponsSspells_003207a0_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The most common spells of this variety are: bound dagger, bound longsword, bound mace, bound battle-axe, bound spear, and bound longbow.","The most common spells of this variety are: bound dagger, bound longsword, bound mace, bound battle-axe, bound spear, and bound longbow.","MorroDefaultQuest_1boundSweaponsSspells_003207a0_3"
"","","Daedric Summonings",Neutral,50,"Certain Daedric summonings are more often encountered on Vvardenfell.","Certain Daedric summonings are more often encountered on Vvardenfell.","MorroDefaultQuest_1DaedricSsummonings_00320a0d_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Good Daedra are the Daedra associated with Boethiah, Azura, and Mephala -- the winged twilight and the hunger.","Good Daedra are the Daedra associated with Boethiah, Azura, and Mephala -- the winged twilight and the hunger.","MorroDefaultQuest_1DaedricSsummonings_00320a0d_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Bad Daedra are associated with Mehrunes Dagon, Malacath, Sheogorath, and Molag Bal. Atronachs are unaligned Daedra of the elemental planes.","Bad Daedra are associated with Mehrunes Dagon, Malacath, Sheogorath, and Molag Bal. Atronachs are unaligned Daedra of the elemental planes.","MorroDefaultQuest_1DaedricSsummonings_00320a0d_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But don't judge a summoning by its patron. The summoner commands a summoning, and, good or bad, nice or nasty, they must do the summoner's bidding.","But don't judge a summoning by its patron. The summoner commands a summoning, and, good or bad, nice or nasty, they must do the summoner's bidding.","MorroDefaultQuest_1DaedricSsummonings_00320a0d_4"
"","","Destruction Spells",Neutral,50,"There are many common variants of destruction spells, not to mention the countless custom versions created by ambitious spellcasters.","There are many common variants of destruction spells, not to mention the countless custom versions created by ambitious spellcasters.","MorroDefaultQuest_1destructionSspells_00320a81_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"There are so many different destruction spells that it helps to divide them into five different classes of effects: elemental damage, attribute-draining, attribute-damaging, vulnerability, and disintegration.","There are so many different destruction spells that it helps to divide them into five different classes of effects: elemental damage, attribute-draining, attribute-damaging, vulnerability, and disintegration.","MorroDefaultQuest_1destructionSspells_00320a81_2"
"","","Conjuration Spells",Neutral,50,"Unlike spells of the other colleges, there are few variants and versions of the conjuration spells, other than according to effect duration.","Unlike spells of the other colleges, there are few variants and versions of the conjuration spells, other than according to effect duration.","MorroDefaultQuest_1conjurationSspells_00320a88_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"There are four different classes of restoration spells: domination spells, summoning spells, bound weapons spells, and bound armor spells.","There are four different classes of restoration spells: domination spells, summoning spells, bound weapons spells, and bound armor spells.","MorroDefaultQuest_1conjurationSspells_00320a88_2"
"","","Restoration Spells",Neutral,50,"There are many common variants of restoration spells, not to mention the countless custom versions created by ambitious spellcasters.","There are many common variants of restoration spells, not to mention the countless custom versions created by ambitious spellcasters.","MorroDefaultQuest_1restorationSspells_00320a8f_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"It helps to divide restoration into four different classes of effects: cure spells, restore spells, fortify spells, and resist spells.","It helps to divide restoration into four different classes of effects: cure spells, restore spells, fortify spells, and resist spells.","MorroDefaultQuest_1restorationSspells_00320a8f_2"
"","","Bound Armor Spells",Neutral,50,"Bound armor spells summon lesser daedra constrained within the form of magical armor for the duration of the magical effect.","Bound armor spells summon lesser daedra constrained within the form of magical armor for the duration of the magical effect.","MorroDefaultQuest_1boundSarmorSspells_00320aa4_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The armor pieces are impossibly light, superbly formed, and supernaturally durable.","The armor pieces are impossibly light, superbly formed, and supernaturally durable.","MorroDefaultQuest_1boundSarmorSspells_00320aa4_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The most common spells of this variety are: bound cuirass, bound helm, bound boots, bound shield, and bound gauntlets.","The most common spells of this variety are: bound cuirass, bound helm, bound boots, bound shield, and bound gauntlets.","MorroDefaultQuest_1boundSarmorSspells_00320aa4_3"
"","","Alteration Spells",Neutral,50,"There are many common variants of alteration spells, not to mention the countless custom versions created by ambitious spellcasters.","There are many common variants of alteration spells, not to mention the countless custom versions created by ambitious spellcasters.","MorroDefaultQuest_1alterationSspells_00320b95_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But here is a list of the most basic spells, representing all the fundamental classes of spell effects produced by this college: water breathing, buoyancy, water walking, shield, fire shield, shock shield, frost shield, burden, feather, jump, slowfall, levitate, lock, and open.","But here is a list of the most basic spells, representing all the fundamental classes of spell effects produced by this college: water breathing, buoyancy, water walking, shield, fire shield, shock shield, frost shield, burden, feather, jump, slowfall, levitate, lock, and open.","MorroDefaultQuest_1alterationSspells_00320b95_2"
"","","Domination Spells",Neutral,50,"Domination spells permit the caster to bend the will of creatures and humanoids to the caster's service.","Domination spells permit the caster to bend the will of creatures and humanoids to the caster's service.","MorroDefaultQuest_1dominationSspells_00320ba3_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Affected creatures and humanoids will not, alas, listen to or follow orders, but they will feel a compulsion to aid and protect the caster.","Affected creatures and humanoids will not, alas, listen to or follow orders, but they will feel a compulsion to aid and protect the caster.","MorroDefaultQuest_1dominationSspells_00320ba3_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Most otherworldly creatures are unaffected, though the undead can be compelled to avoid the caster.","Most otherworldly creatures are unaffected, though the undead can be compelled to avoid the caster.","MorroDefaultQuest_1dominationSspells_00320ba3_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The most common domination spells are: turn undead, command creatures, and command humanoids.","The most common domination spells are: turn undead, command creatures, and command humanoids.","MorroDefaultQuest_1dominationSspells_00320ba3_4"
"","","Ascended Sleeper",Neutral,50,"The ascended sleepers are distorted, half-human, half-beast creatures transformed by a mysterious force into powerful magical beings.","The ascended sleepers are distorted, half-human, half-beast creatures transformed by a mysterious force into powerful magical beings.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ascendedSsleeper_00320cb2_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Ascended sleepers are highly intelligent, aggressive, and dangerous. Ascended sleepers are associated in some way with the Devil Dagoth Ur.","Ascended sleepers are highly intelligent, aggressive, and dangerous. Ascended sleepers are associated in some way with the Devil Dagoth Ur.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ascendedSsleeper_00320cb2_2"
"","","Mysticism Spells",Neutral,50,"There are many common variants of mysticism spells, not to mention the countless custom versions created by ambitious spellcasters.","There are many common variants of mysticism spells, not to mention the countless custom versions created by ambitious spellcasters.","MorroDefaultQuest_1mysticismSspells_00320d33_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"It helps to divide mysticism into three different classes of effects: transport spells, absorption spells, and other mysticism spells.","It helps to divide mysticism into three different classes of effects: transport spells, absorption spells, and other mysticism spells.","MorroDefaultQuest_1mysticismSspells_00320d33_2"
"","","Elemental Damage",Neutral,50,"Elemental damage spells injure natural and supernatural creatures with magics based on the elemental forces of fire, frost, shock, and poison.","Elemental damage spells injure natural and supernatural creatures with magics based on the elemental forces of fire, frost, shock, and poison.","MorroDefaultQuest_1elementalSdamage_00320d3a_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Here is a list of the most basic destruction spells, representing all the fundamental classes of elemental damage effects: flame, flamebolt, spark, sparkbolt, shard, shardbolt, poison, and poisonbolt.","Here is a list of the most basic destruction spells, representing all the fundamental classes of elemental damage effects: flame, flamebolt, spark, sparkbolt, shard, shardbolt, poison, and poisonbolt.","MorroDefaultQuest_1elementalSdamage_00320d3a_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"In general, these effects cause damage on touch or at range, and the '-bolt' version is the ranged variant of the spell.","In general, these effects cause damage on touch or at range, and the '-bolt' version is the ranged variant of the spell.","MorroDefaultQuest_1elementalSdamage_00320d3a_3"
"","","Transport Spells",Neutral,50,"Transport spells instantaneously transport the caster from one location to another.","Transport spells instantaneously transport the caster from one location to another.","MorroDefaultQuest_1transportSspells_00320d41_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Four mysticism transport effects are common in Morrowind: mark, recall, divine intervention, and Almsivi intervention.","Four mysticism transport effects are common in Morrowind: mark, recall, divine intervention, and Almsivi intervention.","MorroDefaultQuest_1transportSspells_00320d41_2"
"","","Summoning Spells",Neutral,50,"Summoning spells summon otherworldly creatures from the outer realms to ward and protect the caster for the duration of the magical effect.","Summoning spells summon otherworldly creatures from the outer realms to ward and protect the caster for the duration of the magical effect.","MorroDefaultQuest_1summoningSspells_00320d48_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"More common spells of this sort include: summon ancestral ghost, summon least bonewalker, summon greater bonewalker, summon skeletal minion, and summon scamp.","More common spells of this sort include: summon ancestral ghost, summon least bonewalker, summon greater bonewalker, summon skeletal minion, and summon scamp.","MorroDefaultQuest_1summoningSspells_00320d48_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"More powerful spells of this class, like summon dremora and summon daedroth, expend too much magicka to be practical for all but master sorcerers.","More powerful spells of this class, like summon dremora and summon daedroth, expend too much magicka to be practical for all but master sorcerers.","MorroDefaultQuest_1summoningSspells_00320d48_3"
"","","Corprus Stalker",Neutral,50,"Corprus stalkers are the deformed, deranged victims of corprus disease.","Corprus stalkers are the deformed, deranged victims of corprus disease.","fbmwFGCorprusStalker_1CorprusSStalker_00321126_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Aggressive and dangerous, they also carry  corprus disease, a deadly disease profoundly affecting a victim's mind and body.","Aggressive and dangerous, they also carry  corprus disease, a deadly disease profoundly affecting a victim's mind and body.","fbmwFGCorprusStalker_1CorprusSStalker_00321126_2"
"","","Winged Twilight",Neutral,50,"The winged twilight are the female-formed Daedric messengers of the Daedra Lord Azura. Daedra hearts have modest magical properties.","The winged twilight are the female-formed Daedric messengers of the Daedra Lord Azura. Daedra hearts have modest magical properties.","MorroDefaultQuest_1wingedStwilight_00320f3e_1"
"","","Illusion Spells",Neutral,50,"There are many common variants of illusion spells, not to mention the countless custom versions created by ambitious spellcasters.","There are many common variants of illusion spells, not to mention the countless custom versions created by ambitious spellcasters.","MorroDefaultQuest_1illusionSspells_00320fa4_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But here is a list of the most basic spells, representing all the fundamental classes of spell effects produced by this college: hide, chameleon, light, chameleon, night-eye, charming touch, paralysis, silence, blind, earwig, calm humanoid, calm creature, frenzy humanoid, frenzy creature, demoralize humanoid, demoralize creature, rally humanoid, and rally creature.","But here is a list of the most basic spells, representing all the fundamental classes of spell effects produced by this college: hide, chameleon, light, chameleon, night-eye, charming touch, paralysis, silence, blind, earwig, calm humanoid, calm creature, frenzy humanoid, frenzy creature, demoralize humanoid, demoralize creature, rally humanoid, and rally creature.","MorroDefaultQuest_1illusionSspells_00320fa4_2"
"","","Flame Atronach",Neutral,50,"The flame atronach is a powerful Daedric summoning associated with elemental fire.","The flame atronach is a powerful Daedric summoning associated with elemental fire.","MorroDefaultQuest_1flameSatronach_003212b7_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Crystalline elemental fire compounds called fire salts may be salvaged from the remains of banished fire atronachs.","Crystalline elemental fire compounds called fire salts may be salvaged from the remains of banished fire atronachs.","MorroDefaultQuest_1flameSatronach_003212b7_2"
"","","Frost Atronach",Neutral,50,"The frost atronach is a powerful Daedric summoning associated with elemental frost.","The frost atronach is a powerful Daedric summoning associated with elemental frost.","MorroDefaultQuest_1frostSatronach_003212b9_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Crystalline elemental frost compounds called frost salts may be salvaged from the remains of banished frost atronachs.","Crystalline elemental frost compounds called frost salts may be salvaged from the remains of banished frost atronachs.","MorroDefaultQuest_1frostSatronach_003212b9_2"
"","","Storm Atronach",Neutral,50,"The storm atronach is a powerful Daedric summoning associated with elemental lightning.","The storm atronach is a powerful Daedric summoning associated with elemental lightning.","MorroDefaultQuest_1stormSatronach_003212bb_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Crystalline elemental shock compounds called shock salts may be salvaged from the remains of banished storm atronachs.","Crystalline elemental shock compounds called shock salts may be salvaged from the remains of banished storm atronachs.","MorroDefaultQuest_1stormSatronach_003212bb_2"
"","","Disintegration",Neutral,50,"There are only two common disintegration spells: weapon eater and armor eater. Each causes the affected item to become worn and less effective.","There are only two common disintegration spells: weapon eater and armor eater. Each causes the affected item to become worn and less effective.","MorroDefaultQuest_1disintegration_00321320_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Neither can actually cause an item to cease to exist, but each can reduce its target's effectiveness so much that it becomes completely useless until repaired.","Neither can actually cause an item to cease to exist, but each can reduce its target's effectiveness so much that it becomes completely useless until repaired.","MorroDefaultQuest_1disintegration_00321320_2"
"","","Restore Spells",Neutral,50,"Restore spells restore fundamental attributes reduced by attribute-damaging magical effects.","Restore spells restore fundamental attributes reduced by attribute-damaging magical effects.","MorroDefaultQuest_1restoreSspells_00321327_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"These spells are the only means of restoring attributes injured in this fashion.","These spells are the only means of restoring attributes injured in this fashion.","MorroDefaultQuest_1restoreSspells_00321327_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The most common restoration spells of this kind are: restore agility, restore endurance, restore fatigue, restore health, restore intelligence, restore luck, restore personality, restore speed, restore strength, restore willpower, and restore spell points.","The most common restoration spells of this kind are: restore agility, restore endurance, restore fatigue, restore health, restore intelligence, restore luck, restore personality, restore speed, restore strength, restore willpower, and restore spell points.","MorroDefaultQuest_1restoreSspells_00321327_3"
"","","Fortify Spells",Neutral,50,"Fortify spells temporarily increase fundamental attributes for the duration of the spell effects.","Fortify spells temporarily increase fundamental attributes for the duration of the spell effects.","MorroDefaultQuest_1fortifySspells_0032132e_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The most common restoration spells of this kind are: nimbleness, fortitude, vigor, vitality, wisdom, jack of trades, charisma, feet of notorgo, powerwell, orc strength, and iron will.","The most common restoration spells of this kind are: nimbleness, fortitude, vigor, vitality, wisdom, jack of trades, charisma, feet of notorgo, powerwell, orc strength, and iron will.","MorroDefaultQuest_1fortifySspells_0032132e_2"
"","","Golden Saints",Neutral,50,"These magical winged females are spawn of Sheogorath. Their hearts have modest magical properties.","These magical winged females are spawn of Sheogorath. Their hearts have modest magical properties.","MorroDefaultQuest_1goldenSsaints_0032197d_1"
"","","Latest Rumors",Neutral,50,"Master Aryon has been trying to talk some of the reclusive Telvanni into joining the Council.","Master Aryon has been trying to talk some of the reclusive Telvanni into joining the Council.","MorroDefaultQuest_1latestSrumors_0032163e_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I think he may be planning to challenge the Archmagister.","I think he may be planning to challenge the Archmagister.","MorroDefaultQuest_1latestSrumors_0032163e_2"
"","","Vulnerability",Neutral,50,"Vulnerability spells make natural and supernatural creatures more vulnerable to magics based on the elemental forces of fire, frost, magica, poison, and shock, reducing the chance that a victim will avoid suffering the effects of all or part of a magical attack.","Vulnerability spells make natural and supernatural creatures more vulnerable to magics based on the elemental forces of fire, frost, magica, poison, and shock, reducing the chance that a victim will avoid suffering the effects of all or part of a magical attack.","MorroDefaultQuest_1vulnerability_0032169e_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The most common of these destruction spells are: weakness to fire, weakness to frost, weakness to shock, weakness to magicka, and weakness to poison.","The most common of these destruction spells are: weakness to fire, weakness to frost, weakness to shock, weakness to magicka, and weakness to poison.","MorroDefaultQuest_1vulnerability_0032169e_2"
"","","Resist Spells",Neutral,50,"Resist spells increase the subject's ability to resist the hostile effects of a variety of malign influences.","Resist spells increase the subject's ability to resist the hostile effects of a variety of malign influences.","MorroDefaultQuest_1resistSspells_003216a5_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The most common restoration spells of this kind are: resist fire, resist frost, resist shock, resist magicka, resist common disease, resist blight disease, resist poison, and resist paralysis.","The most common restoration spells of this kind are: resist fire, resist frost, resist shock, resist magicka, resist common disease, resist blight disease, resist poison, and resist paralysis.","MorroDefaultQuest_1resistSspells_003216a5_2"
"","","Lame Corprus",Neutral,50,"The lame corprus is a deformed, deranged victim of corprus disease.","The lame corprus is a deformed, deranged victim of corprus disease.","MorroDefaultQuest_1lameScorprus_00321c40_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Aggressive and dangerous, they carry corprus disease, a deadly disease profoundly affecting a victim's mind and body.","Aggressive and dangerous, they carry corprus disease, a deadly disease profoundly affecting a victim's mind and body.","MorroDefaultQuest_1lameScorprus_00321c40_2"
"","","Intelligence",Neutral,50,"A creature's intelligence is its property of reasoning, analysis, and retention of facts and experience.","A creature's intelligence is its property of reasoning, analysis, and retention of facts and experience.","MorroDefaultQuest_1intelligence_00321c8e_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Other than its critical utility in problem-solving, this property is most important for the comprehension and manipulation of the arcane forces associated with magic, and creatures with high intelligence are proven to have greater capacity to cast larger and more powerful spell effects.","Other than its critical utility in problem-solving, this property is most important for the comprehension and manipulation of the arcane forces associated with magic, and creatures with high intelligence are proven to have greater capacity to cast larger and more powerful spell effects.","MorroDefaultQuest_1intelligence_00321c8e_2"
"","","Ash Vampire",Neutral,50,"Ash vampires are immortal magical beings of vast powers.","Ash vampires are immortal magical beings of vast powers.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ashSvampire_00321e61_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Close kin and loyal lieutenants of the Devil Dagoth Ur, they partake of his supernatural vitality.","Close kin and loyal lieutenants of the Devil Dagoth Ur, they partake of his supernatural vitality.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ashSvampire_00321e61_2"
"","","Cure Spells",Neutral,50,"Cure spells remove diseases, poisons, and incapacitation spell effects from the victim.","Cure spells remove diseases, poisons, and incapacitation spell effects from the victim.","MorroDefaultQuest_1cureSspells_00321f11_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The most common restoration spells of this kind are: cure common disease, cure blight disease, cure poison, and cure paralysis.","The most common restoration spells of this kind are: cure common disease, cure blight disease, cure poison, and cure paralysis.","MorroDefaultQuest_1cureSspells_00321f11_2"
"","","Personality",Neutral,50,"A creature's personality is its property of exciting the emotions of interest, trust, and loyalty in other creatures.","A creature's personality is its property of exciting the emotions of interest, trust, and loyalty in other creatures.","MorroDefaultQuest_1personality_00321f18_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"For example, a creature with a powerful personality is more able to persuade and influence other creatures through speech, gesture, and demeanor.","For example, a creature with a powerful personality is more able to persuade and influence other creatures through speech, gesture, and demeanor.","MorroDefaultQuest_1personality_00321f18_2"
"","","Ash Zombie",Neutral,50,"The ash zombie is a humanoid creature transformed by a mysterious force into a deranged beast.","The ash zombie is a humanoid creature transformed by a mysterious force into a deranged beast.","MorroDefaultQuest_1AshSZombie_0032232f_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Though their skulls are apparently empty, these creatures are nonetheless intelligent, aggressive, and dangerous.","Though their skulls are apparently empty, these creatures are nonetheless intelligent, aggressive, and dangerous.","MorroDefaultQuest_1AshSZombie_0032232f_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Ash zombies are associated in some way with the Devil Dagoth Ur.","Ash zombies are associated in some way with the Devil Dagoth Ur.","MorroDefaultQuest_1AshSZombie_0032232f_3"
"","","Bad Daedra",Neutral,50,"The four Bad Daedra, according to the Temple, are Molag Bal, Malacath, Mehrunes Dagon, and Sheogorath.","The four Bad Daedra, according to the Temple, are Molag Bal, Malacath, Mehrunes Dagon, and Sheogorath.","MorroDefaultQuest_1BadSDaedra_003223e2_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Bad Daedra include Molag Bal's servant, the daedroth; Malacath's servant, the ogrim;","Bad Daedra include Molag Bal's servant, the daedroth; Malacath's servant, the ogrim;","MorroDefaultQuest_1BadSDaedra_003223e2_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Mehrunes Dagon's servant, the scamp, the dremora, and the clannfear; and Sheogorath's servant, the golden saint.","Mehrunes Dagon's servant, the scamp, the dremora, and the clannfear; and Sheogorath's servant, the golden saint.","MorroDefaultQuest_1BadSDaedra_003223e2_3"
"","","Ash Slave",Neutral,50,"The ash slave is a humanoid creature transformed by a mysterious force into a deranged beast. These creatures are aggressive and dangerous.","The ash slave is a humanoid creature transformed by a mysterious force into a deranged beast. These creatures are aggressive and dangerous.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ashSslave_0032250e_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Ash slaves are associated in some way with the Devil Dagoth Ur.","Ash slaves are associated in some way with the Devil Dagoth Ur.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ashSslave_0032250e_2"
"","","Clannfear",Neutral,50,"The clannfear is a fierce, green, lizardlike bipedal Daedric summoning. Daedra hearts have modest magical properties, and are prized by alchemists.","The clannfear is a fierce, green, lizardlike bipedal Daedric summoning. Daedra hearts have modest magical properties, and are prized by alchemists.","MorroDefaultQuest_1clannfear_00322510_1"
"","","Ash Ghoul",Neutral,50,"The ash ghoul is a distorted, half-human, half-beast creature transformed by a mysterious force into a powerful magical being.","The ash ghoul is a distorted, half-human, half-beast creature transformed by a mysterious force into a powerful magical being.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ashSghoul_0032251a_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Ash ghouls are highly intelligent, aggressive, and dangerous. Ash ghouls are associated in some way with the Devil Dagoth Ur.","Ash ghouls are highly intelligent, aggressive, and dangerous. Ash ghouls are associated in some way with the Devil Dagoth Ur.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ashSghoul_0032251a_2"
"","","Atronachs",Neutral,50,"Atronachs encountered here are of three elemental domains: flame atronachs, or fire daedra; frost atronachs, or frost daedra;","Atronachs encountered here are of three elemental domains: flame atronachs, or fire daedra; frost atronachs, or frost daedra;","MorroDefaultQuest_1atronachs_0032251c_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"and storm atronachs, also called storm daedra.","and storm atronachs, also called storm daedra.","MorroDefaultQuest_1atronachs_0032251c_2"
"","","Endurance",Neutral,50,"A creature's endurance is its property of sustained expenditure of physical energy and its resistance to bodily injury.","A creature's endurance is its property of sustained expenditure of physical energy and its resistance to bodily injury.","MorroDefaultQuest_1endurance_00322607_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"A creature with greater endurance can withstand long periods of physical exertion without suffering from exhaustion, and is less likely to suffer permanent harm or death from disease or physical injuries.","A creature with greater endurance can withstand long periods of physical exertion without suffering from exhaustion, and is less likely to suffer permanent harm or death from disease or physical injuries.","MorroDefaultQuest_1endurance_00322607_2"
"","","Willpower",Neutral,50,"A creature's willpower is its property of maintaining its purpose and identify in the face of hardship and malign natural and supernatural forces.","A creature's willpower is its property of maintaining its purpose and identify in the face of hardship and malign natural and supernatural forces.","MorroDefaultQuest_1willpower_0032260e_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"A creature with strong willpower is better able to resist the effects of hostile spells cast upon it.","A creature with strong willpower is better able to resist the effects of hostile spells cast upon it.","MorroDefaultQuest_1willpower_0032260e_2"
"","","Daedroth",Neutral,50,"The daedroth are the crocodile-headed Daedric minions of the Daedra Lord Molag Bal.","The daedroth are the crocodile-headed Daedric minions of the Daedra Lord Molag Bal.","MorroDefaultQuest_1daedroth_003227f5_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Daedra hearts have modest magical properties, and are also available at reasonable prices and with considerably less excitement from alchemists.","Daedra hearts have modest magical properties, and are also available at reasonable prices and with considerably less excitement from alchemists.","MorroDefaultQuest_1daedroth_003227f5_2"
"","","Strength",Neutral,50,"A creature's strength is its property of efficiently lifting, carrying, and manipulating objects.","A creature's strength is its property of efficiently lifting, carrying, and manipulating objects.","MorroDefaultQuest_1strength_0032282f_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"A stronger creature can carry a greater weight of armor and equipment and strike more powerful blows with hands and weapons.","A stronger creature can carry a greater weight of armor and equipment and strike more powerful blows with hands and weapons.","MorroDefaultQuest_1strength_0032282f_2"
"","","Dremora",Neutral,50,"The Dremora are a class of intelligent, powerful war spirits in the service of the Daedra Lord Mehrunes Dagon.","The Dremora are a class of intelligent, powerful war spirits in the service of the Daedra Lord Mehrunes Dagon.","MorroDefaultQuest_1dremora_0032291c_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Daedra hearts have modest magical properties.","Daedra hearts have modest magical properties.","MorroDefaultQuest_1dremora_0032291c_2"
"","","Fatigue",Neutral,50,"A creature's fatigue is a measure of its capacity for extended physical exertion.","A creature's fatigue is a measure of its capacity for extended physical exertion.","MorroDefaultQuest_1fatigue_003229be_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The greater a creature's fatigue attribute, the longer it can run, swim, and fight.","The greater a creature's fatigue attribute, the longer it can run, swim, and fight.","MorroDefaultQuest_1fatigue_003229be_2"
"","","Magicka",Neutral,50,"A creature's magicka is a measure of its reserves of supernatural energies.","A creature's magicka is a measure of its reserves of supernatural energies.","MorroDefaultQuest_1magicka_00322a87_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Spellcasting creatures expend supernatural energies from their reservoirs when they create magical effects.","Spellcasting creatures expend supernatural energies from their reservoirs when they create magical effects.","MorroDefaultQuest_1magicka_00322a87_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"This reservoir is replenished by resting and by other arcane methods.","This reservoir is replenished by resting and by other arcane methods.","MorroDefaultQuest_1magicka_00322a87_3"
"","","Hunger",Neutral,50,"The hunger is one of the many voracious servants of the Daedra Lord Boethiah. Daedra hearts have modest magical properties.","The hunger is one of the many voracious servants of the Daedra Lord Boethiah. Daedra hearts have modest magical properties.","MorroDefaultQuest_1hunger_00322c41_1"
"","","Health",Neutral,50,"A creature's health is a measure of its capacity to withstand physical punishment.","A creature's health is a measure of its capacity to withstand physical punishment.","MorroDefaultQuest_1health_00322c82_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"A creature with weak health succumbs easily to disease or injury, while a creature with exceptional health can endure and survive deadly diseases and injuries.","A creature with weak health succumbs easily to disease or injury, while a creature with exceptional health can endure and survive deadly diseases and injuries.","MorroDefaultQuest_1health_00322c82_2"
"","","Scamp",Neutral,50,"The scamp is a weak, cowardly servant of Mehrunes Dagon.","The scamp is a weak, cowardly servant of Mehrunes Dagon.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Scamp_00322dbb_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Scamps may be summoned by conjurers, and their skin is sought by alchemists for its magical properties.","Scamps may be summoned by conjurers, and their skin is sought by alchemists for its magical properties.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Scamp_00322dbb_2"
"","","Ogrim",Neutral,50,"Ogrim are massive, powerful, dimly intelligent servants of the Daedra Lord Malacath.","Ogrim are massive, powerful, dimly intelligent servants of the Daedra Lord Malacath.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ogrim_00322e0d_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Daedra hearts have modest magical properties, but you have to dig through a lot of Daedra to get at an ogrim's heart.","Daedra hearts have modest magical properties, but you have to dig through a lot of Daedra to get at an ogrim's heart.","MorroDefaultQuest_1ogrim_00322e0d_2"
"","","Speed",Neutral,50,"A creature's speed is its property of rapid physical articulation and body movements.","A creature's speed is its property of rapid physical articulation and body movements.","MorroDefaultQuest_1speed_00322d54_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"A speedy creature is able to perform all physical actions, from equipping a weapon to running long distances, in shorter periods of time.","A speedy creature is able to perform all physical actions, from equipping a weapon to running long distances, in shorter periods of time.","MorroDefaultQuest_1speed_00322d54_2"
"","","Luck",Neutral,50,"A creature's luck is its property of aligning itself with the subtle currents of fate and destiny.","A creature's luck is its property of aligning itself with the subtle currents of fate and destiny.","MorroDefaultQuest_1luck_00322e70_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"This is the most subtle of fundamental attributes, and can only be judged by observation of the favorable and unfavorable outcomes of a creature's actions over a long period of time.","This is the most subtle of fundamental attributes, and can only be judged by observation of the favorable and unfavorable outcomes of a creature's actions over a long period of time.","MorroDefaultQuest_1luck_00322e70_2"
