Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Slander",Neutral,50,"I spoke nothing but the truth. The Legion is just a mob of blunt-eared apes playing at being soldiers. Is it just your cowardice?","I spoke nothing but the truth. The Legion is just a mob of blunt-eared apes playing at being soldiers. Is it just your cowardice?","fbmwILFalseOrdinator_1slander_00322ae7_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Or the incompetence of your so-called Knights? Or is it just the way you smell?","Or the incompetence of your so-called Knights? Or is it just the way you smell?","fbmwILFalseOrdinator_1slander_00322ae7_2"
