Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Caius Cosades",Neutral,50,"Interesting old fellow. Been in Balmora a long time, since before the District reorganization.","Interesting old fellow. Been in Balmora a long time, since before the District reorganization.","fbmwMQ01_1CaiusSCosades_003217ce_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Been in some trouble, but he apparently knows some people. Goes off for a while, then comes back.","Been in some trouble, but he apparently knows some people. Goes off for a while, then comes back.","fbmwMQ01_1CaiusSCosades_003217ce_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"He's a veteran, I think -- has friends over at Fort Moonmoth. Don't know where he gets his money, but I wouldn't be surprised if it wasn't legal.","He's a veteran, I think -- has friends over at Fort Moonmoth. Don't know where he gets his money, but I wouldn't be surprised if it wasn't legal.","fbmwMQ01_1CaiusSCosades_003217ce_3"
