Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Latest Rumors",Neutral,50,"Do you know what the Legion does with the stolen goods they take off their prisoners? They stick them in evidence chests, right there in the forts.","Do you know what the Legion does with the stolen goods they take off their prisoners? They stick them in evidence chests, right there in the forts.","MorroDefaultQuest_1latestSrumors_00321625_1"
