Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Someone in Particular",Neutral,50,"Thongar the Nord runs Thongar's Tradehouse, the Redoran-style building over to the east. The rest of these shacks are fisherman's homes.","Thongar the Nord runs Thongar's Tradehouse, the Redoran-style building over to the east. The rest of these shacks are fisherman's homes.","MorroDefaultQuest_1someoneSinSparticular_003206b3_1"
"","","Latest Rumors",Neutral,50,"A group of hard cases came through here recently.","A group of hard cases came through here recently.","MorroDefaultQuest_1latestSrumors_00321605_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And an old druegher says he's seen people putting goods ashore from a small boat on the coast northeast of Khuul.","And an old druegher says he's seen people putting goods ashore from a small boat on the coast northeast of Khuul.","MorroDefaultQuest_1latestSrumors_00321605_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I think someone has a smugglers operation in a cave nearby where they're stashing the stuff.","I think someone has a smugglers operation in a cave nearby where they're stashing the stuff.","MorroDefaultQuest_1latestSrumors_00321605_3"
