Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"You! You killed my mother!","You! You killed my mother!","fbmwTR09_GREETING_00f8b92f_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"You! You killed my father!","You! You killed my father!","fbmwTR09_GREETING_00f8b930_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I'm true to my word. I said I would not discuss King Helseth in 'The Common Tongue'. That's what you wanted, and that's what you've got. Now, if you'll excuse me, I have work to do...","I'm true to my word. I said I would not discuss King Helseth in 'The Common Tongue'. That's what you wanted, and that's what you've got. Now, if you'll excuse me, I have work to do...","fbmwTR09_GREETING_00f8b931_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I said you could go. So go. But I warn you -- don't touch anything here, and don't interfere with myself or my colleagues, or you will not leave here alive. Now, if you'll excuse me, I have work to do....","I said you could go. So go. But I warn you -- don't touch anything here, and don't interfere with myself or my colleagues, or you will not leave here alive. Now, if you'll excuse me, I have work to do....","fbmwTR09_GREETING_00f8b932_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"What are you doing here? And may I suggest you make your answer very clear, because this office and what we do here is a well-kept-secret. And we wish to keep it a secret, even if it means that you do not leave here alive.","What are you doing here? And may I suggest you make your answer very clear, because this office and what we do here is a well-kept-secret. And we wish to keep it a secret, even if it means that you do not leave here alive.","fbmwTR09_GREETING_00f8b933_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"What are you doing here? And may I suggest you make your answer very clear, because this office and what we do here is a well-kept-secret.","What are you doing here? And may I suggest you make your answer very clear, because this office and what we do here is a well-kept-secret.","fbmwTRDBAttack_GREETING_0001e4ff_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And we wish to keep it a secret, even if it means that you do not leave her alive.","And we wish to keep it a secret, even if it means that you do not leave her alive.","fbmwTRDBAttack_GREETING_0001e4ff_2"
"","","King Llethan's death",Neutral,50,"I've presented my views on this subject elsewhere. You're welcome to examine them at your leisure.","I've presented my views on this subject elsewhere. You're welcome to examine them at your leisure.","fbmwTR05People_1KingSLlethanAsSdeath_003207a4_1"
"","","Anonymous Writer",Neutral,50,"Do I know an anonymous writer? No comment.","Do I know an anonymous writer? No comment.","fbmwTR09_1anonymousSwriter_00320dc8_1"
"","","Trels Varis",Neutral,50,"That's me.","That's me.","fbmwTR09_1TrelsSVaris_00321da4_1"
"","","You will stop libelling the king.",Neutral,50,"I haven't printed lies about King Helseth in 'The Common Tongue'. I've only printed the truth. And I intend to keep on printing the truth in 'The Common Tongue' -- unless you think you can stop me.","I haven't printed lies about King Helseth in 'The Common Tongue'. I've only printed the truth. And I intend to keep on printing the truth in 'The Common Tongue' -- unless you think you can stop me.","fbmwTR09_fbmwtr09Lies_00f8bca9_1"
"","","Excuse me. I'm just an honest burglar",Neutral,50,"I see. You've made a serious mistake. I don't approve of your trade -- but I understand that a desperate person -- or imprudently greedy person -- ","I see. You've made a serious mistake. I don't approve of your trade -- but I understand that a desperate person -- or imprudently greedy person --","fbmwTR09_fbmwtr09burglar_00f8bcab_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"may turn his hand to crime without being truly evil. Very well. You may go. I'd like to preserve our secret office... but I won't kill you to do it. ","may turn his hand to crime without being truly evil. Very well. You may go. I'd like to preserve our secret office... but I won't kill you to do it.","fbmwTR09_fbmwtr09burglar_00f8bcab_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Oh, well. Since our offices are no longer secret, we'll have to relocate immediately. But don't touch anything here, and don't interfere with myself or my colleagues, or you will not leave here alive.","Oh, well. Since our offices are no longer secret, we'll have to relocate immediately. But don't touch anything here, and don't interfere with myself or my colleagues, or you will not leave here alive.","fbmwTR09_fbmwtr09burglar_00f8bcab_3"
"","","Excuse me. I'm just an honest burglar",Neutral,50,"I see. You've made a serious mistake. I don't approve of your trade -- but I understand that a desperate person -- or imprudently greedy person -- ","I see. You've made a serious mistake. I don't approve of your trade -- but I understand that a desperate person -- or imprudently greedy person --","fbmwTRDBAttack_fbmwtr09burglar_0001e500_1"
"","","",Neutral,50," may turn his hand to crime without being truly evil. Very well. You may go. I'd like to preserve our secret office...","may turn his hand to crime without being truly evil. Very well. You may go. I'd like to preserve our secret office...","fbmwTRDBAttack_fbmwtr09burglar_0001e500_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"but I won't kill you to do it. Just go... and keep your mouth shut.","but I won't kill you to do it. Just go... and keep your mouth shut.","fbmwTRDBAttack_fbmwtr09burglar_0001e500_3"
"","","I'm looking for the Eye of Argonia.",Neutral,50,"Congratulations. You have produced an original and entertaining excuse. Completely unbelievable, of course, but none the worse for that.","Congratulations. You have produced an original and entertaining excuse. Completely unbelievable, of course, but none the worse for that.","fbmwTR09_fbmwtr09Eye_00f8bcad_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Never heard a believable excuse before, anyway. Very well. You may go. I'd like to preserve our secret office... but I won't kill you to do it.","Never heard a believable excuse before, anyway. Very well. You may go. I'd like to preserve our secret office... but I won't kill you to do it.","fbmwTR09_fbmwtr09Eye_00f8bcad_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Oh, well. Since our offices are no longer secret, we'll have to relocate immediately. But don't touch anything here, and don't interfere with myself or my colleagues, or you will not leave here alive.","Oh, well. Since our offices are no longer secret, we'll have to relocate immediately. But don't touch anything here, and don't interfere with myself or my colleagues, or you will not leave here alive.","fbmwTR09_fbmwtr09Eye_00f8bcad_3"
"","","I'm looking for the Eye of Argonia.",Neutral,50,"Congratulations. You have produced an original and entertaining excuse. Completely unbelievable, of course, but none the worse for that.","Congratulations. You have produced an original and entertaining excuse. Completely unbelievable, of course, but none the worse for that.","fbmwTRDBAttack_fbmwtr09Eye_0001e501_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Never heard a believable excuse before, anyway. Very well. You may go. I'd like to preserve our secret office...","Never heard a believable excuse before, anyway. Very well. You may go. I'd like to preserve our secret office...","fbmwTRDBAttack_fbmwtr09Eye_0001e501_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But I won't kill you to do it. Just go... and keep your mouth shut.","But I won't kill you to do it. Just go... and keep your mouth shut.","fbmwTRDBAttack_fbmwtr09Eye_0001e501_3"
"","","My mistake. I'll leave. Honest.",Neutral,50,"I know you by reputation. You've done some remarkable things. Very well. You may go. I'd like to preserve our secret office... but I won't kill you to do it.","I know you by reputation. You've done some remarkable things. Very well. You may go. I'd like to preserve our secret office... but I won't kill you to do it.","fbmwTR09_fbmwtr09SirRobinApproach_00f8bcaf_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Oh, well. Since our offices are no longer secret, we'll have to relocate immediately. But don't touch anything here, and don't interfere with myself or my colleagues, or you will not leave here alive.","Oh, well. Since our offices are no longer secret, we'll have to relocate immediately. But don't touch anything here, and don't interfere with myself or my colleagues, or you will not leave here alive.","fbmwTR09_fbmwtr09SirRobinApproach_00f8bcaf_2"
"","","My mistake. I'll leave. Honest.",Neutral,50,"I'm afraid not. The only way to be sure of preserving our secret is to seal your lips -- permanently. I regret the loss of life -- but it is the risk you run when you break into someone's secret office.","I'm afraid not. The only way to be sure of preserving our secret is to seal your lips -- permanently. I regret the loss of life -- but it is the risk you run when you break into someone's secret office.","fbmwTR09_fbmwtr09SirRobinApproach_00f8bcb0_1"
"","","My mistake. I'll leave. Honest.",Neutral,50,"'Honest.' So you expect me to trust you? My experiences with trusting adventurers like you have been disappointing in the past.","'Honest.' So you expect me to trust you? My experiences with trusting adventurers like you have been disappointing in the past.","fbmwTRDBAttack_fbmwtr09SirRobinApproach_0001e502_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But... this time, you may go. I'd like to preserve our secret office... but I won't kill you to do it. Just go... and keep your mouth shut.","But... this time, you may go. I'd like to preserve our secret office... but I won't kill you to do it. Just go... and keep your mouth shut.","fbmwTRDBAttack_fbmwtr09SirRobinApproach_0001e502_2"
"","","I think killing you will stop you.",Neutral,50,"Of course you're right. And of course if I kill you first, I preserve the secret of my hidden office. The choice is easy.","Of course you're right. And of course if I kill you first, I preserve the secret of my hidden office. The choice is easy.","fbmwTR09_fbmwtr09Kill_00f8bcb2_1"
"","","What about a gift of 1000 gold?",Neutral,50,"You are not a very good judge of character. I am a man of principle, and will not hold my common tongue for a payment of gold. And of course if I kill you first, I preserve the secret of my hidden office.","You are not a very good judge of character. I am a man of principle, and will not hold my common tongue for a payment of gold. And of course if I kill you first, I preserve the secret of my hidden office.","fbmwTR09_fbmwtr09gift_00f8bcb4_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The choice is easy.","The choice is easy.","fbmwTR09_fbmwtr09gift_00f8bcb4_2"
"","","I'll give the Widows Fund 3000 gold.",Neutral,50,"Hmm. You are a shrewd judge of character. I am a man of principle, and will not hold my common tongue for a payment of gold. But I know what benefits gold can do if it is used in a good cause.","Hmm. You are a shrewd judge of character. I am a man of principle, and will not hold my common tongue for a payment of gold. But I know what benefits gold can do if it is used in a good cause.","fbmwTR09_fbmwtr09Widows_00f8bcb6_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Very well. I will not discuss King Helseth in 'The Common Tongue'. You have my word. And I'll take your 3000 gold, and will contribute it to the Widows and Orphans Fund.","Very well. I will not discuss King Helseth in 'The Common Tongue'. You have my word. And I'll take your 3000 gold, and will contribute it to the Widows and Orphans Fund.","fbmwTR09_fbmwtr09Widows_00f8bcb6_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And now, if you'll excuse me, we'll have to relocate immediately, now that the secret of our office is spoiled.","And now, if you'll excuse me, we'll have to relocate immediately, now that the secret of our office is spoiled.","fbmwTR09_fbmwtr09Widows_00f8bcb6_3"
"","","I'll give the Widows Fund 3000 gold.",Neutral,50,"And you don't HAVE 3000 gold right now? I suppose you plan to get it to me 'right away'? Why don't I trust you? Well, thank you for your generous offer, but I'm afraid not. The only way to be sure of preserving our secret is to seal your lips -- permanently. ","And you don't HAVE 3000 gold right now? I suppose you plan to get it to me 'right away'? Why don't I trust you? Well, thank you for your generous offer, but I'm afraid not. The only way to be sure of preserving our secret is to seal your lips -- permanently.","fbmwTR09_fbmwtr09Widows_00f8bcb7_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I regret the loss of life -- but it is the risk you run when you break into someone's secret office.","I regret the loss of life -- but it is the risk you run when you break into someone's secret office.","fbmwTR09_fbmwtr09Widows_00f8bcb7_2"
"","","Stop, or I'll kill your parents.",Neutral,50,"Well. I must say, you've done your research. You've located Granny Varis and Gee-Pop Varis. I value truth -- but I value the lives of my parents more highly.","Well. I must say, you've done your research. You've located Granny Varis and Gee-Pop Varis. I value truth -- but I value the lives of my parents more highly.","fbmwTR09_fbmwtr09Parents_00f8bcb9_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Very well. I will not discuss King Helseth in 'The Common Tongue'. You have my word. And now, if you'll excuse me, we'll have to relocate immediately, now that the secret of our office is spoiled.","Very well. I will not discuss King Helseth in 'The Common Tongue'. You have my word. And now, if you'll excuse me, we'll have to relocate immediately, now that the secret of our office is spoiled.","fbmwTR09_fbmwtr09Parents_00f8bcb9_2"
