Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"He he!  Ha ha!  Can it be?  A visitor in my workshop?  How can I help you, my sweet?  I have candy treats to spare, if you come in search of happiness!","He he!  Ha ha!  Can it be?  A visitor in my workshop?  How can I help you, my sweet?  I have candy treats to spare, if you come in search of happiness!","fbmwBMMoonSugar_GREETING_0002a47a_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Ha ha!  What's this?  Why it's my little friend, come to pay Uncle Sweetshare a visit!  I've been a good boy! I promise!  He he he he he!","Ha ha!  What's this?  Why it's my little friend, come to pay Uncle Sweetshare a visit!  I've been a good boy! I promise!  He he he he he!","fbmwBMMoonSugar_GREETING_0002a47b_1"
"","","Moon Sugar Investigation",Neutral,50,"That Severia Gratius is so grumpy!  Maybe I should visit her next!  Because that's what I do!  I visit the sad and miserable and spread all the happiness I can!","That Severia Gratius is so grumpy!  Maybe I should visit her next!  Because that's what I do!  I visit the sad and miserable and spread all the happiness I can!","fbmwBMMoonSugar_1moonSsugarSinvestigation_00f8afe9_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"It is the way of Uncle Sweetshare, you see!  Now that Jeleen, there's a sad, sad boy.  His true love has disappeared, don't you know.  Very sad, very sad.","It is the way of Uncle Sweetshare, you see!  Now that Jeleen, there's a sad, sad boy.  His true love has disappeared, don't you know.  Very sad, very sad.","fbmwBMMoonSugar_1moonSsugarSinvestigation_00f8afe9_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"That's why I sang to him!  He needed something extra, something special!  Sugar and a song!  It cures all!","That's why I sang to him!  He needed something extra, something special!  Sugar and a song!  It cures all!","fbmwBMMoonSugar_1moonSsugarSinvestigation_00f8afe9_3"
"","","Uncle Sweetshare",Neutral,50,"That's me, you see!  Uncle Sweetshare!  Just like in the children's rhyme!  When I found that old song the lyrics moved me like nothing else in my life!","That's me, you see!  Uncle Sweetshare!  Just like in the children's rhyme!  When I found that old song the lyrics moved me like nothing else in my life!","fbmwBMMoonSugar_1UncleSSweetshare_00f8b038_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I knew at that moment who I truly was, and what I was meant to do!  So I had this workshop built!  I make treats here, you see!  Delicious treats with the special sugar!","I knew at that moment who I truly was, and what I was meant to do!  So I had this workshop built!  I make treats here, you see!  Delicious treats with the special sugar!","fbmwBMMoonSugar_1UncleSSweetshare_00f8b038_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Moon sugar!  He he, ha ha!  Then I spread my cheer throughout the land!  But it's all a secret!  Shhhhhhhh....","Moon sugar!  He he, ha ha!  Then I spread my cheer throughout the land!  But it's all a secret!  Shhhhhhhh....","fbmwBMMoonSugar_1UncleSSweetshare_00f8b038_3"
"","","Uncle Sweetshare",Neutral,50,"Why that's me!  At least...it used to be me.  I don't feel much like Uncle Sweetshare anymore, to tell you the truth!  Not without my white helm!  But that's just fine! Ha ha ha ha!","Why that's me!  At least...it used to be me.  I don't feel much like Uncle Sweetshare anymore, to tell you the truth!  Not without my white helm!  But that's just fine! Ha ha ha ha!","fbmwBMMoonSugar_1UncleSSweetshare_00f8b039_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Because I still have my scrumptious treats, with all the sugar I can eat!  He he he he he!","Because I still have my scrumptious treats, with all the sugar I can eat!  He he he he he!","fbmwBMMoonSugar_1UncleSSweetshare_00f8b039_2"
"","","Candy Treats",Neutral,50,"My candy treats are tasty, they are!  And filled with special sugar and love!  They bring happiness!  Happiness to everyone on Solstheim!","My candy treats are tasty, they are!  And filled with special sugar and love!  They bring happiness!  Happiness to everyone on Solstheim!","fbmwBMMoonSugar_1candyStreats_00f8b047_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"That's what I do, you see!  I give out my special sugary treats and spread happiness throughout the land!  It's difficult work, but oh so very rewarding!","That's what I do, you see!  I give out my special sugary treats and spread happiness throughout the land!  It's difficult work, but oh so very rewarding!","fbmwBMMoonSugar_1candyStreats_00f8b047_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"M'nashi certainly thought so.  Ahh, M'nashi, the dear lad....","M'nashi certainly thought so.  Ahh, M'nashi, the dear lad....","fbmwBMMoonSugar_1candyStreats_00f8b047_3"
"","","M'nashi",Neutral,50,"M'nashi was my assistant!  He helped me make my candy!  He so loved his sugar, M'nashi did.  Loved it a little too much, I'm afraid!","M'nashi was my assistant!  He helped me make my candy!  He so loved his sugar, M'nashi did.  Loved it a little too much, I'm afraid!","fbmwBMMoonSugar_1MAnashi_00f8b05d_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"He died, you see.  His, ah, sweet tooth got the better of him.  I buried him, just outside.  We had a lovely little ceremony.  The horkers came and sang for him, they did!","He died, you see.  His, ah, sweet tooth got the better of him.  I buried him, just outside.  We had a lovely little ceremony.  The horkers came and sang for him, they did!","fbmwBMMoonSugar_1MAnashi_00f8b05d_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"He he he!  Ha ha ha ha ha!","He he he!  Ha ha ha ha ha!","fbmwBMMoonSugar_1MAnashi_00f8b05d_3"
"","","You're mad. I must kill you.",Neutral,50,"He he he he he!  Mad?  Mad, you call me?  Oh no...it is you who are mad!  For how can anyone who doesn't recognize true happiness ever be considered sane?","He he he he he!  Mad?  Mad, you call me?  Oh no...it is you who are mad!  For how can anyone who doesn't recognize true happiness ever be considered sane?","fbmwBMMoonSugar_1UncleSSweetshare1_00f8b075_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Oh why oh why can't you people just be happy?  Well, let's get to it then!  He he he, ha ha!","Oh why oh why can't you people just be happy?  Well, let's get to it then!  He he he, ha ha!","fbmwBMMoonSugar_1UncleSSweetshare1_00f8b075_2"
"","","Stop sharing your sugar.",Neutral,50,"Give you my helm?  Stop sharing...stop sharing my sugar?  He...heh...ho...hmmm....  Distressing...most distressing....  But you WILL let me live?","Give you my helm?  Stop sharing...stop sharing my sugar?  He...heh...ho...hmmm....  Distressing...most distressing....  But you WILL let me live?","fbmwBMMoonSugar_1UncleSSweetshare2_00f8b076_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I do so love to live!  All right, then.  We have a deal!  Here's my white helm, and you have my promise I will not spread any more cheer!","I do so love to live!  All right, then.  We have a deal!  Here's my white helm, and you have my promise I will not spread any more cheer!","fbmwBMMoonSugar_1UncleSSweetshare2_00f8b076_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I will keep my candy all to myself!  That won't be so bad, will it? He he he he!  Ha ha ha!","I will keep my candy all to myself!  That won't be so bad, will it? He he he he!  Ha ha ha!","fbmwBMMoonSugar_1UncleSSweetshare2_00f8b076_3"
