Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Sculptor",Surprise,50,"A sculptor? Not going to find many around here. Art's not really at a premium, you know?","A sculptor? Not going to find many around here. Art's not really at a premium, you know?","fbmwDABoethiah_1sculptor_0001e12f_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"There's an orc in town who likes to carve up some stones, but I'm not about to buy his sculptures. He lives in Ghorak Manor with a bunch of other orcs. Odd ones, to be sure.","There's an orc in town who likes to carve up some stones, but I'm not about to buy his sculptures. He lives in Ghorak Manor with a bunch of other orcs. Odd ones, to be sure.","fbmwDABoethiah_1sculptor_0001e12f_2"
