Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Disgust,50,"I am Vistha-Kai, Warden of the Corprusarium. I am here to warn you: do not harm the inmates. ","I am Vistha-Kai, Warden of the Corprusarium. I am here to warn you: do not harm the inmates.","mwGreetingsUnique_GREETING_000033f0_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If you come to plunder the dungeon, you must endure their attacks, and take your chances with me, their Warden and Protector.","If you come to plunder the dungeon, you must endure their attacks, and take your chances with me, their Warden and Protector.","mwGreetingsUnique_GREETING_000033f0_2"
"","","GREETING",Disgust,50,"You have been warned. Do not harm the inmates of the Corprusarium. If you plan to plunder the dungeon, you must endure their attacks, and mine.","You have been warned. Do not harm the inmates of the Corprusarium. If you plan to plunder the dungeon, you must endure their attacks, and mine.","mwGreetingsUnique_GREETING_000033f1_1"
"","","Endure their attacks",Neutral,50,"Do not harm the inmates. I will not tolerate you adding to their suffering. Indeed, they are brutal and ferocious, and they will kill you if they can.","Do not harm the inmates. I will not tolerate you adding to their suffering. Indeed, they are brutal and ferocious, and they will kill you if they can.","MorroDefaultQuest_1endureStheirSattacks_00320762_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But you are their guests, and you may not harm them, or you will answer to me.","But you are their guests, and you may not harm them, or you will answer to me.","MorroDefaultQuest_1endureStheirSattacks_00320762_2"
"","","Plunder the dungeon",Neutral,50,"For his own amusement, Divayth Fyr permits thieves to test their skills by attempting to steal the treasures he keeps below in the Corprusarium.","For his own amusement, Divayth Fyr permits thieves to test their skills by attempting to steal the treasures he keeps below in the Corprusarium.","MorroDefaultQuest_1plunderStheSdungeon_00320855_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The dangers are fearful. The inmates are savage, and they carry the most terrible disease on Tamriel.","The dangers are fearful. The inmates are savage, and they carry the most terrible disease on Tamriel.","MorroDefaultQuest_1plunderStheSdungeon_00320855_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The treasures themselves are guarded by traps and terrors. And the guards, myself chief among them, will take great delight in trying to kill you.","The treasures themselves are guarded by traps and terrors. And the guards, myself chief among them, will take great delight in trying to kill you.","MorroDefaultQuest_1plunderStheSdungeon_00320855_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Those are the rules. Abide by them ,or leave.","Those are the rules. Abide by them ,or leave.","MorroDefaultQuest_1plunderStheSdungeon_00320855_4"
"","","Yagrum Bagarn",Neutral,50,"Yagrum Bagarn is in the bowels of the Corprusarium. Pass through the gate and go straight across to the next door. He rides in a four-legged cart.","Yagrum Bagarn is in the bowels of the Corprusarium. Pass through the gate and go straight across to the next door. He rides in a four-legged cart.","MorroDefaultQuest_1YagrumSBagarn_00aa5330_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"He's not as dangerous as the other corprus victims. I doubt he'll give you any trouble.","He's not as dangerous as the other corprus victims. I doubt he'll give you any trouble.","MorroDefaultQuest_1YagrumSBagarn_00aa5330_2"
"","","Corprusarium",Neutral,50,"Lord Fyr shelters and maintains the victims of corprus disease here in the Corprusarium.","Lord Fyr shelters and maintains the victims of corprus disease here in the Corprusarium.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Corprusarium_00321bed_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"He does them a great service, because no other could or would help them.","He does them a great service, because no other could or would help them.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Corprusarium_00321bed_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"He also does the world a great service by keeping them here where they can do no harm to others.","He also does the world a great service by keeping them here where they can do no harm to others.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Corprusarium_00321bed_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The inmates are sad, distorted monsters, angry and cruel, and their sufferings are great, but they still live and feel, and I honor Lord Fyr's care and compassion for them.","The inmates are sad, distorted monsters, angry and cruel, and their sufferings are great, but they still live and feel, and I honor Lord Fyr's care and compassion for them.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Corprusarium_00321bed_4"
"","","Warden",Neutral,50,"I am the guardian and peacekeeper of the Corprusarium.","I am the guardian and peacekeeper of the Corprusarium.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Warden_00322bf8_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I have spent long years in service to Lord Fyr, first as a slave, then as a free hireling, and now as a friend and partner.","I have spent long years in service to Lord Fyr, first as a slave, then as a free hireling, and now as a friend and partner.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Warden_00322bf8_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"He has been kind and generous to me, and I take his interests, and the interests of those he shelters, to heart.","He has been kind and generous to me, and I take his interests, and the interests of those he shelters, to heart.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Warden_00322bf8_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The treasures of his dungeon are open to sport, according to Lord Fyr's whim, and you're welcome to try to steal them.","The treasures of his dungeon are open to sport, according to Lord Fyr's whim, and you're welcome to try to steal them.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Warden_00322bf8_4"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But I, too, find great sport in hunting thieves.","But I, too, find great sport in hunting thieves.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Warden_00322bf8_5"
