Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Good luck on the mountain. Go with Kynareth. And don't forget my old lucky coin.","Good luck on the mountain. Go with Kynareth. And don't forget my old lucky coin.","fbmwICImperialVeteran_GREETING_0002a4eb_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Hello. They call me Wulf. What brings you to Ghostgate?","Hello. They call me Wulf. What brings you to Ghostgate?","MorroDefaultQuest_GREETING_0002a4ec_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Right. I'm Wulf, like I said. I was wondering what you were doing here in Ghostgate.","Right. I'm Wulf, like I said. I was wondering what you were doing here in Ghostgate.","MorroDefaultQuest_GREETING_0002a4ed_1"
"","","Buoyant Armigers",Neutral,50,"The light-hearted Buoyant Armigers are rivals of the more solemn Ordinators in service to the Temple.","The light-hearted Buoyant Armigers are rivals of the more solemn Ordinators in service to the Temple.","MorroDefaultQuest_1BuoyantSArmigers_00320d26_1"
"","","Buoyant Armigers",Neutral,50,"The Buoyant Armigers serve the Temple as champions and knights-errant.","The Buoyant Armigers serve the Temple as champions and knights-errant.","MorroDefaultQuest_1BuoyantSArmigers_00320d27_1"
"","","Buoyant Armigers",Neutral,50,"The Buoyant Armigers pattern themselves on Lord Vivec's heroic spirit of exploration and adventure, and they emulate his mastery of the varied arts of personal combat, chivalric courtesy, and subtle verse.","The Buoyant Armigers pattern themselves on Lord Vivec's heroic spirit of exploration and adventure, and they emulate his mastery of the varied arts of personal combat, chivalric courtesy, and subtle verse.","MorroDefaultQuest_1BuoyantSArmigers_00320d28_1"
"","","Buoyant Armigers",Neutral,50,"The Buoyant Armigers is an small military order of the Temple, exclusively dedicated to and answering to Lord Vivec.","The Buoyant Armigers is an small military order of the Temple, exclusively dedicated to and answering to Lord Vivec.","MorroDefaultQuest_1BuoyantSArmigers_00320d29_1"
"","","Poor old Emperor",Neutral,50,"The Emperor is getting old. Don't know how much longer he'll hang on. So is the whole Empire, for that matter. Getting old, that is.","The Emperor is getting old. Don't know how much longer he'll hang on. So is the whole Empire, for that matter. Getting old, that is.","MorroDefaultQuest_1poorSoldSEmperor_00320e22_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The Emperor and the legions have held the Empire together for hundreds of years. It's been a good thing, by and large.","The Emperor and the legions have held the Empire together for hundreds of years. It's been a good thing, by and large.","MorroDefaultQuest_1poorSoldSEmperor_00320e22_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But maybe it's time for a change. Time for something young and new. What? No idea. Because I'm old. Old dog doesn't get new ideas.","But maybe it's time for a change. Time for something young and new. What? No idea. Because I'm old. Old dog doesn't get new ideas.","MorroDefaultQuest_1poorSoldSEmperor_00320e22_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But maybe young folks like you should try some new ideas. I don't know. Could be messy. But change is never pretty.","But maybe young folks like you should try some new ideas. I don't know. Could be messy. But change is never pretty.","MorroDefaultQuest_1poorSoldSEmperor_00320e22_4"
"","","Ordinators",Neutral,50,"The Order of the Inquisition identifies and suppresses heresy among priests and laymen.","The Order of the Inquisition identifies and suppresses heresy among priests and laymen.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Ordinators_0032239b_1"
"","","Ordinators",Neutral,50,"The Order of Doctrine and Ordination are militant scholars.","The Order of Doctrine and Ordination are militant scholars.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Ordinators_003223a0_1"
"","","Ordinators",Neutral,50,"The Order of War fights the enemies of the Temple; most War Ordinators are stationed near Red Mountain.","The Order of War fights the enemies of the Temple; most War Ordinators are stationed near Red Mountain.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Ordinators_003223a5_1"
"","","Ordinators",Neutral,50,"The Order of the Watch provides guards for temples and shrines.","The Order of the Watch provides guards for temples and shrines.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Ordinators_003223aa_1"
"","","Ordinators",Neutral,50,"Grandmaster Berel Sala is the chief Ordinator on Vvardenfell.","Grandmaster Berel Sala is the chief Ordinator on Vvardenfell.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Ordinators_003223af_1"
"","","Ordinators",Neutral,50,"The four orders of Ordinators answer to the Alma Rula in Almalexia.","The four orders of Ordinators answer to the Alma Rula in Almalexia.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Ordinators_003223b4_1"
"","","Ordinators",Neutral,50,"The Ordinators are the holy guards and soldiers of the Temple.","The Ordinators are the holy guards and soldiers of the Temple.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Ordinators_003223b9_1"
"","","Ghostgate",Neutral,50,"This is a helluva place. Why are you here?","This is a helluva place. Why are you here?","fbmwICImperialVeteran_1Ghostgate_00322584_1"
"","","Wulf",Neutral,50,"Wulf. That's me.","Wulf. That's me.","fbmwICImperialVeteran_1Wulf_00322eb5_1"
"","","I'll take the lucky coin to Dagoth Ur",Neutral,50,"That's very kind of you. Here's the coin. I've had it with me a long time, and it's always brought me luck.","That's very kind of you. Here's the coin. I've had it with me a long time, and it's always brought me luck.","fbmwICImperialVeteran_1Ghostgate4_00323581_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But I have no more use for it, and I'd like to pass it on to somebody younger. Somebody going places I can't go anymore.","But I have no more use for it, and I'd like to pass it on to somebody younger. Somebody going places I can't go anymore.","fbmwICImperialVeteran_1Ghostgate4_00323581_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Your generation's shaper of history... an engine of destiny. That coin will bring you luck on the mountain. I promise.","Your generation's shaper of history... an engine of destiny. That coin will bring you luck on the mountain. I promise.","fbmwICImperialVeteran_1Ghostgate4_00323581_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"'For Emperor and Empire,' as we say in the legions. Go with Kynareth.","'For Emperor and Empire,' as we say in the legions. Go with Kynareth.","fbmwICImperialVeteran_1Ghostgate4_00323581_4"
"","","I don't accept gifts from strangers.",Neutral,50,"You're a suspicious sort. But maybe I can't blame you. Worried about a request from a strange old man in a strange place like this.","You're a suspicious sort. But maybe I can't blame you. Worried about a request from a strange old man in a strange place like this.","fbmwICImperialVeteran_1Ghostgate3_00323582_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Well, I won't press you. But I would sure be grateful for the favor, if you could see your way to changing your mind.","Well, I won't press you. But I would sure be grateful for the favor, if you could see your way to changing your mind.","fbmwICImperialVeteran_1Ghostgate3_00323582_2"
"","","I am the Nerevarine, and I go to confront Dagoth Ur in his citadel.",Neutral,50,"What a piece of luck! Look. I'm an old Legion veteran, as old as the poor old Emperor, bless his soul. I'm too old for campaigning.","What a piece of luck! Look. I'm an old Legion veteran, as old as the poor old Emperor, bless his soul. I'm too old for campaigning.","fbmwICImperialVeteran_1Ghostgate2_00001c67_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I came this far to look at hell. But I can't go any farther than this.","I came this far to look at hell. But I can't go any farther than this.","fbmwICImperialVeteran_1Ghostgate2_00001c67_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I'd take it kindly if you'd carry this old lucky coin with you when you go to Dagoth Ur.","I'd take it kindly if you'd carry this old lucky coin with you when you go to Dagoth Ur.","fbmwICImperialVeteran_1Ghostgate2_00001c67_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Sort of a token of the tough young hero I used to be. Would you do that for an old man?","Sort of a token of the tough young hero I used to be. Would you do that for an old man?","fbmwICImperialVeteran_1Ghostgate2_00001c67_4"
"","","Perhaps I should keep my business here secret.",Neutral,50,"Suit yourself. I don't know why you'd bother to keep anything a secret here.","Suit yourself. I don't know why you'd bother to keep anything a secret here.","fbmwICImperialVeteran_1Ghostgate1_00001c68_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I was just wondering if you might be headed inside the Ghostfence to Dagoth Ur.","I was just wondering if you might be headed inside the Ghostfence to Dagoth Ur.","fbmwICImperialVeteran_1Ghostgate1_00001c68_2"
