Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I see you have equipped Wraithguard. I wish you luck with it.","I see you have equipped Wraithguard. I wish you luck with it.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_GREETING_000067a1_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Remember. When you first equip Wraithguard, you must endure a terrible shock.","Remember. When you first equip Wraithguard, you must endure a terrible shock.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_GREETING_0000760f_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Even if you are in perfect health, and have fortified your health as much as possible, you are likely to die from the shock.","Even if you are in perfect health, and have fortified your health as much as possible, you are likely to die from the shock.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_GREETING_0000760f_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Don't even think about it until you are much healthier.","Don't even think about it until you are much healthier.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_GREETING_0000760f_3"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Remember. When you first equip Wraithguard, you must endure a terrible shock.","Remember. When you first equip Wraithguard, you must endure a terrible shock.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_GREETING_00007610_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If you are not in perfect health, and have not fortified your health as much as possible, you'll be dead before you hit the ground.","If you are not in perfect health, and have not fortified your health as much as possible, you'll be dead before you hit the ground.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_GREETING_00007610_2"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I have learned all I can from Kagrenac's Planbook and Kagrenac's Journals.","I have learned all I can from Kagrenac's Planbook and Kagrenac's Journals.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_GREETING_00007611_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Now, if you're still willing, I'll try to restore the mythopoeic enchantments on Wraithguard.","Now, if you're still willing, I'll try to restore the mythopoeic enchantments on Wraithguard.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_GREETING_00007611_2"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Patience. When I have had sufficient time to review Kagrenac's Planbook and Kagrenac's Journals, I will try to restore the mythopoeic enchantments on","Patience. When I have had sufficient time to review Kagrenac's Planbook and Kagrenac's Journals, I will try to restore the mythopoeic enchantments on","fbmwMQTheBackPath_GREETING_00007612_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Wraithguard.","Wraithguard.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_GREETING_00007612_2"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"If you have really brought me Kagrenac's Planbook and Kagrenac's Journals, I can at least try to restore the mythopoeic enchantments on Wraithguard.","If you have really brought me Kagrenac's Planbook and Kagrenac's Journals, I can at least try to restore the mythopoeic enchantments on Wraithguard.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_GREETING_00007613_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I have nothing. Go away. Leave me in peace... but... wait. What is that you have there? Is that what I think it is?","I have nothing. Go away. Leave me in peace... but... wait. What is that you have there? Is that what I think it is?","fbmwMQTheBackPath_GREETING_00007614_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"That unique dwemer artifact you have?","That unique dwemer artifact you have?","fbmwMQTheBackPath_GREETING_00007614_2"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"So. It's you again. What brings you to visit Yagrum Bagarn, Master Crafter, and Last Living Dwarf?","So. It's you again. What brings you to visit Yagrum Bagarn, Master Crafter, and Last Living Dwarf?","fbmwMQ08_GREETING_00009a8e_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"So. It's you again. What brings you to visit Yagrum Bagarn, Master Crafter, and Last Living Dwarf?","So. It's you again. What brings you to visit Yagrum Bagarn, Master Crafter, and Last Living Dwarf?","fbmwMQ08_GREETING_00009a8f_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"You're here for the Dwemer boots. Tell my gracious Keeper that I have done what I could. Only a Dwemer magecrafter could have done so much.","You're here for the Dwemer boots. Tell my gracious Keeper that I have done what I could. Only a Dwemer magecrafter could have done so much.","fbmwMQ08_GREETING_00009a90_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But only idiots could have created these boots. It shames my race that we must be judged by the works of such lack-wit blunderers.","But only idiots could have created these boots. It shames my race that we must be judged by the works of such lack-wit blunderers.","fbmwMQ08_GREETING_00009a90_2"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I have Lord Fyr's Dwemer boots. That's what you're here for, aren't you?","I have Lord Fyr's Dwemer boots. That's what you're here for, aren't you?","fbmwMQ08_GREETING_00009a91_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Do not harm me, or you will be very sorry. I warn you. Leave me alone, and I will leave you alone.","Do not harm me, or you will be very sorry. I warn you. Leave me alone, and I will leave you alone.","fbmwMQ08_GREETING_00009a92_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I have nothing. Go away. Leave me in peace.","I have nothing. Go away. Leave me in peace.","fbmwMQ08_GREETING_00009a93_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"So. It's you again. What brings you to visit Yagrum Bagarn, Master Crafter, and Last Living Dwarf?","So. It's you again. What brings you to visit Yagrum Bagarn, Master Crafter, and Last Living Dwarf?","fbmwMQ08_GREETING_0001fac2_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"You're here for the Dwemer boots. Tell my gracious Keeper that I have done what I could. Only a Dwemer magecrafter could have done so much.","You're here for the Dwemer boots. Tell my gracious Keeper that I have done what I could. Only a Dwemer magecrafter could have done so much.","fbmwMQ08_GREETING_0001fac1_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But only idiots could have created these boots. It shames my race that we must be judged by the works of such lack-wit blunderers.","But only idiots could have created these boots. It shames my race that we must be judged by the works of such lack-wit blunderers.","fbmwMQ08_GREETING_0001fac1_2"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I have Lord Fyr's Dwemer boots. That's what you're here for, aren't you?","I have Lord Fyr's Dwemer boots. That's what you're here for, aren't you?","fbmwMQ08_GREETING_0001fac0_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"Do not harm me, or you will be very sorry. I warn you. Leave me alone, and I will leave you alone.","Do not harm me, or you will be very sorry. I warn you. Leave me alone, and I will leave you alone.","mwGreetingsUnique_GREETING_0001fabf_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"I have nothing. Go away. Leave me in peace.","I have nothing. Go away. Leave me in peace.","mwGreetingsUnique_GREETING_0001fabe_1"
"","","GREETING",Neutral,50,"You've killed one of my benefactors. And now it is your turn to die.","You've killed one of my benefactors. And now it is your turn to die.","MorroDefaultQuest_GREETING_00009a9f_1"
"","","Please activate Wraithguard.",Neutral,50,"Very well. [Yagrum Bagarn takes the unique Dwemer artifact, and performs a series of manipulations. He then returns it.] Now, the first time you equip Wraithguard, you will experience a terrible shock.","Very well. [Yagrum Bagarn takes the unique Dwemer artifact, and performs a series of manipulations. He then returns it.] Now, the first time you equip Wraithguard, you will experience a terrible shock.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_mwMQBackPath03WraithguardYes_00002104_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If you are in perfect health, I am confident you will survive. But you may want to fortify your health as much as possible beforehand, just in case.","If you are in perfect health, I am confident you will survive. But you may want to fortify your health as much as possible beforehand, just in case.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_mwMQBackPath03WraithguardYes_00002104_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Afterwards, Wraithguard should be working as designed, and everything will be fine.","Afterwards, Wraithguard should be working as designed, and everything will be fine.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_mwMQBackPath03WraithguardYes_00002104_3"
"","","Please activate Wraithguard.",Neutral,50,"Very well. [Yagrum Bagarn takes the unique Dwemer artifact, and performs a series of manipulations. He then returns it.] Now, the first time you equip Wraithguard, you will experience a terrible shock.","Very well. [Yagrum Bagarn takes the unique Dwemer artifact, and performs a series of manipulations. He then returns it.] Now, the first time you equip Wraithguard, you will experience a terrible shock.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_mwMQBackPath03WraithguardYes_00002106_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If you are in perfect health, and you have fortified your health as much as possible, there is a good chance you will survive. But the risk is great, and you MUST fortify your health as much as possible beforehand.","If you are in perfect health, and you have fortified your health as much as possible, there is a good chance you will survive. But the risk is great, and you MUST fortify your health as much as possible beforehand.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_mwMQBackPath03WraithguardYes_00002106_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Afterwards, Wraithguard should be working as designed, and everything will be fine.","Afterwards, Wraithguard should be working as designed, and everything will be fine.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_mwMQBackPath03WraithguardYes_00002106_3"
"","","Please activate Wraithguard.",Neutral,50,"Very well. [Yagrum Bagarn takes the unique Dwemer artifact, and performs a series of manipulations. He then returns it.] Now, the first time you equip Wraithguard, you will experience a terrible shock.","Very well. [Yagrum Bagarn takes the unique Dwemer artifact, and performs a series of manipulations. He then returns it.] Now, the first time you equip Wraithguard, you will experience a terrible shock.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_mwMQBackPath03WraithguardYes_00002105_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If you are in perfect health, and you have fortified your health as much as possible, there is a slight chance you will survive.","If you are in perfect health, and you have fortified your health as much as possible, there is a slight chance you will survive.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_mwMQBackPath03WraithguardYes_00002105_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If you survived, Wraithguard would work as designed. If you eat right, exercise, and improve your health, when you are much healthier, then you might risk equipping Wraithguard.","If you survived, Wraithguard would work as designed. If you eat right, exercise, and improve your health, when you are much healthier, then you might risk equipping Wraithguard.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_mwMQBackPath03WraithguardYes_00002105_3"
"","","Not right now. I'd like to prepare myself.",Neutral,50,"Very well. Whenever you are ready, come back, and I'll perform the necessary procedures.","Very well. Whenever you are ready, come back, and I'll perform the necessary procedures.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_mwMQBackPath03WraithguardNo_00002102_1"
"","","Disappearance of the Dwarves",Neutral,50,"Hmm.... I cannot say what happened. I was not there to observe. I was in an Outer Realm at the time, and when I came back, my people were gone.","Hmm.... I cannot say what happened. I was not there to observe. I was in an Outer Realm at the time, and when I came back, my people were gone.","MorroDefaultQuest_1DisappearanceSofStheSDwarves_0001faad_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I left Red Mountain, wandering Tamriel for years, searching our deserted colonies, looking for a survivor or an explanation.","I left Red Mountain, wandering Tamriel for years, searching our deserted colonies, looking for a survivor or an explanation.","MorroDefaultQuest_1DisappearanceSofStheSDwarves_0001faad_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Then, a long, long time ago, I returned to Red Mountain, still looking for answers. Instead, I found corprus disease, and I have been here ever since.","Then, a long, long time ago, I returned to Red Mountain, still looking for answers. Instead, I found corprus disease, and I have been here ever since.","MorroDefaultQuest_1DisappearanceSofStheSDwarves_0001faad_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I have theories, if you are interested.","I have theories, if you are interested.","MorroDefaultQuest_1DisappearanceSofStheSDwarves_0001faad_4"
"","","Kagrenac's enchantments",Neutral,50,"Let me be clear. It is better that Kagrenac's work be lost forever. Perhaps I could recreate his work. But I wouldn't.","Let me be clear. It is better that Kagrenac's work be lost forever. Perhaps I could recreate his work. But I wouldn't.","fbmwMQCompletedDialogues_1KagrenacAsSenchantments_00aafab5_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But I wouldn't. Perhaps I could rediscover the principles of Kagrenac's tools that permit them to draw power from Lorkhan's Heart. But I wouldn't.","But I wouldn't. Perhaps I could rediscover the principles of Kagrenac's tools that permit them to draw power from Lorkhan's Heart. But I wouldn't.","fbmwMQCompletedDialogues_1KagrenacAsSenchantments_00aafab5_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"That tale is finished. Forever.","That tale is finished. Forever.","fbmwMQCompletedDialogues_1KagrenacAsSenchantments_00aafab5_3"
"","","Mythopoeic Enchantments",Neutral,50,"You have equipped Wraithguard and lived to tell about it. Congratulations.","You have equipped Wraithguard and lived to tell about it. Congratulations.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1mythopoeicSenchantments_00aafaba_1"
"","","Mythopoeic Enchantments",Neutral,50,"I won't even consider this procedure until you are in perfect health. Come back to me when you're completely healed.","I won't even consider this procedure until you are in perfect health. Come back to me when you're completely healed.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1mythopoeicSenchantments_00002107_1"
"","","Mythopoeic Enchantments",Neutral,50,"I've studied Kagrenac's Planbook and Journals. I know what to do. The artifact simply must be harmonized with your personal magicka signature.","I've studied Kagrenac's Planbook and Journals. I know what to do. The artifact simply must be harmonized with your personal magicka signature.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1mythopoeicSenchantments_000020ff_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"However, the process is dangerous. You will certainly be injured. I am certain, however, that you will survive the process.","However, the process is dangerous. You will certainly be injured. I am certain, however, that you will survive the process.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1mythopoeicSenchantments_000020ff_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Are you ready for me to activate Wraithguard and harmonize it to your magicka signature?","Are you ready for me to activate Wraithguard and harmonize it to your magicka signature?","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1mythopoeicSenchantments_000020ff_3"
"","","Mythopoeic Enchantments",Neutral,50,"I've studied Kagrenac's Planbook and Journals. I know what to do. The artifact simply must be harmonized with your personal magicka signature.","I've studied Kagrenac's Planbook and Journals. I know what to do. The artifact simply must be harmonized with your personal magicka signature.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1mythopoeicSenchantments_00002101_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"However, the process is dangerous. You will certainly be injured. I am not sure you will survive the process.","However, the process is dangerous. You will certainly be injured. I am not sure you will survive the process.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1mythopoeicSenchantments_00002101_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"There is no risk now, while I harmonize the artifact with your magicka, but when you first equip Wraithguard, you should fortify your health as much as possible.","There is no risk now, while I harmonize the artifact with your magicka, but when you first equip Wraithguard, you should fortify your health as much as possible.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1mythopoeicSenchantments_00002101_4"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Are you ready for me to activate Wraithguard and harmonize it to your magicka signature?","Are you ready for me to activate Wraithguard and harmonize it to your magicka signature?","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1mythopoeicSenchantments_00002101_3"
"","","Mythopoeic Enchantments",Neutral,50,"I've studied Kagrenac's Planbook and Journals. I know what to do. The artifact simply must be harmonized with your personal magicka signature.","I've studied Kagrenac's Planbook and Journals. I know what to do. The artifact simply must be harmonized with your personal magicka signature.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1mythopoeicSenchantments_00002100_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"However, the process is dangerous, and I think equipping Wraithguard would kill you. There is no risk now, while I harmonize the artifact with your magicka, but when you first equip Wraithguard, you would be badly injured, and probably killed.","However, the process is dangerous, and I think equipping Wraithguard would kill you. There is no risk now, while I harmonize the artifact with your magicka, but when you first equip Wraithguard, you would be badly injured, and probably killed.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1mythopoeicSenchantments_00002100_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Are you ready for me to activate Wraithguard and harmonize it to your magicka signature?","Are you ready for me to activate Wraithguard and harmonize it to your magicka signature?","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1mythopoeicSenchantments_00002100_3"
"","","Mythopoeic Enchantments",Neutral,50,"I'm ready, but you don't have the unique Dwemer artifact.","I'm ready, but you don't have the unique Dwemer artifact.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1mythopoeicSenchantments_00f8e3af_1"
"","","Mythopoeic Enchantments",Neutral,50,"Patience! These things take time!","Patience! These things take time!","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1mythopoeicSenchantments_00f8e3b0_1"
"","","Mythopoeic Enchantments",Neutral,50,"You've found Kagrenac's Journals and Kagrenac's Planbook! Good. I'll take them and study them. It shouldn't take long. Give me a day, then come back, and I think I can restore Wraithguard's mythopoeic enchantments.","You've found Kagrenac's Journals and Kagrenac's Planbook! Good. I'll take them and study them. It shouldn't take long. Give me a day, then come back, and I think I can restore Wraithguard's mythopoeic enchantments.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1mythopoeicSenchantments_00f8e3b1_1"
"","","Mythopoeic Enchantments",Neutral,50,"You've found Kagrenac's Journals and Kagrenac's Planbook. But where is the unique Dwemer artifact?","You've found Kagrenac's Journals and Kagrenac's Planbook. But where is the unique Dwemer artifact?","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1mythopoeicSenchantments_00f8e3b2_1"
"","","Mythopoeic Enchantments",Neutral,50,"You must find Kagrenac's Planbook and Kagrenac's Journals and bring them to me before I can attempt to restore the mythopoeic enchantments on Wraithguard.","You must find Kagrenac's Planbook and Kagrenac's Journals and bring them to me before I can attempt to restore the mythopoeic enchantments on Wraithguard.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1mythopoeicSenchantments_00f8e3b3_1"
"","","Mythopoeic Enchantments",Neutral,50,"Good! Very good! You have found Kagrenac's Journals! Now you must also find Kagrenac's Planbook and bring them to me before I can attempt to restore the mythopoeic enchantments on Wraithguard.","Good! Very good! You have found Kagrenac's Journals! Now you must also find Kagrenac's Planbook and bring them to me before I can attempt to restore the mythopoeic enchantments on Wraithguard.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1mythopoeicSenchantments_00f8e3b4_1"
"","","Mythopoeic Enchantments",Neutral,50,"Good! Very good! You have found Kagrenac's Planbook! Now you must also find Kagrenac's Journals and bring them to me before I can attempt to restore the mythopoeic enchantments on Wraithguard.","Good! Very good! You have found Kagrenac's Planbook! Now you must also find Kagrenac's Journals and bring them to me before I can attempt to restore the mythopoeic enchantments on Wraithguard.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1mythopoeicSenchantments_00f8e3b5_1"
"","","Mythopoeic Enchantments",Neutral,50,"I'm not sure I can explain. In his search for the secrets of immortality, Kagrenac sought to control supernatural forces that you might call 'divine'.","I'm not sure I can explain. In his search for the secrets of immortality, Kagrenac sought to control supernatural forces that you might call 'divine'.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1mythopoeicSenchantments_00f8e3b6_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"This artifact -- called 'Wraithguard -- was one of the tools that he created for this purpose. Some believed his tampering with such forces was profane, and terribly dangerous.","This artifact -- called 'Wraithguard -- was one of the tools that he created for this purpose. Some believed his tampering with such forces was profane, and terribly dangerous.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1mythopoeicSenchantments_00f8e3b6_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"You know the Dwemer disappeared? His use of these tools may have been responsible.","You know the Dwemer disappeared? His use of these tools may have been responsible.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1mythopoeicSenchantments_00f8e3b6_3"
"","","Tales of your exploits",Neutral,50,"A remarkable story. A pity to have to destroy Kagrenac's enchantments on the Heart. It would have been interesting to study them.","A remarkable story. A pity to have to destroy Kagrenac's enchantments on the Heart. It would have been interesting to study them.","fbmwMQCompletedDialogues_1talesSofSyourSexploits_00aafabb_1"
"","","Unique Dwemer Artifact",Neutral,50,"Do you know what this is? This is Wraithguard, an enchanted device created ages ago by my former master, High Craftlord Kagrenac, a long-dead Dwemer  mage-smith.","Do you know what this is? This is Wraithguard, an enchanted device created ages ago by my former master, High Craftlord Kagrenac, a long-dead Dwemer  mage-smith.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1uniqueSdwemerSartifact_00aafabd_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I believe it is one of the tools he created to forge mythopoeic enchantments. I was one of Lord Kagrenac's Master Crafters, and though I didn't work on this project, I knew of it from my fellow mage-smiths.","I believe it is one of the tools he created to forge mythopoeic enchantments. I was one of Lord Kagrenac's Master Crafters, and though I didn't work on this project, I knew of it from my fellow mage-smiths.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1uniqueSdwemerSartifact_00aafabd_2"
"","","Kagrenac's Planbook",Neutral,50,"Kagrenac carefully planned all his projects in advance. His planbook will have all his original designs. I don't know where the planbook might be.","Kagrenac carefully planned all his projects in advance. His planbook will have all his original designs. I don't know where the planbook might be.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1KagrenacAsSPlanbook_00aafab7_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I am fairly sure it hasn't been discovered, or Divayth Fyr would have heard, and would have told me.","I am fairly sure it hasn't been discovered, or Divayth Fyr would have heard, and would have told me.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1KagrenacAsSPlanbook_00aafab7_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"That suggests it remains to be discovered in some Dwemer ruin here on Vvardenfell.","That suggests it remains to be discovered in some Dwemer ruin here on Vvardenfell.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1KagrenacAsSPlanbook_00aafab7_3"
"","","Kagrenac's Journals",Neutral,50,"Kagrenac recorded every step in his manufacture and testing of enchanted items.","Kagrenac recorded every step in his manufacture and testing of enchanted items.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1KagrenacAsSJournals_00aafab6_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"His journals will record any modifications or enhancements made to his original designs. I don't know where the journals might be.","His journals will record any modifications or enhancements made to his original designs. I don't know where the journals might be.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1KagrenacAsSJournals_00aafab6_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I am fairly sure they haven't been discovered, or Divayth Fyr would have heard, and would have told me.","I am fairly sure they haven't been discovered, or Divayth Fyr would have heard, and would have told me.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1KagrenacAsSJournals_00aafab6_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"That suggests they remain to be discovered in some Dwemer ruin here on Vvardenfell.","That suggests they remain to be discovered in some Dwemer ruin here on Vvardenfell.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_1KagrenacAsSJournals_00aafab6_4"
"","","Divine Metaphysics",Neutral,50,"This book is just an explanation of some of Kagrenac's theories.","This book is just an explanation of some of Kagrenac's theories.","fbmwMGDwarves_1DivineSMetaphysics_0001faae_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I could spend hours explaining them to you, but Kagrenac is dead, and I believe his theories must die with him.","I could spend hours explaining them to you, but Kagrenac is dead, and I believe his theories must die with him.","fbmwMGDwarves_1DivineSMetaphysics_0001faae_2"
"","","Last Living Dwarf",Neutral,50,"This is how I style myself. I do not know for a fact that I am the last. But in my travels thousands of years ago, I never encountered another.","This is how I style myself. I do not know for a fact that I am the last. But in my travels thousands of years ago, I never encountered another.","MorroDefaultQuest_1LastSLivingSDwarf_00aafab8_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And since I have been here, I often ask Lord Fyr, but he says he has never heard a credible rumor of another Dwemer, on Tamriel, or in any Outer Realm.","And since I have been here, I often ask Lord Fyr, but he says he has never heard a credible rumor of another Dwemer, on Tamriel, or in any Outer Realm.","MorroDefaultQuest_1LastSLivingSDwarf_00aafab8_2"
"","","Hanging Gardens",Neutral,50,"Yes, this book is written in both Aldmeris and in Dwemer.","Yes, this book is written in both Aldmeris and in Dwemer.","MorroDefaultQuest_1HangingSGardens_0001fab4_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Many books were written in both languages in the days of Resdayn when Dunmer and Dwemer ruled together peacefully.","Many books were written in both languages in the days of Resdayn when Dunmer and Dwemer ruled together peacefully.","MorroDefaultQuest_1HangingSGardens_0001fab4_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I'd offer to translate, but this is really just a boring travel guide. If you find any other books in Dwemer, I could translate them for you.","I'd offer to translate, but this is really just a boring travel guide. If you find any other books in Dwemer, I could translate them for you.","MorroDefaultQuest_1HangingSGardens_0001fab4_3"
"","","Gracious Keeper",Neutral,50,"I owe my life to Lord Fyr. He took me in when I was a mad monster, out of my mind.","I owe my life to Lord Fyr. He took me in when I was a mad monster, out of my mind.","MorroDefaultQuest_1graciousSkeeper_00aafab3_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"In time, I emerged from my dementia, and now I am quite lucid most of the time, though my body is still a grotesque and useless prison.","In time, I emerged from my dementia, and now I am quite lucid most of the time, though my body is still a grotesque and useless prison.","MorroDefaultQuest_1graciousSkeeper_00aafab3_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And I still have some feeble hope of a cure. Lord Fyr has tried many spells and potions. None have helped me, but neither have they harmed me.","And I still have some feeble hope of a cure. Lord Fyr has tried many spells and potions. None have helped me, but neither have they harmed me.","MorroDefaultQuest_1graciousSkeeper_00aafab3_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"If anyone can cure this disease, Lord Fyr can.","If anyone can cure this disease, Lord Fyr can.","MorroDefaultQuest_1graciousSkeeper_00aafab3_4"
"","","Bleak Existence",Neutral,50,"Since the disappearance of the Dwarves, I have been alone in this world, trapped in this grim prison. I can scarcely move.","Since the disappearance of the Dwarves, I have been alone in this world, trapped in this grim prison. I can scarcely move.","MorroDefaultQuest_1bleakSexistence_00aafaac_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And my fellow inmates are scarcely good company. The risk of corprus disease deters most visitors.","And my fellow inmates are scarcely good company. The risk of corprus disease deters most visitors.","MorroDefaultQuest_1bleakSexistence_00aafaac_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But if you meet with cultivated minds undaunted by the terrors of the Corprusarium, you might mention your recent interview with the Last Living Dwarf.","But if you meet with cultivated minds undaunted by the terrors of the Corprusarium, you might mention your recent interview with the Last Living Dwarf.","MorroDefaultQuest_1bleakSexistence_00aafaac_3"
"","","Dwemer Boots",Neutral,50,"I gave you the boots. Didn't I?","I gave you the boots. Didn't I?","fbmwMQ08_1DwemerSboots_00aafaaf_1"
"","","Dwemer Boots",Neutral,50,"Lord Fyr obtained these enchanted Dwemer boots from an unfortunate thief.","Lord Fyr obtained these enchanted Dwemer boots from an unfortunate thief.","fbmwMQ08_1DwemerSboots_00aafab0_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"And, given the quality of their craftsmanship, little wonder the fellow came a bad end. But I can do nothing for them.","And, given the quality of their craftsmanship, little wonder the fellow came a bad end. But I can do nothing for them.","fbmwMQ08_1DwemerSboots_00aafab0_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The fundamental enchantment is flawed. Might as well start over again...","The fundamental enchantment is flawed. Might as well start over again...","fbmwMQ08_1DwemerSboots_00aafab0_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"if such a pair of boots could still be fashioned in these benighted latter days. But I have done my best.","if such a pair of boots could still be fashioned in these benighted latter days. But I have done my best.","fbmwMQ08_1DwemerSboots_00aafab0_4"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Take them to Lord Fyr, with my sincere apologies.","Take them to Lord Fyr, with my sincere apologies.","fbmwMQ08_1DwemerSboots_00aafab0_5"
"","","Egg of Time",Neutral,50,"By refreshing my memory with Divine Metaphysics, I believe I can explain. The Dwemer were not unified in their thinking.","By refreshing my memory with "Divine Metaphysics," I believe I can explain. The Dwemer were not unified in their thinking.","fbmwMGDwarves_1EggSofSTime_0001fab1_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Kagrenac and his tonal architects, among them Bthuand Mzahnch, believed they could improve the Dwemer race.","Kagrenac and his tonal architects, among them Bthuand Mzahnch, believed they could improve the Dwemer race.","fbmwMGDwarves_1EggSofSTime_0001fab1_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Others argued that the attempt would be too great a risk.","Others argued that the attempt would be too great a risk.","fbmwMGDwarves_1EggSofSTime_0001fab1_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"The war with Nerevar and the Dunmer may have led Kagrenac to carry out his experiments prematurely.","The war with Nerevar and the Dunmer may have led Kagrenac to carry out his experiments prematurely.","fbmwMGDwarves_1EggSofSTime_0001fab1_4"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Although this book argues that nothing disastrous could result, the disappearance of my race argues otherwise.","Although this book argues that nothing disastrous could result, the disappearance of my race argues otherwise.","fbmwMGDwarves_1EggSofSTime_0001fab1_5"
"","","Egg of Time",Neutral,50,"I had not seen this book before, but it reinforces some my own theories. If you were to find more books like this, bring them to me and perhaps I could tell you more.","I had not seen this book before, but it reinforces some my own theories. If you were to find more books like this, bring them to me and perhaps I could tell you more.","fbmwMGDwarves_1EggSofSTime_0001fab2_1"
"","","Theories",Neutral,50,"Lord Kagrenac, the foremost arcane philosopher and magecrafter of my era, devised tools to shape mythopoeic forces, intending to transcend the limits of Dwemer mortality.","Lord Kagrenac, the foremost arcane philosopher and magecrafter of my era, devised tools to shape mythopoeic forces, intending to transcend the limits of Dwemer mortality.","MorroDefaultQuest_1theories_00aafabc_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"However, in reviewing his formulae, some logicians argued that side effects were unpredictable, and errors might be catastrophic.","However, in reviewing his formulae, some logicians argued that side effects were unpredictable, and errors might be catastrophic.","MorroDefaultQuest_1theories_00aafabc_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I think Kagrenac might have succeeded in granting our race eternal life, with unforeseen consequences --","I think Kagrenac might have succeeded in granting our race eternal life, with unforeseen consequences --","MorroDefaultQuest_1theories_00aafabc_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"such as wholesale displacement to an Outer Realm. Or he may have erred, and utterly destroyed our race.","such as wholesale displacement to an Outer Realm. Or he may have erred, and utterly destroyed our race.","MorroDefaultQuest_1theories_00aafabc_4"
"","","My Race",Neutral,50,"Once I was a Master Crafter in the service of Lord Kagrenac, chief architect of the great Second Empire freeholds, and the greatest enchanter of his time.","Once I was a Master Crafter in the service of Lord Kagrenac, chief architect of the great Second Empire freeholds, and the greatest enchanter of his time.","MorroDefaultQuest_1mySrace_00aafab9_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I could not match the genius of Lord Kagrenac, but what he could envision, I and my colleagues could build. All of that is gone forever.","I could not match the genius of Lord Kagrenac, but what he could envision, I and my colleagues could build. All of that is gone forever.","MorroDefaultQuest_1mySrace_00aafab9_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I still retain my cunning, but my hands and eyes fail me, and my memories have long faded.","I still retain my cunning, but my hands and eyes fail me, and my memories have long faded.","MorroDefaultQuest_1mySrace_00aafab9_3"
"","","",Neutral,50,"My only consolation is each day to mock the gods who destroyed my race, and condemned me to this bleak existence.","My only consolation is each day to mock the gods who destroyed my race, and condemned me to this bleak existence.","MorroDefaultQuest_1mySrace_00aafab9_4"
"","","Sounds dangerous to me. Thank you.",Neutral,50,"It probably is very dangerous. You couldn't have known, but you took a great risk handling it.","It probably is very dangerous. You couldn't have known, but you took a great risk handling it.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_mwMQBackPath01Dangerous_00f8e3b8_1"
"","","Plead on the basis of my reputation.",Neutral,50,"I see. I thought I had heard of you. But I had not realized that all these good deeds you describe were your handiwork. Yes. I am satisfied of your motivations and character.","I see. I thought I had heard of you. But I had not realized that all these good deeds you describe were your handiwork. Yes. I am satisfied of your motivations and character.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_mwMQBackPath02Deeds_00f8e3ba_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I believe I can trust you. If you can find Kagrenac's Planbook and Kagrenac's Journals and bring them to me, I will do my best to restore Wraithguard to its proper functions.","I believe I can trust you. If you can find Kagrenac's Planbook and Kagrenac's Journals and bring them to me, I will do my best to restore Wraithguard to its proper functions.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_mwMQBackPath02Deeds_00f8e3ba_2"
"","","Plead on the basis of my reputation.",Neutral,50,"Well. Perhaps your reputation is not all that it might be. But I like you, and I trust my instincts. If you can find Kagrenac's Planbook and Kagrenac's Journals and bring them to me, I will do my best to restore Wraithguard to its proper functions.","Well. Perhaps your reputation is not all that it might be. But I like you, and I trust my instincts. If you can find Kagrenac's Planbook and Kagrenac's Journals and bring them to me, I will do my best to restore Wraithguard to its proper functions.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_mwMQBackPath02Deeds_00f8e3bb_1"
"","","Plead on the basis of my reputation.",Neutral,50,"I'm sorry. Your reputation is not so great that I would risk putting such a powerful device in your hands without a very compelling reason.","I'm sorry. Your reputation is not so great that I would risk putting such a powerful device in your hands without a very compelling reason.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_mwMQBackPath02Deeds_00f8e3bc_1"
"","","I don't think this artifact is working. Can you restore the artifact?",Neutral,50,"I'm not sure. Let me see. [Examines the artifact.]","I'm not sure. Let me see. [Examines the artifact.]","fbmwMQTheBackPath_mwMQBackPath01Restore_00f8e3be_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"No. I don't think so. Not without Kagrenac's Planbook and Kagrenac's Journals. But, if the originals still exist, and I could study them, then, yes, perhaps I could restore the artifact.","No. I don't think so. Not without Kagrenac's Planbook and Kagrenac's Journals. But, if the originals still exist, and I could study them, then, yes, perhaps I could restore the artifact.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_mwMQBackPath01Restore_00f8e3be_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Whether I should or would, on the other hand, that is a different matter.","Whether I should or would, on the other hand, that is a different matter.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_mwMQBackPath01Restore_00f8e3be_3"
"","","Offer payment or service.",Neutral,50,"This is not a matter of personal gain. This is a matter of right and wrong, and the risk of potential harm... and the question of your motivations and character.","This is not a matter of personal gain. This is a matter of right and wrong, and the risk of potential harm... and the question of your motivations and character.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_mwMQBackPath02Pay_00f8e3c0_1"
"","","Show him 'Vivec's Plan' and 'Dagoth Ur's Plans'.",Neutral,50,"[Reads 'Vivec's Plan' and 'Dagoth Ur's Plans'.]","[Reads 'Vivec's Plan' and 'Dagoth Ur's Plans'.]","fbmwMQTheBackPath_mwMQBackPath02Plans_00f8e3c2_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I see. Dagoth Ur's use of the enchantments on the Heart of Lorkhan presents a great danger. And you need this artifact -- Wraithguard -- to destroy those enchantments, and Dagoth Ur.","I see. Dagoth Ur's use of the enchantments on the Heart of Lorkhan presents a great danger. And you need this artifact -- Wraithguard -- to destroy those enchantments, and Dagoth Ur.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_mwMQBackPath02Plans_00f8e3c2_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"This is a good cause. If you can find Kagrenac's Planbook and Kagrenac's Journals and bring them to me, I will do my best to restore Wraithguard to its proper functions.","This is a good cause. If you can find Kagrenac's Planbook and Kagrenac's Journals and bring them to me, I will do my best to restore Wraithguard to its proper functions.","fbmwMQTheBackPath_mwMQBackPath02Plans_00f8e3c2_3"
