Race,Gender,Dialogue,Emotion-Type,Emotion-Value,Responsetext,Translation,Filename
"","","Offer to fight a dual to the death.",Neutral,50,"You are not an unworthy opponent. I hear honor in your words, and courage in your heart. I would regret killing you.","You are not an unworthy opponent. I hear honor in your words, and courage in your heart. I would regret killing you.","fbmwMQ06_fbmwMQ06Challenge_0001dd74_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But regret even more should you kill me. Very well. Perhaps Sul-Matuul will be angry with me. But I think I can bear that.","But regret even more should you kill me. Very well. Perhaps Sul-Matuul will be angry with me. But I think I can bear that.","fbmwMQ06_fbmwMQ06Challenge_0001dd74_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Go to the Ashkhan's Yurt and speak with Sul-Matuul. Ask him your questions, and tell him I have sent you.","Go to the Ashkhan's Yurt and speak with Sul-Matuul. Ask him your questions, and tell him I have sent you.","fbmwMQ06_fbmwMQ06Challenge_0001dd74_3"
"","","Offer to fight a dual to the death.",Neutral,50,"You would not stand a chance against me. But I hear honor in your words, and courage in your heart. Very well.","You would not stand a chance against me. But I hear honor in your words, and courage in your heart. Very well.","fbmwMQ06_fbmwMQ06Challenge_0001dd75_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Perhaps Sul-Matuul will be angry with me. But I think I can bear that. Go to the Ashkhan's Yurt and speak with Sul-Matuul.","Perhaps Sul-Matuul will be angry with me. But I think I can bear that. Go to the Ashkhan's Yurt and speak with Sul-Matuul.","fbmwMQ06_fbmwMQ06Challenge_0001dd75_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Ask him your questions, and tell him I have sent you.","Ask him your questions, and tell him I have sent you.","fbmwMQ06_fbmwMQ06Challenge_0001dd75_3"
"","","Offer to fight a dual to the death.",Neutral,50,"You are a mere stripling. I might win as much honor by killing a dog. You shall not speak to Sul-Matuul or Nibani Maesa.","You are a mere stripling. I might win as much honor by killing a dog. You shall not speak to Sul-Matuul or Nibani Maesa.","fbmwMQ06_fbmwMQ06Challenge_0001dd76_1"
"","","I am a great hero.",Neutral,50,"These are indeed worthy deeds. I hear the truth in your words. Perhaps Sul-Matuul will be angry with me. But I think I can bear that.","These are indeed worthy deeds. I hear the truth in your words. Perhaps Sul-Matuul will be angry with me. But I think I can bear that.","fbmwMQ06_fbmwMQ06Boast_0001e4ac_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Go to the Ashkhan's Yurt and speak with Sul-Matuul. Ask him your questions, and tell him I have sent you.","Go to the Ashkhan's Yurt and speak with Sul-Matuul. Ask him your questions, and tell him I have sent you.","fbmwMQ06_fbmwMQ06Boast_0001e4ac_2"
"","","I am a great hero.",Neutral,50,"Hmm. I know not what to make of your deeds. Your words may be more worthy than your deeds. But you are well-spoken, and you do tell a pretty tale.","Hmm. I know not what to make of your deeds. Your words may be more worthy than your deeds. But you are well-spoken, and you do tell a pretty tale.","fbmwMQ06_fbmwMQ06Boast_0001e4ad_1"
"","","",Neutral,50," Perhaps Sul-Matuul will be angry with me. But I think I can bear that. Go to the Ashkhan's Yurt and speak with Sul-Matuul.","Perhaps Sul-Matuul will be angry with me. But I think I can bear that. Go to the Ashkhan's Yurt and speak with Sul-Matuul.","fbmwMQ06_fbmwMQ06Boast_0001e4ad_2"
"","","",Neutral,50," Ask him your questions, and tell him I have sent you.","Ask him your questions, and tell him I have sent you.","fbmwMQ06_fbmwMQ06Boast_0001e4ad_3"
"","","I am a great hero.",Neutral,50,"You think well of yourself. But I do not share your opinion. You shall not speak to Sul-Matuul or Nibani Maesa.","You think well of yourself. But I do not share your opinion. You shall not speak to Sul-Matuul or Nibani Maesa.","fbmwMQ06_fbmwMQ06Boast_0001e4ae_1"
"","","I have learned much of the cult.",Neutral,50,"Hmm. These are not simple matters. You know a great deal more than I would have thought. And some of what you say is news to me.","Hmm. These are not simple matters. You know a great deal more than I would have thought. And some of what you say is news to me.","fbmwMQ06_fbmwMQ06HumbleKnowledge_0001e4b0_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I believe you should speak to Sul-Matuul. Perhaps he will be angry with me. But I think I can bear that.","I believe you should speak to Sul-Matuul. Perhaps he will be angry with me. But I think I can bear that.","fbmwMQ06_fbmwMQ06HumbleKnowledge_0001e4b0_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Go to the Ashkhan's Yurt and speak with Sul-Matuul. Ask him your questions, and tell him I have sent you.","Go to the Ashkhan's Yurt and speak with Sul-Matuul. Ask him your questions, and tell him I have sent you.","fbmwMQ06_fbmwMQ06HumbleKnowledge_0001e4b0_3"
"","","I have learned much of the cult.",Neutral,50,"All of that may be true, and I'm sure you think it is very important, but it has nothing to do with us -- at least, not the way you tell it.","All of that may be true, and I'm sure you think it is very important, but it has nothing to do with us -- at least, not the way you tell it.","fbmwMQ06_fbmwMQ06HumbleKnowledge_0001e4b1_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I'm sorry, but I will not let you bother Sul-Matuul or Nibani Maesa with all this.","I'm sorry, but I will not let you bother Sul-Matuul or Nibani Maesa with all this.","fbmwMQ06_fbmwMQ06HumbleKnowledge_0001e4b1_2"
"","","I offer you 200 gold as tribute.",Neutral,50,"Yes, a gift of 200 gold coins. That is an earnest proof of your respect. Yes, I believe you should speak to our ashkhan.","Yes, a gift of 200 gold coins. That is an earnest proof of your respect. Yes, I believe you should speak to our ashkhan.","fbmwMQ06_fbmwMQ06Bribe_0001e4b3_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Perhaps he will be angry with me. But I think I can bear that. Go to the Ashkhan's Yurt and speak with Sul-Matuul.","Perhaps he will be angry with me. But I think I can bear that. Go to the Ashkhan's Yurt and speak with Sul-Matuul.","fbmwMQ06_fbmwMQ06Bribe_0001e4b3_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Ask him your questions, and tell him I have sent you.","Ask him your questions, and tell him I have sent you.","fbmwMQ06_fbmwMQ06Bribe_0001e4b3_3"
"","","Nerevarine Prophecies",Neutral,50,"I still can't believe it. An outlander.... But you are an outlander no more. You came to us as an outlander, according to prophecy.","I still can't believe it. An outlander.... But you are an outlander no more. You came to us as an outlander, according to prophecy.","fbmwMQ10_1NerevarineSprophecies_0001dd6e_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"But now you are one of us.","But now you are one of us.","fbmwMQ10_1NerevarineSprophecies_0001dd6e_2"
"","","Nerevarine Prophecies",Neutral,50,"It is strange to hear an outlander claim the signs of prophecy.","It is strange to hear an outlander claim the signs of prophecy.","fbmwMQ06_1NerevarineSprophecies_0001dd6f_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Stranger still to hear an outlander speak of Nerevar Moon-and-Star, and ask to be tested. Very strange.","Stranger still to hear an outlander speak of Nerevar Moon-and-Star, and ask to be tested. Very strange.","fbmwMQ06_1NerevarineSprophecies_0001dd6f_2"
"","","Nerevarine Prophecies",Neutral,50,"Go to Sul-Matuul's yurt. Tell him that Zabamund has sent you to speak to him.","Go to Sul-Matuul's yurt. Tell him that Zabamund has sent you to speak to him.","fbmwMQ06_1NerevarineSprophecies_0001dd70_1"
"","","Nerevarine Prophecies",Neutral,50,"I will not listen. I will only hear your word of challenge.","I will not listen. I will only hear your word of challenge.","fbmwMQ06_1NerevarineSprophecies_0001dd71_1"
"","","Nerevarine Prophecies",Neutral,50,"The Nerevarine Prophecies are not for outlanders. Why should Sul-Matuul and Nibani Maesa speak to you about these things?","The Nerevarine Prophecies are not for outlanders. Why should Sul-Matuul and Nibani Maesa speak to you about these things?","fbmwMQ06_1NerevarineSprophecies_0001dd72_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"Who are you, that we should trust you?","Who are you, that we should trust you?","fbmwMQ06_1NerevarineSprophecies_0001dd72_2"
"","","Thoughtful Gift",Neutral,50,"Challenge me. The gift I want from you is your blood.","Challenge me. The gift I want from you is your blood.","fbmwMQ06_1thoughtfulSgift_0001dd55_1"
"","","Thoughtful Gift",Neutral,50,"Challenge me. The gift I want from you is your blood.","Challenge me. The gift I want from you is your blood.","fbmwMQ06_1thoughtfulSgift_0001dd56_1"
"","","Thoughtful Gift",Neutral,50,"It is our custom. Among strangers, we honor this custom with gold.","It is our custom. Among strangers, we honor this custom with gold.","fbmwMQ06_1thoughtfulSgift_0032110c_1"
"","","Vision of Azura",Neutral,50,"Surely we are living in the greatest days of the world. I can only hope we will survive them, and tell these stories again and again, when Dagoth Ur is defeated.","Surely we are living in the greatest days of the world. I can only hope we will survive them, and tell these stories again and again, when Dagoth Ur is defeated.","MorroDefaultQuest_1visionSofSAzura_00aa1f48_1"
"","","Harrowing",Neutral,50,"Among my people, I am accounted brave and able. But I would not go there. These are tales to be told to my sons, and the sons of my sons.","Among my people, I am accounted brave and able. But I would not go there. These are tales to be told to my sons, and the sons of my sons.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Harrowing_00001c5d_1"
"","","Talk",Neutral,50,"Challenge me, if you are not afraid.","Challenge me, if you are not afraid.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Talk_00aadd42_1"
"","","Talk",Neutral,50,"Challenge me, if you are not afraid.","Challenge me, if you are not afraid.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Talk_00aadd43_1"
"","","Talk",Neutral,50,"Welcome, clanfriend. Nibani Maesa has told me that she thinks you may be the Nerevarine, and that she has promised to counsel you.","Welcome, clanfriend. Nibani Maesa has told me that she thinks you may be the Nerevarine, and that she has promised to counsel you.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Talk_00aadd44_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"There is little that can surprise me. But Nibani Maesa is no one's fool. You will find her in her yurt.","There is little that can surprise me. But Nibani Maesa is no one's fool. You will find her in her yurt.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Talk_00aadd44_2"
"","","Talk",Neutral,50,"Go and speak to Sul-Matuul. You have earned the right. Speak with respect, and say you have bested his gulakhan in ritual challenge.","Go and speak to Sul-Matuul. You have earned the right. Speak with respect, and say you have bested his gulakhan in ritual challenge.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Talk_00aadd45_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"His yurt is the central one in the group of five yurts beneath one awning.","His yurt is the central one in the group of five yurts beneath one awning.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Talk_00aadd45_2"
"","","Talk",Neutral,50,"You have no standing among us, outlander. But you speak well, and with respect. So I will explain.","You have no standing among us, outlander. But you speak well, and with respect. So I will explain.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Talk_00aadd46_1"
"","","",Neutral,50,"It is against our customs that an outlander should speak to an ashkhan or wise woman.","It is against our customs that an outlander should speak to an ashkhan or wise woman.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Talk_00aadd46_2"
"","","",Neutral,50,"I'll tell you, also, that Sul-Matuul has no love for outlanders.","I'll tell you, also, that Sul-Matuul has no love for outlanders.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Talk_00aadd46_3"
"","","Talk",Neutral,50,"Sul-Matuul will not talk to you. Nibani Maesa will not talk to you. You have no standing among us, outlander.","Sul-Matuul will not talk to you. Nibani Maesa will not talk to you. You have no standing among us, outlander.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Talk_00aadd47_1"
"","","Talk",Neutral,50,"Perhaps it is not your fault. But your talk does not interest me.","Perhaps it is not your fault. But your talk does not interest me.","MorroDefaultQuest_1Talk_00aadd48_1"
